<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Racing on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/racing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Racing on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:47:37 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/racing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Drift Boss</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/drift-boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:47:37 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/drift-boss/</guid>
      <description>Drift your car like a boss. Drift left and right with good timing.
Concentrate and anticipate your drifts and skids in tight spots.
How many points can you score?
Features: Great arcade 3d environment Unlock cool vehicles by collecting more points. Unlock trucks, taxis, police cars, ice cream trucks, ambulances, firetrucks and more. Full responsive design Full screen capability Great soundtracknd theme. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Truck Driving</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/monster-truck-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/monster-truck-driving/</guid>
      <description>Control your monster truck to reach the flag.
Boost, brake and tilt your truck left/right to navigate the path.
Earn stars by completing the level in record time.
Features: Interactive tutorial Use stars to unlock cool characters such as a cool flaming truck, Batman truck, Shark truck, Hyena truck and more. Panning function to plan your routes 20 challenging levels Play repeatedly to get the best high score Upbeat theme Monster Truck and Dirt Bike enthusiasts will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biker Lane</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/biker-lane/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/biker-lane/</guid>
      <description>Control your bike rider to reach the flag.
Boost, brake and tilt your bike left/right to navigate the tricky roads.
Earn stars by completing the level in record time.
Features: Interactive tutorial Use stars to unlock cool characters such as grandma biker, traffic police biker, punk biker, and pro biker. Panning function to plan your routes 20 challenging levels Play repeatedly to get the best high score Upbeat theme Motorcycle and moto x3m enthusiasts will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confident Driver</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/confident-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/confident-driver/</guid>
      <description>How fast are your reflexes? Control your car, pick the right lanes and avoid any crashes to win the level.
Features Drive alongside other vehicles such as mini coopers, new york taxi cabs, trucks, police cars and more Precise and accurate turning, allowing users to cut really sharp corners Beautiful graphics with vehicles closely resembling real vehicles A variety of obstacles such as oil spills, roadblocks, ice and more Challenging levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oddbods Monster Truck Driving</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-monster-truck-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-monster-truck-driving/</guid>
      <description>Control your Oddbods monster truck to reach the flag.
Boost, brake and tilt your truck left/right to navigate the path.
Earn stars by completing the level in record time.
Features: Drive with all 7 Oddbods, including Fuse, Bubbles, Pogo, Zee, Slick, Jeff and Newt. Interactive tutorial Each Oddbod brings something special Use stars to unlock cool vehicles Panning function to plan your routes 20 challenging levels Play repeatedly to get the best high score Upbeat theme Monster Truck and Dirt Bike enthusiasts will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Lane Racing</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/fast-lane-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/fast-lane-racing/</guid>
      <description>Race against other cars.
Tap to switch lanes. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash into other cars!
Keep on your toes and be prepared to switch lanes quickly in this fastlane game.
Features: Endless gameplay Urban hip hop racing theme Extremely simple controls Simple, linear high score system Fans of racing and driving games will love this.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
