<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arcade on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/arcade/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Arcade on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/arcade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alpha Space Invasion</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/alpha-space-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:58 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/alpha-space-invasion/</guid>
      <description>Alpha sector is under invasion. Young pilot, your task is simple. Warp into the sector, and destroy enemy spacecraft before they destroy you.
Avoid the asteroids and keep your shields high. Rake up as many hits as you can!
Features: Interactive tutorial Simple controls (keyboard on desktop, touch controls on mobile) Endless gameplay Fans of sci-fi movies such as Star Wars, Star Trek, Battlestar Galactica and Guardians of the Galaxy will - love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bobblehead Soccer Royale</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bobblehead-soccer-royale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:56:54 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bobblehead-soccer-royale/</guid>
      <description>Move your bobblehead soccer stars around the field. Kick the goals into the opponent&amp;rsquo;s goal.
Collect the powerups to gain an edge over your opponents.
Features: Mad physics that trumps realism Fun and vibrant soccer atmosphere Funny caricature expressions Challenge over 20+ top soccer players in the world Increasingly challenging levels. Get to Level 3 and the game really heats up. Forget FIFA World Cup, fans of puppet soccer fans will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cam and Leon Donut Hop</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cam-and-leon-donut-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:55:10 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cam-and-leon-donut-hop/</guid>
      <description>Brought to you by the creators of a 3D animation, Cam and Leon Donut Hop features 2 funny and cute characters, hopping their way around the park.
Hop in and out of donuts, but don&amp;rsquo;t hit the obstacles!
Features Interactive tutorial Easy to play, hard to master Increasingly challenging obstacles Unlock different characters as you progress. Gain access to Leon, Ladybird, Ice Cube and Pepper Shaker! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways to Die 2 the Games</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:50:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</guid>
      <description>Dumb Ways to Die is back with a bigger and better sequel to the original.
In Dumb Ways To Die 2 - The Games, now you can access various maps and locations to try out even more fun and dangerous challenges.
Collect tokens to unlock different aspects of the city, while complete mini challenges perfectly (or imperfectly, depending on how you play). Score points to keep your ranking high.
Play in cool locations such as Adrenaland, Drown Town, Dumbest of the Dumb, and Freezerville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drift Boss</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/drift-boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:47:37 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/drift-boss/</guid>
      <description>Drift your car like a boss. Drift left and right with good timing.
Concentrate and anticipate your drifts and skids in tight spots.
How many points can you score?
Features: Great arcade 3d environment Unlock cool vehicles by collecting more points. Unlock trucks, taxis, police cars, ice cream trucks, ambulances, firetrucks and more. Full responsive design Full screen capability Great soundtracknd theme. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinosaur Run</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dinosaur-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:46:46 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dinosaur-run/</guid>
      <description>Play a cute and lovable T-Rex running across a desert.
Time your dino jumps to avoid the different obstacles.
How high can you score?
Features: Cool pixel artwork with T Rex dinosaur. Classic grayscale theme set in prehistoric era. Jump over a variety of plants and cactus. Easy to play, hard to master. The background accelerates and decelerates occasionally, to keep you on your toes. Responsive design with fullscreen capability Works great on Chrome and any modern HTML5 browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stupid Zombies</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stupid-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:44:27 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stupid-zombies/</guid>
      <description>One man, one shotgun and a whole lot of zombies. You are humanity&amp;rsquo;s last hope, and it&amp;rsquo;s your job to keep them brainless.
Adjust your shots and angles, and you watch your bullets ricochet from wall to wall, elegantly picking off each zombie&amp;rsquo;s arms and limbs.
Features: 4 giant stages with over 360 challenging levels Exciting zombie theme Simple and innovative ricochet based gameplay. Defeat the stupid zombies with brains and ingenuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duck Carnival Shoot</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/duck-carnival-shoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/duck-carnival-shoot/</guid>
      <description>Take aim and shoot the ducks, before the time runs out!
Earn coins to upgrade your accuracy.
Complete mini missions to earn more coins.
Features: Cute ducks with funny outfits Fun and challenging gameplay. These ducks will surprise you. Interactive tutorial Play interesting mini missions. Gun down Mafia Duck Boss, Hunt the Police, and shoot all Ducks in Business Suits! Disclaimer: No real ducks are harmed in the production of this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pro Bowling 3D</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pro-bowling-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pro-bowling-3d/</guid>
      <description>Position the bowling ball. Then, flick or trace a curve to roll the ball.
How many strikes can you accumulate? Are you the bowling king?
Features: Beautiful bowling arcade. Intuitive tap-and-swipe control. Gorgeous balls. Bowl like a pro. Light background noise for ambience effect. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classic Pinball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/classic-pinball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/classic-pinball/</guid>
      <description>Move your paddle to hit the steel ball. Watch as the ball bounces around the arcade machine, raking up points for you.
You only have three balls. Make them count!
Features: Interactive tutorial Easy to learn, hard to master Classic theme Pumping background music and sound effects </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank Battle</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tank-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tank-battle/</guid>
      <description>Two tanks emerge on the battlefield. Only one will survive. Can you outsmart the other tank?
Collect ammo crates and powerups. Navigate your way to the enemy tank. Fire away!
This is the perfect game to play with friends and family.
Tip: For two player mode, play on the same device (one finger on each side). Enhance social interaction of your audience!
Features: Interactive tutorial to learn the ropes Collect different powerups such as additional health, bubble shields and speed boost Randomly generated battlefield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Piggy Piggy vs Bad Veggies</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-vs-bad-veggies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-vs-bad-veggies/</guid>
      <description>Mango Piggy Piggy is back. This time, you&amp;rsquo;re up against Bad Veggies.
Knock out the Boss Veggie, then bounce on as many Bad Veggies as possible.
Collect powerups to extend your streak, while collecting more mango points. Use collected mango points to purchase cool upgrades.
Features: Interactive tutorial Fun Mango Piggy Piggy theme Collect your Slam points to use the Piggy Slam ability Collect cool powerups such as bombs, stomping machines, and yes, rockets!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Badminton</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/power-badminton/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/power-badminton/</guid>
      <description>Play badminton against clever opponents. Hit short, hit long and smash your way to victory in this badminton league!
Activate power ups to give you an unfair advantage over your opponent. Beware, your opponent has powerups too!
Use your racquet to make cool net shots. Bait them to do a high ball and finish with a smash! Or, play long rallies until your opponent gives up.
Not sure how to play?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chroma Challenge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chroma-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chroma-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Tap to get the ball past the color switching gates.
The gates will only allow the ball with the matching color to pass.
Don&amp;rsquo;t touch the obstacles! You&amp;rsquo;ll explode.
The obstacles are tricky, so time your jumps.
Features: Extremely addictive and challenging gameplay Easy to learn, hard to master. If you can collect more than 3 stars, you&amp;rsquo;re pretty good! Zen theme for focus Fans of color switch type mechanics will appreciate this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Megacity Hop</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/megacity-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/megacity-hop/</guid>
      <description>Cross the roads with busy traffic. Hop your way across this endless mega city!
On desktop, use your arrow keys to move.
On smartphones and tablets, simply swipe to move.
Features: Easy and intuitive controls. Tap to move forward, swipe left or ride to move horizontally Collect coins to unlock various characters in the shop Play characters such as business man, cool DJ , office lady, policeman and sheriff Dynamic generation of terrain to provide endless gameplay If you&amp;rsquo;ve played crossy type games, this is a perfect fit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flick Basketball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flick-basketball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flick-basketball/</guid>
      <description>Flick the ball. Score as many points are you can.
Features: Simple, 1 touch controls Easy to pick up and play. It becomes more challenging as you earn higher scores 3D-like view Collect stars for bonus points </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ski Hero</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ski-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ski-hero/</guid>
      <description>Ski down the mountain, while avoiding the obstacles. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash!
Features: Interactive tutorial. Anyone can play this game! Family friendly theme, suitable for all ages. Beautiful winter christmas landscape. Collect banners to earn extra points. Fans of winter skifree xmas will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rise Higher</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/rise-higher/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/rise-higher/</guid>
      <description>Protect your balloon with your shield.
Move your mouse or finger to block incoming threads from popping your balloon!
Features: Endless gameplay. Easy to learn, hard to master Peaceful and happy theme Very challenging obstacles as you go higher up Save your high score and beat it later </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Baseball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ultimate-baseball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ultimate-baseball/</guid>
      <description>Swing high, middle or low to hit the ball. Find your sweet spot and perfect timing. Hit correctly and score a baseball home run!
A simple arcade style baseball game for the fans.
Features: Simple controls to hit high, medium or low Baseball stadium theme, great for brand exposure The game gets more challenging as you score more home runs! Possibility of integrating a high score leaderboard to compete with other players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flip Jump</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flip-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flip-jump/</guid>
      <description>Tap, hold and release to jump.
Jump from one platform to the next.
How far can you jump?
Features: Extremely cute and positive jumper game theme, great for brands Simple, 1 touch gameplay Unlock more characters by reaching certain milestones Beautiful 3d artwork Fans of Tiao Yi Tiao and Bottle Flip will love this jumper game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways to Die 3 World Tour</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-3-world-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-3-world-tour/</guid>
      <description>Play mini games featuring the characters from Dumb Ways to Die.
Dumb Ways to Die is a worldwide brand with over 300 million downloads on Apple App Store and Google Play combined.
Test your reflexes in this challenging series of mini games, where a milisecond can make the difference between winning and losing.
Score coins for each challenge, and use the to repair the once great town of Dumbville.
Features: Extremely challenging levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scratch and Match Animal</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/scratch-and-match-animal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/scratch-and-match-animal/</guid>
      <description>You have 3 minutes to scratch and match the animal cards. Beat the time and your high score!
Scratch and match beautifully done cards featuring giraffes, elephants, monkeys, tigers, rabbits, cheetahs, polar bears and elephants.
Features: Tutorial Intuitive scratching interface Fun and positive vibe for all ages </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Baseball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/extreme-baseball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/extreme-baseball/</guid>
      <description>Aim and release your baseball to knock out your opponents.
Bounce the ball off the walls to cleverly knock out multiple enemies in one attempt.
Collect baseball cards to increase your score.
Features: Tutorial to learn the ropes Interact with multiple elements such as glass, wood boxes, TNTs, buttons, moving platforms and more. Over 20 challenging levels Baseball card collectors will love this High tempo music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drone Pickup Service</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/drone-pickup-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/drone-pickup-service/</guid>
      <description>The drone revolution has arrived. You operate a Drone pick up service.
Your goal is to navigate the drones into difficult conditions, pick up the packages and return to base.
Fly around trees, hills, cars, airplanes and wind mills to pick up your package.
Complete your tasks in the fastest time to achieve 3 stars.
Features: easy left/right tapping mechanics to navigate extremely challenging levels with various obstacles Play with keyboard , mouse or touch Fun theme and music, suitable for a techy audience who grows up with Uber, Amazon, Instacart and on-demand delivery services </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitchie Clicker</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/twitchie-clicker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/twitchie-clicker/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Twitchie Clicker! If you&amp;rsquo;ve got twitchy fingers, this is the game for you.
Nicknamed H0lyThund3rDude with a cool beanie hat, you have your work cut out for you. Build your streaming empire from nothing. Earn one gamer view at the time, while generating cash.
Upgrade your fame factors to generate more views per second. Unlock cool videos that you can upload to your fans.
Grow your subscriber base to millions of passionate gamers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Running</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/banana-running/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/banana-running/</guid>
      <description>Play as Mr. Nanners, the funniest banana in town with a unique voice.
Unfortunately, Mrs. Nanners is missing, and it&amp;rsquo;s your job to find her in this endless runner.
Run along the city streets in your quest to find Mrs. Nanners. Slide left, right, and under obstacles while collecting Mrs Nanners dolls.
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to collect Banana Balls, and use them to upgrade your gear.
Features: Funny banana theme. Funny banana jokes with voiceover dialogues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tripoly</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tripoly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tripoly/</guid>
      <description>Rotate the triangle, to match the color of the line.
How high can you score?
Features: Fast and upbeat theme Interactive tutorial Easy to start, but it gets challenging very quickly </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Ball Dunkin</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/city-ball-dunkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/city-ball-dunkin/</guid>
      <description>Dunk the basketball into each hoop.
Time your dunks well. Make sure you don&amp;rsquo;t hit the ceiling, or fall to the group.
Collect points to unlock different cool balls from the store.
Beware, the challenges get more difficult over time!
Make your way past tricky hoops that move in weird ways.
How high can you score?
Features: A store to unlock different balls. Really cool ones. Fun theme Day and night transition Increasingly challenging gameplay </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pocket Pac</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pocket-pac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pocket-pac/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t let the monsters catch you! Eat as many dots as you can in this retro arcade game.
Use arrow keys to move around the maze. Make sharp turns to avoid the monsters. Plan your route you never get trapped!
Collect super dots to fight back against the monsters.
How many points can you score?
Features: New and improved maze. Fun arcade theme. Keyboard controls for desktop. Touch controls for mobile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penalty Kick</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/penalty-kick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/penalty-kick/</guid>
      <description>The pitch is set. The stadium is packed full. The fans are chanting. The spotlight is on you.
Swipe the ball towards the goal. Avoid goalies and defenders.
How many goals can you score past the goalkeeper?
Features: fun, arcade style theme fast paced action goalie has varying degrees of intelligence unlock different balls based on high score </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soccer Pong</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soccer-pong/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soccer-pong/</guid>
      <description>How good are you at pong? Drag the paddle, and hit the ball into the opponent&amp;rsquo;s goal post.
Play in a soccer setting with the crowd cheering you all the way. A fun and engaging game for everybody.
Features: 3 different gameplay modes (Easy, Difficult and Expert). Easy mode is the standard classic pong Difficult mode increases the pressure with faster balls and smarter computer Expert mode ( the pong paddle is free to roam everywhere, the ball is fast and the computer is clever!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confident Driver</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/confident-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/confident-driver/</guid>
      <description>How fast are your reflexes? Control your car, pick the right lanes and avoid any crashes to win the level.
Features Drive alongside other vehicles such as mini coopers, new york taxi cabs, trucks, police cars and more Precise and accurate turning, allowing users to cut really sharp corners Beautiful graphics with vehicles closely resembling real vehicles A variety of obstacles such as oil spills, roadblocks, ice and more Challenging levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Triangle Wars</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/triangle-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/triangle-wars/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re a lone spaceship lost in space. Attack other spaceships to survive in the vastness of space. Aim for the highest score.
Features: Interactive tutorial to ease learning curve Endless gameplay Space like physics, for fans of Space Invaders 90s retro games Pick up a variety of powerups such as bombs, splash bullets and extra lives Battle intelligent boss ships Energetic theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Echo Simon</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/echo-simon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/echo-simon/</guid>
      <description>Simon says &amp;hellip; watch the sequence.
Memorize the sequence, then recreate it.
How high can you score?
Features: interactive tutorial endless gameplay easy to learn, difficult to master be prepared for surprises at later levels </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trixology</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/trixology/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/trixology/</guid>
      <description>Rotate the piece to fit the grid below. Fans of modern tetris, you&amp;rsquo;ll love this game.
Cover a full row without gaps, and earn yourself bonus points.
How high is your score?
Features: Clear instructions to learn the ropes Minimalist theme ensures focus for long gameplay and time spent Additional controls such as speed down, accelerate, and rotate clockwise / counterclockwise Increasingly difficult as the level progresses </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stack the Pancake</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stack-the-pancake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stack-the-pancake/</guid>
      <description>Drag and drop the pancake from the pan, onto the plate. It&amp;rsquo;s that simple!
How many pancakes can you pile up? Use your creativity to build stable and towering pan cakes!
Features: Interactive tutorial Fun casual theme, suitable for everyone Addictive stacking gameplay. Make your users compete to get the highest score Intuitive touch based controls </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soda Can Knockdown</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soda-can-knockout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soda-can-knockout/</guid>
      <description>Knock down soda cans with balls. Earn 3 stars for completing each level perfectly.
Features: Challenging levels. Encounter different sets with different soda cans Wide landscape (horizontal) design, with fullscreen mode Beautiful 3D carnival theme. Simple and addictive gameplay. Realistic physics This game is great for fans of various beverage brands such as Coca Cola, Pepsi, Red Bull, Monster and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typing Fighter</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/typing-fighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/typing-fighter/</guid>
      <description>Type fast, type accurate and fight hard in this innovative street fighter style typing game.
Charge up your typing and deliver killer power moves.
Get inspired by motivational phrases and quotes while you type.
Fight against a variety of opponents.
Features: Beautifully designed street fight urban setting Fluid character animations Over 200 motivational quotes and phrases to keep you going </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Volley</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-volley/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-volley/</guid>
      <description>Move your turtle to hit the ball.
Keep the ball from falling into your own court.
First to score 10 wins!
Features: Beautiful and minimalist beach theme Really cute sea turtles Challenging AI </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkour Climb</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-climb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-climb/</guid>
      <description>Tap to jump from wall to wall, parkour style.
How high can you climb up, in this parkur free running game?
Features: Modern futuristic theme Collect shields to stop your fall Collect jetpacks to boost your score Responsive design </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Invasion</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bubble-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bubble-invasion/</guid>
      <description>Defend your base against the invasion of bubbles.
Match 2 or more bubbles of the same color to eliminate them.
Don&amp;rsquo;t let any bubble cross the line!
How high can you score?
Features: Simple, minimalist bubble shooter theme Endless bubble shooter gameplay Responsive design Use a variety of power ups such as freeze, lightning, explosions and rainbow bubbles to gain a competitive edge </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commando Boat</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/commando-boat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/commando-boat/</guid>
      <description>Commando! Drive your speed boat behind enemy lines.
Avoid incoming obstacles such as river mines, tree logs, rocks and other boats.
Shoot and destroy obstacles with bullets.
This is a new and reimagined casual shoot em up game featuring a marine theme.
Features: Collect coins to purchase cool boat models such water raft, speed boat, hovercrafts, and more. Collect powerups including coin magnets, bullets and bubble shields Take ramp to get a cool boost forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knife Master</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/knife-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/knife-master/</guid>
      <description>Throw the knife at the target board.
Score double points for hitting the bullsye.
Sounds easy? As you progress further, you&amp;rsquo;ll need every single ounce of skill and finesse in knife throwing.
Not to mention, you&amp;rsquo;ll need impeccable timing too.
One miss of the knife, and you&amp;rsquo;re out!
Similar to darts, fans of knife throwing and all throwing sports will love this game.
Features: Fast paced knife throwing theme Minimalist look and feel Every challenge is designed exactly the same for each player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bricked</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bricked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bricked/</guid>
      <description>Tap and match bricks of the same color.
Plan your moves carefully, to ensure perfect elimination of the remaining bricks.
How high can you score?
Features: Ability to rewind. You have 3 wishes. Unlimited gameplay. Fun theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkour Run</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-run/</guid>
      <description>Run along rooftops, jump through windows, hang from ledges, and slide under giant water tanks.
Perform various cool parkour inspired tricks using various vectors and angles, but be careful not to fall!
How far can you go in this endless runner platformer game?
Features: Exciting and fast paced music beats Simple minimalist graphics and urban style Addictive and repetitive gameplay, perfect for high score seekers Desktop and mobile friendly controls </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop the Virus</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pop-the-virus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pop-the-virus/</guid>
      <description>With the Coronavirus causing havoc around the world, we all need some time to destress, relax and chill out. Yes, that&amp;rsquo;s 3 different words to induce calm.
Pop as many COVID-19 virus cells before time runs out.
Tap quickly and tap often. Some corona viruses are harder to pop that others. It&amp;rsquo;s because they&amp;rsquo;re sneaky, and they&amp;rsquo;re wearing surgical masks too!
How many covid 19 viruses can you beat? Let&amp;rsquo;s defeat this killer plague together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Lane Racing</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/fast-lane-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/fast-lane-racing/</guid>
      <description>Race against other cars.
Tap to switch lanes. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash into other cars!
Keep on your toes and be prepared to switch lanes quickly in this fastlane game.
Features: Endless gameplay Urban hip hop racing theme Extremely simple controls Simple, linear high score system Fans of racing and driving games will love this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lock Master</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/lock-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/lock-master/</guid>
      <description>Tap to start the lock picking process.
Be patient, concentrate and wait until the key touches the orange dot.
When the moment is right, tap to unlock and score a point in this fast, hypercasual game.
How many locks can you unlock?
Features: Easy to play, hard to master Great spy and thief theme Overcome distractions and obstacles in each level </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climb the Rocks</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/climb-the-rocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/climb-the-rocks/</guid>
      <description>Wait for the right moment to grab the next rock.
Climb one rock at a time. Avoid unstable rocks, while keeping an eye at the prize.
Can you conquer Mount Narya?
Features: Feeling strong like Rocky? Try other more challenging mountains such as Mount Kibar, Alru, Chota, Ordh and Ucca. Endless gameplay Collect diamonds to unlock new mountain climbing characters. Challenging outdoor environment Great theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Escape From Aztec</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/escape-from-aztec/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 12:42:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/escape-from-aztec/</guid>
      <description>You just stole King Aztec&amp;rsquo;s greatest treasure. Now you&amp;rsquo;re being hunted.
Run as fast as you can. Avoid tree trunks, boulders and ancient ruins. Switch lanes, jump and slide your way to freedom.
Collect treasures along the way to purchase powerups.
How far can you escape?
Features: 3D-like environment built with Aztec theme Use Aztec coins to purchase powerups in the store Use a variety of powerups such as invincibility, coin magnets, megaboost and extra lives </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
