<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Just Cute on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/just-cute/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Just Cute on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/just-cute/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Protect the Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/protect-the-kingdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:57 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/protect-the-kingdom/</guid>
      <description>Swing high, middle or low to hit the ball. Find your sweet spot and perfect timing. Hit correctly and score a baseball home run!
A simple arcade style baseball game for the fans.
Features: Simple controls to hit high, medium or low Baseball stadium theme, great for brand exposure The game gets more challenging as you score more home runs! Possibility of integrating a high score leaderboard to compete with other players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Bears</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/love-bears/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:55:50 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/love-bears/</guid>
      <description>Draw lines and shapes to bump the bears. Find a way to bring the two love bears together.
Everything you draw turns into real objects!
Collect 3 stars for every level successfully completed.
Features: Beautiful scenery and theme. Addictive tracing gameplay. Draw anything. Over 30 challenging levels per episode. Extremely cute pastel color theme. Cute bears with hats, glasses, panda caps and more! Suitable for all ages. Fans of Love Balls and Happy Glass will enjoy this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cam and Leon Donut Hop</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cam-and-leon-donut-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:55:10 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cam-and-leon-donut-hop/</guid>
      <description>Brought to you by the creators of a 3D animation, Cam and Leon Donut Hop features 2 funny and cute characters, hopping their way around the park.
Hop in and out of donuts, but don&amp;rsquo;t hit the obstacles!
Features Interactive tutorial Easy to play, hard to master Increasingly challenging obstacles Unlock different characters as you progress. Gain access to Leon, Ladybird, Ice Cube and Pepper Shaker! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Guess What</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:54:22 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</guid>
      <description>Didi and Friends, popular kids animation with over 1 billion views on Youtube is here with a brand new game.
Guess the hidden character, then drag and drop the matching picture to reveal it.
Teach your kids and toddlers to spot patterns, and get rewarded with happy smiles from Didi the Chicken and his friends!
Features: Fun and vibrant theme, guaranteed to excite kids, preschoolers and toddlers. Simple gameplay suitable for kids Fullscreen mode Learn everyday objects, animals, environmental elements and above all, the brand new set of Didi and Friends characters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Hunt</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oil-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:48:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oil-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Stretch out a pipe in order to strike oil.
Hit it big as you guide oil-hungry heroes and monsters in a mystical wasteland! Aim for the highest score, and unlock funny characters!
Explore different lands - from long stretching savannas, to green hills, sandy beaches and dark marshes - you’ll be surprised at all the places you’ll find where you can just stick a pipe and watch as tons of fantastic tasty dark stuff spill out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinosaur Run</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dinosaur-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:46:46 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dinosaur-run/</guid>
      <description>Play a cute and lovable T-Rex running across a desert.
Time your dino jumps to avoid the different obstacles.
How high can you score?
Features: Cool pixel artwork with T Rex dinosaur. Classic grayscale theme set in prehistoric era. Jump over a variety of plants and cactus. Easy to play, hard to master. The background accelerates and decelerates occasionally, to keep you on your toes. Responsive design with fullscreen capability Works great on Chrome and any modern HTML5 browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Piggy Piggy vs Bad Veggies</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-vs-bad-veggies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-vs-bad-veggies/</guid>
      <description>Mango Piggy Piggy is back. This time, you&amp;rsquo;re up against Bad Veggies.
Knock out the Boss Veggie, then bounce on as many Bad Veggies as possible.
Collect powerups to extend your streak, while collecting more mango points. Use collected mango points to purchase cool upgrades.
Features: Interactive tutorial Fun Mango Piggy Piggy theme Collect your Slam points to use the Piggy Slam ability Collect cool powerups such as bombs, stomping machines, and yes, rockets!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Megacity Hop</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/megacity-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/megacity-hop/</guid>
      <description>Cross the roads with busy traffic. Hop your way across this endless mega city!
On desktop, use your arrow keys to move.
On smartphones and tablets, simply swipe to move.
Features: Easy and intuitive controls. Tap to move forward, swipe left or ride to move horizontally Collect coins to unlock various characters in the shop Play characters such as business man, cool DJ , office lady, policeman and sheriff Dynamic generation of terrain to provide endless gameplay If you&amp;rsquo;ve played crossy type games, this is a perfect fit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vampires and Garlic</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/vampires-and-garlic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/vampires-and-garlic/</guid>
      <description>Halloween and vampires are upon us! What do vampires dislike? Garlic!
Throw garlic bombs (yes, made out of garlic) at pesky vampires. Control the angle and strength of your throws.
Remember to watch your garlic count!
Features: A variety of obstacles including challenging terrain, and objects such as boxes, pulleys and TNTs. Simple point and click throwing mechanic Interactive tutorial 30 challenging levels Fun halloween theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flip Jump</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flip-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flip-jump/</guid>
      <description>Tap, hold and release to jump.
Jump from one platform to the next.
How far can you jump?
Features: Extremely cute and positive jumper game theme, great for brands Simple, 1 touch gameplay Unlock more characters by reaching certain milestones Beautiful 3d artwork Fans of Tiao Yi Tiao and Bottle Flip will love this jumper game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Soccer</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-soccer/</guid>
      <description>Aim and shoot the ball into the goal. Collect the starfish to gain maximum score.
With golden sand, coconut trees, sand castles, crabs, and a gorgeous sunshine, what more do you need?
Features: Interactive tutorial Over 20 challenging levels. Put your thinking cap on. Fun beach theme and music Interact with challenging obstacles such as crabs, sandcastles, and more. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Ball Dunkin</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/city-ball-dunkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/city-ball-dunkin/</guid>
      <description>Dunk the basketball into each hoop.
Time your dunks well. Make sure you don&amp;rsquo;t hit the ceiling, or fall to the group.
Collect points to unlock different cool balls from the store.
Beware, the challenges get more difficult over time!
Make your way past tricky hoops that move in weird ways.
How high can you score?
Features: A store to unlock different balls. Really cool ones. Fun theme Day and night transition Increasingly challenging gameplay </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways Jr Zanys Hospital</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-jr-zanys-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-jr-zanys-hospital/</guid>
      <description>From the creators of Dumb Ways to Die, the hit brand with over 300 million downloads total on Google Play and Apple App Store - we present to you an exciting spin-off brand called Dumb Ways JR Zany&amp;rsquo;s Hospital.
Visit Dumb Ways Hospital with Doctor Zany. Explore three main areas of play: a waiting room full of surprises to discover, a check-up room where children can play the role of doctor, and an ambulance that visits the hospital featuring fun guest appearances from the original Dumb Ways cast!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pocket Pac</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pocket-pac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pocket-pac/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t let the monsters catch you! Eat as many dots as you can in this retro arcade game.
Use arrow keys to move around the maze. Make sharp turns to avoid the monsters. Plan your route you never get trapped!
Collect super dots to fight back against the monsters.
How many points can you score?
Features: New and improved maze. Fun arcade theme. Keyboard controls for desktop. Touch controls for mobile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Build Me</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-build-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-build-me/</guid>
      <description>Remember the parts, then drag and drop the parts to form a complete character.
We&amp;rsquo;re proud to present Arty Mouse - Build Me, a branded game built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Interactive tutorial Fun theme for kids of all ages - helps to train cognitive abilities and memory Work with a variety of interesting characters from the Arty Mouse universe, including Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, and Spiro the snail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Sticker Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-sticker-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-sticker-book/</guid>
      <description>Now, your kids can express themselves through art.
Place your favourite Arty Mouse stickers onto the board, decorate them as you wish.
Drag and drop, resize and reposition them to your hearts content. Need to erase a sticker? No problem.
Create millions of sticker combinations using different Arty Mouse characters, objects and backgrounds. Work with Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, Spiro the snail, and more characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Chicken Memory Match</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-memory-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-memory-match/</guid>
      <description>From the hit animation series Chuck Chicken, we bring you this exciting memory match game.
Match your favorite Chuck Chicken cards, and do it in the shortest amount of time!
Discover cool cards featuring Chuck, Flick, Wing as well as nemesis cards including Dr Mingo, Dee, Don, Dex.
Features: Interactive tutorial Beautiful Chuck Chicken artwork Simple, crisp gameplay Fast paced action card theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-and-friends-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-and-friends-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Express your creativity via this coloring book.
We&amp;rsquo;re proud to present Arty Mouse &amp;amp; Friends Coloring Book, a digital coloring book built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Multiple templates to start with Choose different brush sizes and colours Eraser mode Save your works (useful if you&amp;rsquo;d like to print the pictures) Color interesting characters from the Arty Mouse universe, including Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, and Spiro the snail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kuu Kuu Harajuku Diy Kawaii Stickers</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/kuu-kuu-harajuku-diy-kawaii-stickers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/kuu-kuu-harajuku-diy-kawaii-stickers/</guid>
      <description>Tick tock, time to rock! Kuu Kuu Harajuku is an animation brand created by Grammy winner Gwen Stefani. They&amp;rsquo;re back with a game for tween and teen girls!
Create your own sticker book with characters from the hit TV series. Drag and drop stickers that represent G, Love, Angel, Music and Baby into beautiful backgrounds of Harajuku City. Start with the Clubhouse, and move your way to decorate the studio, parks, and the Harajuku City skyline!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Piggy Piggy Hero</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-hero/</guid>
      <description>Mango Piggy Piggy is back with a brand new series and new episodes.
In his hero edition, control different superhero piggies, as you attempt to defend your town against the invasion of enemy robots.
Whats New:
Activate Panther Piggy to dash through obstacles. Activate Hulk Piggy to create a memorable, powerful smash attack. Activate Marvel Piggy to deal widespread damage to enemies. Activate Antman Piggy to suddenly become huge and inflict crazy damage Activate Spider Piggy to pull targets towards it Launch your hero piggy against the enemy, in Angry Birds fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boj Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Showcase your creativity via this coloring book, featuring Boj and friends. A fun, all-digital and reusable coloring book built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Multiple Boj themed templates to start with Choose different brush sizes and colours Did something wrong? Undo your colors via an eraser Save your works and print them. This feature is great for classrooms Color interesting characters from the Boj universe, including Boj the Bilby himself, Mimi, Pops, Denzil, Mr Cloppity, Mia Twitch, Julie Twitch and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Chicken Magic Egg</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-magic-egg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-magic-egg/</guid>
      <description>Chuck Chicken is on a mission. Defeat his nemesis Dee, Don, Dex, Dr Mingo and more in this exciting and fast-paced puzzle platformer game.
Chuck Chicken is a worldwide kids and tweens animation brand with over 2 billion views.
In this game, throw your egg, and watch as it bounces from wall to wall, defeating your opponents.
Collect magic eggs to transform Chuck into his alter ego super hero. For example,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jumping Burger</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jumping-burger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jumping-burger/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re a sliding burger with jumping ability.
Avoid obstacles such as ketchup bottles, birds and tiny mice as you slide forward, while collecting ingredients to unlock the perfect burger.
Ingredients include lettuce, tomato, cheese, burger patties, mushroom and salmon fillets.
Grab Chillis to be come temporarily invincible.
How far can you go?
Features: Cute restaurant diner setting Easy to play, hard to master. This game is very challenging. A shop to unlock your burgers </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Volley</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-volley/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-volley/</guid>
      <description>Move your turtle to hit the ball.
Keep the ball from falling into your own court.
First to score 10 wins!
Features: Beautiful and minimalist beach theme Really cute sea turtles Challenging AI </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flossy and Jim Whale Tickler</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flossy-and-jim-whale-tickler/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flossy-and-jim-whale-tickler/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a cute whale that you can tickle all day long.
Tickle and rub the whale until the bar fills up. Watch as you receive a special response from the whale.
With this game, spread the positivity and feel-good vibe with your audience.
Features: Random emotions and quotes each time Extremely cute design This whale has tusk! It&amp;rsquo;s a Narwhal! Unlimited gameplay and tickles Fun and chill music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wheels on the Bus Sing Along</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/wheels-on-the-bus-sing-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/wheels-on-the-bus-sing-along/</guid>
      <description>The wheels on the bus go round and round in this kids activity game. Ride the bus with fellow animals such as Tiger the driver, Elephant, Rabbit, Monkey and Fox.
Listen to the sweet voice singing the song. Allow your kids to work on discovery activities such as tapping on the animals, activating the bus lights, making the bird sing, honking the bus and more.
Features: real vocals by voice actors cute animal characters touch-based activities for kids to keep busy This game is great for parents teaching kids sing-along songs with activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teddy Bubble Rescue</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/teddy-bubble-rescue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/teddy-bubble-rescue/</guid>
      <description>Big Teddy needs your help! Pop the objects to rescue the mini teddy bears.
Place your shooter aim carefully to clear the maximum amount of objects in each level.
Features: Interactive tutorial 20 challenging levels Fun theme Solve sets using a variety of tactics. Use clever theory of angles, target higher objects and other tactics to solve each level </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
