<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tower Defense on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/tower-defense/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tower Defense on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/tower-defense/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Protect the Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/protect-the-kingdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:57 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/protect-the-kingdom/</guid>
      <description>Swing high, middle or low to hit the ball. Find your sweet spot and perfect timing. Hit correctly and score a baseball home run!
A simple arcade style baseball game for the fans.
Features: Simple controls to hit high, medium or low Baseball stadium theme, great for brand exposure The game gets more challenging as you score more home runs! Possibility of integrating a high score leaderboard to compete with other players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skeleton Defense</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/skeleton-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/skeleton-defense/</guid>
      <description>Soldier! You&amp;rsquo;re the last hope for humanity. It&amp;rsquo;s up to you to stop the waves of undead skeletons.
Features: Interactive tutorial to learn the ropes Scary skeleton theme 7 different weapons. Use rifles, grenades, rockets, molotov cocktails and other impressive weapons to stop these skeletons 5 different skeleton types Unlimited gameplay A shop to upgrade and unlock new weapons </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Invasion</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bubble-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bubble-invasion/</guid>
      <description>Defend your base against the invasion of bubbles.
Match 2 or more bubbles of the same color to eliminate them.
Don&amp;rsquo;t let any bubble cross the line!
How high can you score?
Features: Simple, minimalist bubble shooter theme Endless bubble shooter gameplay Responsive design Use a variety of power ups such as freeze, lightning, explosions and rainbow bubbles to gain a competitive edge </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
