<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Soccer on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/soccer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Soccer on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:56:54 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/soccer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bobblehead Soccer Royale</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bobblehead-soccer-royale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:56:54 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bobblehead-soccer-royale/</guid>
      <description>Move your bobblehead soccer stars around the field. Kick the goals into the opponent&amp;rsquo;s goal.
Collect the powerups to gain an edge over your opponents.
Features: Mad physics that trumps realism Fun and vibrant soccer atmosphere Funny caricature expressions Challenge over 20+ top soccer players in the world Increasingly challenging levels. Get to Level 3 and the game really heats up. Forget FIFA World Cup, fans of puppet soccer fans will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Soccer</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-soccer/</guid>
      <description>Aim and shoot the ball into the goal. Collect the starfish to gain maximum score.
With golden sand, coconut trees, sand castles, crabs, and a gorgeous sunshine, what more do you need?
Features: Interactive tutorial Over 20 challenging levels. Put your thinking cap on. Fun beach theme and music Interact with challenging obstacles such as crabs, sandcastles, and more. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penalty Kick</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/penalty-kick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/penalty-kick/</guid>
      <description>The pitch is set. The stadium is packed full. The fans are chanting. The spotlight is on you.
Swipe the ball towards the goal. Avoid goalies and defenders.
How many goals can you score past the goalkeeper?
Features: fun, arcade style theme fast paced action goalie has varying degrees of intelligence unlock different balls based on high score </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soccer Pong</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soccer-pong/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soccer-pong/</guid>
      <description>How good are you at pong? Drag the paddle, and hit the ball into the opponent&amp;rsquo;s goal post.
Play in a soccer setting with the crowd cheering you all the way. A fun and engaging game for everybody.
Features: 3 different gameplay modes (Easy, Difficult and Expert). Easy mode is the standard classic pong Difficult mode increases the pressure with faster balls and smarter computer Expert mode ( the pong paddle is free to roam everywhere, the ball is fast and the computer is clever!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Soccer</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/smart-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/smart-soccer/</guid>
      <description>Soccer has never been this fun. Simply drag, aim and release to shoot the soccer ball.
The first to score 3 goals wins.
Features: Choose your side, from 32 nations. Smart and calculative AI. Be prepared to play hard! Tutorial to learn the ropes Exciting soccer stadium environment, perfect for soccer nuts </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
