<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Airplane on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/airplane/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Airplane on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/airplane/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alpha Space Invasion</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/alpha-space-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:58 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/alpha-space-invasion/</guid>
      <description>Alpha sector is under invasion. Young pilot, your task is simple. Warp into the sector, and destroy enemy spacecraft before they destroy you.
Avoid the asteroids and keep your shields high. Rake up as many hits as you can!
Features: Interactive tutorial Simple controls (keyboard on desktop, touch controls on mobile) Endless gameplay Fans of sci-fi movies such as Star Wars, Star Trek, Battlestar Galactica and Guardians of the Galaxy will - love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper Planes</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/paper-planes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/paper-planes/</guid>
      <description>This is the game to train your focus and hand eye coordination.
Swipe in direction of the middle plane.
Score as many points within 60 seconds. Track your daily and weekly score.
Features: Unlock combos multipliers with a winning streak Interactive tutorial Relaxed theme suitable for focus </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tripoly</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tripoly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tripoly/</guid>
      <description>Rotate the triangle, to match the color of the line.
How high can you score?
Features: Fast and upbeat theme Interactive tutorial Easy to start, but it gets challenging very quickly </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Triangle Wars</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/triangle-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/triangle-wars/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re a lone spaceship lost in space. Attack other spaceships to survive in the vastness of space. Aim for the highest score.
Features: Interactive tutorial to ease learning curve Endless gameplay Space like physics, for fans of Space Invaders 90s retro games Pick up a variety of powerups such as bombs, splash bullets and extra lives Battle intelligent boss ships Energetic theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
