<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sports on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/sports/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sports on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:56:54 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/sports/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bobblehead Soccer Royale</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bobblehead-soccer-royale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:56:54 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bobblehead-soccer-royale/</guid>
      <description>Move your bobblehead soccer stars around the field. Kick the goals into the opponent&amp;rsquo;s goal.
Collect the powerups to gain an edge over your opponents.
Features: Mad physics that trumps realism Fun and vibrant soccer atmosphere Funny caricature expressions Challenge over 20+ top soccer players in the world Increasingly challenging levels. Get to Level 3 and the game really heats up. Forget FIFA World Cup, fans of puppet soccer fans will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pro Bowling 3D</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pro-bowling-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pro-bowling-3d/</guid>
      <description>Position the bowling ball. Then, flick or trace a curve to roll the ball.
How many strikes can you accumulate? Are you the bowling king?
Features: Beautiful bowling arcade. Intuitive tap-and-swipe control. Gorgeous balls. Bowl like a pro. Light background noise for ambience effect. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Badminton</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/power-badminton/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/power-badminton/</guid>
      <description>Play badminton against clever opponents. Hit short, hit long and smash your way to victory in this badminton league!
Activate power ups to give you an unfair advantage over your opponent. Beware, your opponent has powerups too!
Use your racquet to make cool net shots. Bait them to do a high ball and finish with a smash! Or, play long rallies until your opponent gives up.
Not sure how to play?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pro Wrestling Action</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pro-wrestling-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pro-wrestling-action/</guid>
      <description>Get ready to rumble! Punch, kick, and wrestle your way through to be the last man standing.
Knock out your opponents, then throw them out of the ring!
Need to perform a spectacular feat? Climb the ropes, time your jumps and dive on the opponent.
Collect coins to upgrade your favourite wrestler in the shop.
Features: Simple controls to maximize fun. Start kicking and punching right away! Entertaining wrestling theme Clever and not so clever computer opponents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rugby Extreme</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/rugby-extreme-flick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/rugby-extreme-flick/</guid>
      <description>Flick the ball into the goal post. How many goals can you score?
Features: Easy to play, difficult to master Get extra points for scoring in designated target areas Beware of the changing wind speeds at higher levels Flying capemen will try to block your shots Unlock different objects such as beer bottles, watermelon, easter eggs and rockets Fans of flick kick rugby, american football and rugby world cup will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flick Basketball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flick-basketball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flick-basketball/</guid>
      <description>Flick the ball. Score as many points are you can.
Features: Simple, 1 touch controls Easy to pick up and play. It becomes more challenging as you earn higher scores 3D-like view Collect stars for bonus points </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini Golf Adventure</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mini-golf-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mini-golf-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Put the ball into the hole. Use the shortest amount of putts to score maximum stars.
Collect gems to increase your score! Embark on this fun golfing adventure, as your discover new objects and power-ups to help you win.
Features: Discover new elements in this golf paradise, such as the magnet, teleportation stations, windmills, wind accelerators, and yes, a mole! Who&amp;rsquo;s the mole? Interactive tutorial to start putting away Over 24 levels and more to come Fun family oriented theme, suitable for all ages </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ski Hero</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ski-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ski-hero/</guid>
      <description>Ski down the mountain, while avoiding the obstacles. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash!
Features: Interactive tutorial. Anyone can play this game! Family friendly theme, suitable for all ages. Beautiful winter christmas landscape. Collect banners to earn extra points. Fans of winter skifree xmas will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Baseball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ultimate-baseball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ultimate-baseball/</guid>
      <description>Swing high, middle or low to hit the ball. Find your sweet spot and perfect timing. Hit correctly and score a baseball home run!
A simple arcade style baseball game for the fans.
Features: Simple controls to hit high, medium or low Baseball stadium theme, great for brand exposure The game gets more challenging as you score more home runs! Possibility of integrating a high score leaderboard to compete with other players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways to Die 3 World Tour</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-3-world-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-3-world-tour/</guid>
      <description>Play mini games featuring the characters from Dumb Ways to Die.
Dumb Ways to Die is a worldwide brand with over 300 million downloads on Apple App Store and Google Play combined.
Test your reflexes in this challenging series of mini games, where a milisecond can make the difference between winning and losing.
Score coins for each challenge, and use the to repair the once great town of Dumbville.
Features: Extremely challenging levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Baseball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/extreme-baseball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/extreme-baseball/</guid>
      <description>Aim and release your baseball to knock out your opponents.
Bounce the ball off the walls to cleverly knock out multiple enemies in one attempt.
Collect baseball cards to increase your score.
Features: Tutorial to learn the ropes Interact with multiple elements such as glass, wood boxes, TNTs, buttons, moving platforms and more. Over 20 challenging levels Baseball card collectors will love this High tempo music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penalty Kick</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/penalty-kick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/penalty-kick/</guid>
      <description>The pitch is set. The stadium is packed full. The fans are chanting. The spotlight is on you.
Swipe the ball towards the goal. Avoid goalies and defenders.
How many goals can you score past the goalkeeper?
Features: fun, arcade style theme fast paced action goalie has varying degrees of intelligence unlock different balls based on high score </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stick Golf</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stick-golf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stick-golf/</guid>
      <description>Aim, adjust the club power and go! Playing golf has never been this easy.
From easy to challenging terrains, use your acute golf senses to land a hole in one.
Avoid bunkers and water hazards!
Features: interactive tutorial to help your audience relaxed theme and background. Playing golf has never been this relaxing. earn coins from successful holes use coins at the shop, to purchase fun skins such as top hat, pirate hat, bunny hats and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soccer Pong</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soccer-pong/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soccer-pong/</guid>
      <description>How good are you at pong? Drag the paddle, and hit the ball into the opponent&amp;rsquo;s goal post.
Play in a soccer setting with the crowd cheering you all the way. A fun and engaging game for everybody.
Features: 3 different gameplay modes (Easy, Difficult and Expert). Easy mode is the standard classic pong Difficult mode increases the pressure with faster balls and smarter computer Expert mode ( the pong paddle is free to roam everywhere, the ball is fast and the computer is clever!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowboard Hero</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/snowboard-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/snowboard-hero/</guid>
      <description>Snowboard your way down the mountain, while avoiding the obstacles. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash!
Features: Interactive tutorial. Anyone can play this game! Fast, pumping music suitable for X sports. Beautiful winter christmas landscape. Collect banners to earn extra points. Fans of winter skifree xmas or snowboarding will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soda Can Knockdown</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soda-can-knockout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soda-can-knockout/</guid>
      <description>Knock down soda cans with balls. Earn 3 stars for completing each level perfectly.
Features: Challenging levels. Encounter different sets with different soda cans Wide landscape (horizontal) design, with fullscreen mode Beautiful 3D carnival theme. Simple and addictive gameplay. Realistic physics This game is great for fans of various beverage brands such as Coca Cola, Pepsi, Red Bull, Monster and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Volley</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-volley/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-volley/</guid>
      <description>Move your turtle to hit the ball.
Keep the ball from falling into your own court.
First to score 10 wins!
Features: Beautiful and minimalist beach theme Really cute sea turtles Challenging AI </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkour Climb</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-climb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-climb/</guid>
      <description>Tap to jump from wall to wall, parkour style.
How high can you climb up, in this parkur free running game?
Features: Modern futuristic theme Collect shields to stop your fall Collect jetpacks to boost your score Responsive design </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knife Master</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/knife-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/knife-master/</guid>
      <description>Throw the knife at the target board.
Score double points for hitting the bullsye.
Sounds easy? As you progress further, you&amp;rsquo;ll need every single ounce of skill and finesse in knife throwing.
Not to mention, you&amp;rsquo;ll need impeccable timing too.
One miss of the knife, and you&amp;rsquo;re out!
Similar to darts, fans of knife throwing and all throwing sports will love this game.
Features: Fast paced knife throwing theme Minimalist look and feel Every challenge is designed exactly the same for each player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climb the Rocks</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/climb-the-rocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/climb-the-rocks/</guid>
      <description>Wait for the right moment to grab the next rock.
Climb one rock at a time. Avoid unstable rocks, while keeping an eye at the prize.
Can you conquer Mount Narya?
Features: Feeling strong like Rocky? Try other more challenging mountains such as Mount Kibar, Alru, Chota, Ordh and Ucca. Endless gameplay Collect diamonds to unlock new mountain climbing characters. Challenging outdoor environment Great theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Soccer</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/smart-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/smart-soccer/</guid>
      <description>Soccer has never been this fun. Simply drag, aim and release to shoot the soccer ball.
The first to score 3 goals wins.
Features: Choose your side, from 32 nations. Smart and calculative AI. Be prepared to play hard! Tutorial to learn the ropes Exciting soccer stadium environment, perfect for soccer nuts </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
