<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Physics on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/physics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Physics on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:56:54 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/physics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bobblehead Soccer Royale</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bobblehead-soccer-royale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:56:54 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bobblehead-soccer-royale/</guid>
      <description>Move your bobblehead soccer stars around the field. Kick the goals into the opponent&amp;rsquo;s goal.
Collect the powerups to gain an edge over your opponents.
Features: Mad physics that trumps realism Fun and vibrant soccer atmosphere Funny caricature expressions Challenge over 20+ top soccer players in the world Increasingly challenging levels. Get to Level 3 and the game really heats up. Forget FIFA World Cup, fans of puppet soccer fans will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Bears</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/love-bears/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:55:50 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/love-bears/</guid>
      <description>Draw lines and shapes to bump the bears. Find a way to bring the two love bears together.
Everything you draw turns into real objects!
Collect 3 stars for every level successfully completed.
Features: Beautiful scenery and theme. Addictive tracing gameplay. Draw anything. Over 30 challenging levels per episode. Extremely cute pastel color theme. Cute bears with hats, glasses, panda caps and more! Suitable for all ages. Fans of Love Balls and Happy Glass will enjoy this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bomb the Bridge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bomb-the-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:51:50 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bomb-the-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Plant C4 bombs anywhere on the bridge.
Wait for enemy troops to cross, then detonate them.
Blow up 100% of the bridge and eliminate all troops to score 3 stars.
Features: Realistic physics Addictive theme Challenging levels Blow up armies, military trucks and tanks! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Hunt</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oil-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:48:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oil-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Stretch out a pipe in order to strike oil.
Hit it big as you guide oil-hungry heroes and monsters in a mystical wasteland! Aim for the highest score, and unlock funny characters!
Explore different lands - from long stretching savannas, to green hills, sandy beaches and dark marshes - you’ll be surprised at all the places you’ll find where you can just stick a pipe and watch as tons of fantastic tasty dark stuff spill out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stupid Zombies</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stupid-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:44:27 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stupid-zombies/</guid>
      <description>One man, one shotgun and a whole lot of zombies. You are humanity&amp;rsquo;s last hope, and it&amp;rsquo;s your job to keep them brainless.
Adjust your shots and angles, and you watch your bullets ricochet from wall to wall, elegantly picking off each zombie&amp;rsquo;s arms and limbs.
Features: 4 giant stages with over 360 challenging levels Exciting zombie theme Simple and innovative ricochet based gameplay. Defeat the stupid zombies with brains and ingenuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Bottle Shooter</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/3d-bottle-shoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/3d-bottle-shoot/</guid>
      <description>Aim and shoot glass bottles. It&amp;rsquo;s so simple, yet so addictive.
Listen to the harmonic sounds of glass shattering amidst the peaceful countryside.
Aim for 3 stars in each level.
Features: Over 30 challenging levels Serene and peaceful countryside vibe Simple controls for the casual user Beautiful, low-poly gun, countryside, trees and mountains. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Construct a Bridge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/construct-a-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/construct-a-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Hello Engineer! Build a bridge that does not collapse.
Connect joints with lines, to create your engineering marvel.
Then, test your bridge with real trucks passing over.
Will your bridge stand the test?
Your construction is limited by the amount of funds you have, so build your bridge wisely!
Features: Fun theme suitable for everyone Grid system enabled for easier construction Ability to edit your bridge anytime via Undo command Ability to delete portions of your bridge via the Delete command </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Badminton</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/power-badminton/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/power-badminton/</guid>
      <description>Play badminton against clever opponents. Hit short, hit long and smash your way to victory in this badminton league!
Activate power ups to give you an unfair advantage over your opponent. Beware, your opponent has powerups too!
Use your racquet to make cool net shots. Bait them to do a high ball and finish with a smash! Or, play long rallies until your opponent gives up.
Not sure how to play?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vampires and Garlic</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/vampires-and-garlic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/vampires-and-garlic/</guid>
      <description>Halloween and vampires are upon us! What do vampires dislike? Garlic!
Throw garlic bombs (yes, made out of garlic) at pesky vampires. Control the angle and strength of your throws.
Remember to watch your garlic count!
Features: A variety of obstacles including challenging terrain, and objects such as boxes, pulleys and TNTs. Simple point and click throwing mechanic Interactive tutorial 30 challenging levels Fun halloween theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini Golf Adventure</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mini-golf-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mini-golf-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Put the ball into the hole. Use the shortest amount of putts to score maximum stars.
Collect gems to increase your score! Embark on this fun golfing adventure, as your discover new objects and power-ups to help you win.
Features: Discover new elements in this golf paradise, such as the magnet, teleportation stations, windmills, wind accelerators, and yes, a mole! Who&amp;rsquo;s the mole? Interactive tutorial to start putting away Over 24 levels and more to come Fun family oriented theme, suitable for all ages </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ski Hero</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ski-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ski-hero/</guid>
      <description>Ski down the mountain, while avoiding the obstacles. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash!
Features: Interactive tutorial. Anyone can play this game! Family friendly theme, suitable for all ages. Beautiful winter christmas landscape. Collect banners to earn extra points. Fans of winter skifree xmas will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Hour</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/happy-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/happy-hour/</guid>
      <description>Fill up the martini glass. It&amp;rsquo;s Happy Hour!
Control the flow of drinks to fill up your glass! Everything you draw turns into real objects.
Come up with your own solution to each level.
Features: Funny Happy Hour quotes. Work on multiple drinks including cocktails, wine, spirits, beer and other alcohol related items. Beautiful bar scene and nightlife theme Chill vibe Addictive tracing gameplay. Draw anything. Over 30 challenging levels per city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spidey Swing</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/spidey-swing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/spidey-swing/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the adventures of Spidey. Shoot webs, grab on and swing like a spider pro. Avoid things such as sharp edges, rotating chainsaws, arrows, mace and other deadly objects.
Keep the majority of your body parts intact, and get to the finish line. Keep our beloved Spidey alive!
Features Interactive tutorial Touch, keyboard and mouse controls City skyscraper theme Update: Over 48 extremely challenging levels. Test your spider-man skills. Presence of blood and gore (can be turned off by request) Fans of spiderman and marvel superheroes will love the game </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways to Die 3 World Tour</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-3-world-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-3-world-tour/</guid>
      <description>Play mini games featuring the characters from Dumb Ways to Die.
Dumb Ways to Die is a worldwide brand with over 300 million downloads on Apple App Store and Google Play combined.
Test your reflexes in this challenging series of mini games, where a milisecond can make the difference between winning and losing.
Score coins for each challenge, and use the to repair the once great town of Dumbville.
Features: Extremely challenging levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Truck Driving</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/monster-truck-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/monster-truck-driving/</guid>
      <description>Control your monster truck to reach the flag.
Boost, brake and tilt your truck left/right to navigate the path.
Earn stars by completing the level in record time.
Features: Interactive tutorial Use stars to unlock cool characters such as a cool flaming truck, Batman truck, Shark truck, Hyena truck and more. Panning function to plan your routes 20 challenging levels Play repeatedly to get the best high score Upbeat theme Monster Truck and Dirt Bike enthusiasts will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Baseball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/extreme-baseball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/extreme-baseball/</guid>
      <description>Aim and release your baseball to knock out your opponents.
Bounce the ball off the walls to cleverly knock out multiple enemies in one attempt.
Collect baseball cards to increase your score.
Features: Tutorial to learn the ropes Interact with multiple elements such as glass, wood boxes, TNTs, buttons, moving platforms and more. Over 20 challenging levels Baseball card collectors will love this High tempo music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valet Parking</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/valet-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/valet-parking/</guid>
      <description>A must have car parking simulator game. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to learn, and yet incredibly difficult to master.
Park your car in the perfect spot, with surgical precision. Be careful not to bump into other cars and objects.
Put on your safety belt, and let the game begin! Fans of parking frenzy games will love this.
Features: Interactive tutorial Beautiful parking spots 3 Star based system to reward precision Over 50+ parking challenges Keyboard controls for desktop, and touch controls for smartphones and tablets Drive a variety of cool cars </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Soccer</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-soccer/</guid>
      <description>Aim and shoot the ball into the goal. Collect the starfish to gain maximum score.
With golden sand, coconut trees, sand castles, crabs, and a gorgeous sunshine, what more do you need?
Features: Interactive tutorial Over 20 challenging levels. Put your thinking cap on. Fun beach theme and music Interact with challenging obstacles such as crabs, sandcastles, and more. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drone Pickup Service</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/drone-pickup-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/drone-pickup-service/</guid>
      <description>The drone revolution has arrived. You operate a Drone pick up service.
Your goal is to navigate the drones into difficult conditions, pick up the packages and return to base.
Fly around trees, hills, cars, airplanes and wind mills to pick up your package.
Complete your tasks in the fastest time to achieve 3 stars.
Features: easy left/right tapping mechanics to navigate extremely challenging levels with various obstacles Play with keyboard , mouse or touch Fun theme and music, suitable for a techy audience who grows up with Uber, Amazon, Instacart and on-demand delivery services </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Piggy Piggy Farm</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-farm/</guid>
      <description>Mango Piggy Piggy is HUNGRY. He comes across a mango farm. The mangoes look sweet and juicy, just like how he likes it.
Drag and aim to launch Mango Piggy Piggy towards the mangos. Eat them all to earn 3 stars!
Features: Fun, positive and ridiculously cute character. MPP bounces around and squeals almost like a soft toy. Innovative touch and drag mechanic Over 30 levels Unlock a hidden level Don&amp;rsquo;t eat the red mango!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Ball Dunkin</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/city-ball-dunkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/city-ball-dunkin/</guid>
      <description>Dunk the basketball into each hoop.
Time your dunks well. Make sure you don&amp;rsquo;t hit the ceiling, or fall to the group.
Collect points to unlock different cool balls from the store.
Beware, the challenges get more difficult over time!
Make your way past tricky hoops that move in weird ways.
How high can you score?
Features: A store to unlock different balls. Really cool ones. Fun theme Day and night transition Increasingly challenging gameplay </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways Jr Zanys Hospital</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-jr-zanys-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-jr-zanys-hospital/</guid>
      <description>From the creators of Dumb Ways to Die, the hit brand with over 300 million downloads total on Google Play and Apple App Store - we present to you an exciting spin-off brand called Dumb Ways JR Zany&amp;rsquo;s Hospital.
Visit Dumb Ways Hospital with Doctor Zany. Explore three main areas of play: a waiting room full of surprises to discover, a check-up room where children can play the role of doctor, and an ambulance that visits the hospital featuring fun guest appearances from the original Dumb Ways cast!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Horace vs Cheese</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/horace-vs-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/horace-vs-cheese/</guid>
      <description>Pull and launch Horace the Hamster into the cheese. Eat them all to earn 3 stars.
Then, land safely into the cheese house.
From the creators of Flossy and Jim, we bring you a new brand called Horace and co.
Features: Fun, positive and ridiculously cute character. Horace bounces around and squeals almost like a soft toy. Innovative touch and drag mechanic Over 30 levels Unlock a hidden level Don&amp;rsquo;t eat the blue cheese!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Piggy Piggy Hero</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-hero/</guid>
      <description>Mango Piggy Piggy is back with a brand new series and new episodes.
In his hero edition, control different superhero piggies, as you attempt to defend your town against the invasion of enemy robots.
Whats New:
Activate Panther Piggy to dash through obstacles. Activate Hulk Piggy to create a memorable, powerful smash attack. Activate Marvel Piggy to deal widespread damage to enemies. Activate Antman Piggy to suddenly become huge and inflict crazy damage Activate Spider Piggy to pull targets towards it Launch your hero piggy against the enemy, in Angry Birds fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Chicken Magic Egg</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-magic-egg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-magic-egg/</guid>
      <description>Chuck Chicken is on a mission. Defeat his nemesis Dee, Don, Dex, Dr Mingo and more in this exciting and fast-paced puzzle platformer game.
Chuck Chicken is a worldwide kids and tweens animation brand with over 2 billion views.
In this game, throw your egg, and watch as it bounces from wall to wall, defeating your opponents.
Collect magic eggs to transform Chuck into his alter ego super hero. For example,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oddbods Soccer Challenge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-soccer-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-soccer-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Fancy a soccer game with your favourite Oddbods? Kick the ball into the goal, but beware! The mischievous Oddbods are here to stop you.
Features: Compete against Oddbods such as Fuse, Bubbles, Pogo, Zee, Slick, Jeff and Newt. Fun Oddbods theme song Each Oddbod brings something interesting to the game Over 60 levels more more to be added soon Interactive tutorial Fans of soccer or football will love this game. If you&amp;rsquo;re into the World Cup, English Premier League or UEFA Champions League, this game will be interesting too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stick Golf</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stick-golf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stick-golf/</guid>
      <description>Aim, adjust the club power and go! Playing golf has never been this easy.
From easy to challenging terrains, use your acute golf senses to land a hole in one.
Avoid bunkers and water hazards!
Features: interactive tutorial to help your audience relaxed theme and background. Playing golf has never been this relaxing. earn coins from successful holes use coins at the shop, to purchase fun skins such as top hat, pirate hat, bunny hats and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biker Lane</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/biker-lane/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/biker-lane/</guid>
      <description>Control your bike rider to reach the flag.
Boost, brake and tilt your bike left/right to navigate the tricky roads.
Earn stars by completing the level in record time.
Features: Interactive tutorial Use stars to unlock cool characters such as grandma biker, traffic police biker, punk biker, and pro biker. Panning function to plan your routes 20 challenging levels Play repeatedly to get the best high score Upbeat theme Motorcycle and moto x3m enthusiasts will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Castle Siege</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/castle-siege/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/castle-siege/</guid>
      <description>Use your cannon ball to destroy the foundations of the castle structure.
When the castle structure falls, the guards will be eliminated. Remember to avoid hurting the hostages!
Features: Innovative splitting mechanic. Aim your cannonball to split structures into multiple pieces Collect treasures to increase your score Place your shots correctly to earn more crowns Comedic sound effects Fun relaxed puzzle game </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jumping Burger</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jumping-burger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jumping-burger/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re a sliding burger with jumping ability.
Avoid obstacles such as ketchup bottles, birds and tiny mice as you slide forward, while collecting ingredients to unlock the perfect burger.
Ingredients include lettuce, tomato, cheese, burger patties, mushroom and salmon fillets.
Grab Chillis to be come temporarily invincible.
How far can you go?
Features: Cute restaurant diner setting Easy to play, hard to master. This game is very challenging. A shop to unlock your burgers </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sky Castle</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sky-castle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sky-castle/</guid>
      <description>My liege, stack the castle parts above each other. Stack them high and strong. Be the ruler of the tallest castle in the world.
Features: Endless gameplay. Spend hours trying to perfect your placement. The castle becomes more challenging to build as they get higher Simple controls: tap to place castle blocks Use a variety of helpers such as Reverse, Repeat, Insurance, and Double Coins Beautiful graphics and ancient medieval theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowboard Hero</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/snowboard-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/snowboard-hero/</guid>
      <description>Snowboard your way down the mountain, while avoiding the obstacles. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash!
Features: Interactive tutorial. Anyone can play this game! Fast, pumping music suitable for X sports. Beautiful winter christmas landscape. Collect banners to earn extra points. Fans of winter skifree xmas or snowboarding will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oddbods Monster Truck Driving</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-monster-truck-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-monster-truck-driving/</guid>
      <description>Control your Oddbods monster truck to reach the flag.
Boost, brake and tilt your truck left/right to navigate the path.
Earn stars by completing the level in record time.
Features: Drive with all 7 Oddbods, including Fuse, Bubbles, Pogo, Zee, Slick, Jeff and Newt. Interactive tutorial Each Oddbod brings something special Use stars to unlock cool vehicles Panning function to plan your routes 20 challenging levels Play repeatedly to get the best high score Upbeat theme Monster Truck and Dirt Bike enthusiasts will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stack the Pancake</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stack-the-pancake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stack-the-pancake/</guid>
      <description>Drag and drop the pancake from the pan, onto the plate. It&amp;rsquo;s that simple!
How many pancakes can you pile up? Use your creativity to build stable and towering pan cakes!
Features: Interactive tutorial Fun casual theme, suitable for everyone Addictive stacking gameplay. Make your users compete to get the highest score Intuitive touch based controls </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soda Can Knockdown</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soda-can-knockout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soda-can-knockout/</guid>
      <description>Knock down soda cans with balls. Earn 3 stars for completing each level perfectly.
Features: Challenging levels. Encounter different sets with different soda cans Wide landscape (horizontal) design, with fullscreen mode Beautiful 3D carnival theme. Simple and addictive gameplay. Realistic physics This game is great for fans of various beverage brands such as Coca Cola, Pepsi, Red Bull, Monster and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Invasion</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bubble-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bubble-invasion/</guid>
      <description>Defend your base against the invasion of bubbles.
Match 2 or more bubbles of the same color to eliminate them.
Don&amp;rsquo;t let any bubble cross the line!
How high can you score?
Features: Simple, minimalist bubble shooter theme Endless bubble shooter gameplay Responsive design Use a variety of power ups such as freeze, lightning, explosions and rainbow bubbles to gain a competitive edge </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bricked</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bricked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bricked/</guid>
      <description>Tap and match bricks of the same color.
Plan your moves carefully, to ensure perfect elimination of the remaining bricks.
How high can you score?
Features: Ability to rewind. You have 3 wishes. Unlimited gameplay. Fun theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkour Run</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-run/</guid>
      <description>Run along rooftops, jump through windows, hang from ledges, and slide under giant water tanks.
Perform various cool parkour inspired tricks using various vectors and angles, but be careful not to fall!
How far can you go in this endless runner platformer game?
Features: Exciting and fast paced music beats Simple minimalist graphics and urban style Addictive and repetitive gameplay, perfect for high score seekers Desktop and mobile friendly controls </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climb the Rocks</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/climb-the-rocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/climb-the-rocks/</guid>
      <description>Wait for the right moment to grab the next rock.
Climb one rock at a time. Avoid unstable rocks, while keeping an eye at the prize.
Can you conquer Mount Narya?
Features: Feeling strong like Rocky? Try other more challenging mountains such as Mount Kibar, Alru, Chota, Ordh and Ucca. Endless gameplay Collect diamonds to unlock new mountain climbing characters. Challenging outdoor environment Great theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
