<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Educational on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/educational/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Educational on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:54:22 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/educational/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Guess What</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:54:22 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</guid>
      <description>Didi and Friends, popular kids animation with over 1 billion views on Youtube is here with a brand new game.
Guess the hidden character, then drag and drop the matching picture to reveal it.
Teach your kids and toddlers to spot patterns, and get rewarded with happy smiles from Didi the Chicken and his friends!
Features: Fun and vibrant theme, guaranteed to excite kids, preschoolers and toddlers. Simple gameplay suitable for kids Fullscreen mode Learn everyday objects, animals, environmental elements and above all, the brand new set of Didi and Friends characters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crossword Casual</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/crossword-casual/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/crossword-casual/</guid>
      <description>Solve everyday crossword puzzles involving various themes such as cities, objects, food, and buildings.
Features: Full screen mode Easy to use crossword puzzle. Regardless of device, play the same crossword puzzle as everybody else Easy selection of puzzle grid to insert answers Virtual keyboard for mobile and tablet users. Easily enter your answers to solve the puzzles Random puzzles generated from a pool of questions and answers Relaxing theme, suitable for everyone Note: if you&amp;rsquo;d like different themes, please contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trivia Quiz</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/trivia-quiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/trivia-quiz/</guid>
      <description>Test your general knowledge in this trivia quiz game.
How many questions can you answer correctly?
Features: Simple, clean and welcoming theme Easy to configure Trivia Quiz. Let us know what you need, and we&amp;rsquo;ll customize it for you. Question separated into different difficulty levels (easy questions first, followed by more challenging questions) 30 randomly rotated questions per round Over 100 different questions in the pool Fullscreen mode </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cash Back</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cash-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cash-back/</guid>
      <description>Calculate and return the correct change to customers. Return a combination of dollar notes and coins to customers who purchase items from your store.
Score correctly and generate sales for your store!
Features: Interactive tutorial Hints system 3 difficulty modes Happy theme suitable for young kids </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Faces</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/funny-faces/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/funny-faces/</guid>
      <description>Quick, you have 5 seconds to remember the face.
Then, drag and drop face parts into the correct positions.
How fast can you reconstruct each face?
Features: Fun and uplifting theme Increasingly complex faces to reconstruct. It gets challenging! Interactive tutorial Attention to detail. Players get to work on hair, eyes, eyebrows, nose, mouth, glasses, moustache and more. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways Jr Zanys Hospital</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-jr-zanys-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-jr-zanys-hospital/</guid>
      <description>From the creators of Dumb Ways to Die, the hit brand with over 300 million downloads total on Google Play and Apple App Store - we present to you an exciting spin-off brand called Dumb Ways JR Zany&amp;rsquo;s Hospital.
Visit Dumb Ways Hospital with Doctor Zany. Explore three main areas of play: a waiting room full of surprises to discover, a check-up room where children can play the role of doctor, and an ambulance that visits the hospital featuring fun guest appearances from the original Dumb Ways cast!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Build Me</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-build-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-build-me/</guid>
      <description>Remember the parts, then drag and drop the parts to form a complete character.
We&amp;rsquo;re proud to present Arty Mouse - Build Me, a branded game built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Interactive tutorial Fun theme for kids of all ages - helps to train cognitive abilities and memory Work with a variety of interesting characters from the Arty Mouse universe, including Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, and Spiro the snail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Sticker Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-sticker-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-sticker-book/</guid>
      <description>Now, your kids can express themselves through art.
Place your favourite Arty Mouse stickers onto the board, decorate them as you wish.
Drag and drop, resize and reposition them to your hearts content. Need to erase a sticker? No problem.
Create millions of sticker combinations using different Arty Mouse characters, objects and backgrounds. Work with Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, Spiro the snail, and more characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-and-friends-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-and-friends-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Express your creativity via this coloring book.
We&amp;rsquo;re proud to present Arty Mouse &amp;amp; Friends Coloring Book, a digital coloring book built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Multiple templates to start with Choose different brush sizes and colours Eraser mode Save your works (useful if you&amp;rsquo;d like to print the pictures) Color interesting characters from the Arty Mouse universe, including Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, and Spiro the snail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Connect the Dots</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-connect-the-dots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-connect-the-dots/</guid>
      <description>Didi and Friends, popular kids animation with over 1 billion views on Youtube is here with a brand new game.
Connect the dots to reveal interesting objects, animals and characters.
Teach your kids and toddlers to connect the dots, and get rewarded with happy smiles from Didi the Chicken and his friends!
Features: Fun and vibrant theme, guaranteed to excite kids, preschoolers and toddlers. Simple gameplay suitable for kids Fullscreen mode Learn everyday objects, animals, environmental elements and above all, the brand new set of Didi and Friends characters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boj Giggly Park Adventure</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-giggly-park-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-giggly-park-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Explore Giggly Park with Boj and friends.
Boj is an award winning kids television series worldwide.
Do wonderful things such as ride a bike, climb the tree, fly a kite, dig underground for treasures, ride the swing, control a helicopter remotely and more.
Interact with various characters from the Boj universe, such as Mimi, Pops, Mr Cloppity, Denzil, Mia Twitch and more.
This is a new and innovative gameplay to encourage users to explore their curiosity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typing Fighter</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/typing-fighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/typing-fighter/</guid>
      <description>Type fast, type accurate and fight hard in this innovative street fighter style typing game.
Charge up your typing and deliver killer power moves.
Get inspired by motivational phrases and quotes while you type.
Fight against a variety of opponents.
Features: Beautifully designed street fight urban setting Fluid character animations Over 200 motivational quotes and phrases to keep you going </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sort the Trash</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sort-the-trash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sort-the-trash/</guid>
      <description>Protect the environment by learning how to recycle correctly.
Collect items that can be recycled only. Avoid collecting contaminators such as organic waste, disposable coffee cups, plastic straws, ceramic dishware and lithium ion batteries.
Go green and save the Earth. Start becoming eco-friendly today!
Features: Simple elegant design Responsive design Positive them with recycling facts </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Learn Abc</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-learn-abc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-learn-abc/</guid>
      <description>Arty Mouse is back with a new game! Teach your toddlers to trace alphabets from A to Z.
Help them recognize letter shapes and associate them with phonic sounds.
Suitable for toddlers, preschool and kindergarten kids.
Work with fun characters from the Arty Mouse universe, including Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, Spiro the snail, and more characters.
Features: Interactive tutorial Upper and lower case alphabet tracing Fun, welcoming and inclusive game for kids </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Crossword</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/holiday-crossword/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/holiday-crossword/</guid>
      <description>Solve holiday themed crossword puzzles involving various topics such as cities, food, celebrations and gift ideas.
Features: Full screen mode Easy to use cross word puzzle. Regardless of device, play the same crossword puzzle as everybody else Easy selection of puzzle grid to insert answers Virtual keyboard for mobile and tablet users. Easily enter your answers to solve the puzzles Random puzzles generated from a pool of questions and answers Relaxing theme, suitable for everyone Note: if you&amp;rsquo;d like different themes and questions, please contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Numbers Challenge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/numbers-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/numbers-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Which side is greater? Left, right or are they equal?
Numbers Challenge is a new and exciting cognitive math based game.
Answer 5 questions in a row correctly, to move up the level.
Miss one, and the game is over at the end of the level.
Features: Easy to start. The math gets complicated the further you go Peaceful theme, suitable for concentration Tough and tricky questions Accuracy stats for math geeks </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop the Virus</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pop-the-virus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pop-the-virus/</guid>
      <description>With the Coronavirus causing havoc around the world, we all need some time to destress, relax and chill out. Yes, that&amp;rsquo;s 3 different words to induce calm.
Pop as many COVID-19 virus cells before time runs out.
Tap quickly and tap often. Some corona viruses are harder to pop that others. It&amp;rsquo;s because they&amp;rsquo;re sneaky, and they&amp;rsquo;re wearing surgical masks too!
How many covid 19 viruses can you beat? Let&amp;rsquo;s defeat this killer plague together.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
