<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kids on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/kids/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kids on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/kids/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Protect the Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/protect-the-kingdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:57 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/protect-the-kingdom/</guid>
      <description>Swing high, middle or low to hit the ball. Find your sweet spot and perfect timing. Hit correctly and score a baseball home run!
A simple arcade style baseball game for the fans.
Features: Simple controls to hit high, medium or low Baseball stadium theme, great for brand exposure The game gets more challenging as you score more home runs! Possibility of integrating a high score leaderboard to compete with other players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Guess What</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:54:22 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</guid>
      <description>Didi and Friends, popular kids animation with over 1 billion views on Youtube is here with a brand new game.
Guess the hidden character, then drag and drop the matching picture to reveal it.
Teach your kids and toddlers to spot patterns, and get rewarded with happy smiles from Didi the Chicken and his friends!
Features: Fun and vibrant theme, guaranteed to excite kids, preschoolers and toddlers. Simple gameplay suitable for kids Fullscreen mode Learn everyday objects, animals, environmental elements and above all, the brand new set of Didi and Friends characters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:53:32 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Showcase your kids creativity via this coloring book, featuring Didi and Friends.
A fun, all-digital and reusable coloring book built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Multiple Didi &amp;amp; Friends themed templates to start with Choose different brush sizes and colours Full screen mode for immersive experience Did something wrong? Undo your colors via an eraser Save your works and print them. This feature is great for classrooms Color interesting characters from the Didi &amp;amp; Friends universe, including Didi, Nana, Jojo, Tatak, Bingo and Pak Atan, Positive theme, to foster good vibes via colouring </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scratch and Match Animal</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/scratch-and-match-animal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/scratch-and-match-animal/</guid>
      <description>You have 3 minutes to scratch and match the animal cards. Beat the time and your high score!
Scratch and match beautifully done cards featuring giraffes, elephants, monkeys, tigers, rabbits, cheetahs, polar bears and elephants.
Features: Tutorial Intuitive scratching interface Fun and positive vibe for all ages </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cash Back</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cash-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cash-back/</guid>
      <description>Calculate and return the correct change to customers. Return a combination of dollar notes and coins to customers who purchase items from your store.
Score correctly and generate sales for your store!
Features: Interactive tutorial Hints system 3 difficulty modes Happy theme suitable for young kids </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Faces</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/funny-faces/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/funny-faces/</guid>
      <description>Quick, you have 5 seconds to remember the face.
Then, drag and drop face parts into the correct positions.
How fast can you reconstruct each face?
Features: Fun and uplifting theme Increasingly complex faces to reconstruct. It gets challenging! Interactive tutorial Attention to detail. Players get to work on hair, eyes, eyebrows, nose, mouth, glasses, moustache and more. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Piggy Piggy Farm</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-farm/</guid>
      <description>Mango Piggy Piggy is HUNGRY. He comes across a mango farm. The mangoes look sweet and juicy, just like how he likes it.
Drag and aim to launch Mango Piggy Piggy towards the mangos. Eat them all to earn 3 stars!
Features: Fun, positive and ridiculously cute character. MPP bounces around and squeals almost like a soft toy. Innovative touch and drag mechanic Over 30 levels Unlock a hidden level Don&amp;rsquo;t eat the red mango!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways Jr Zanys Hospital</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-jr-zanys-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-jr-zanys-hospital/</guid>
      <description>From the creators of Dumb Ways to Die, the hit brand with over 300 million downloads total on Google Play and Apple App Store - we present to you an exciting spin-off brand called Dumb Ways JR Zany&amp;rsquo;s Hospital.
Visit Dumb Ways Hospital with Doctor Zany. Explore three main areas of play: a waiting room full of surprises to discover, a check-up room where children can play the role of doctor, and an ambulance that visits the hospital featuring fun guest appearances from the original Dumb Ways cast!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Build Me</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-build-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-build-me/</guid>
      <description>Remember the parts, then drag and drop the parts to form a complete character.
We&amp;rsquo;re proud to present Arty Mouse - Build Me, a branded game built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Interactive tutorial Fun theme for kids of all ages - helps to train cognitive abilities and memory Work with a variety of interesting characters from the Arty Mouse universe, including Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, and Spiro the snail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Sticker Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-sticker-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-sticker-book/</guid>
      <description>Now, your kids can express themselves through art.
Place your favourite Arty Mouse stickers onto the board, decorate them as you wish.
Drag and drop, resize and reposition them to your hearts content. Need to erase a sticker? No problem.
Create millions of sticker combinations using different Arty Mouse characters, objects and backgrounds. Work with Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, Spiro the snail, and more characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Chicken Memory Match</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-memory-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-memory-match/</guid>
      <description>From the hit animation series Chuck Chicken, we bring you this exciting memory match game.
Match your favorite Chuck Chicken cards, and do it in the shortest amount of time!
Discover cool cards featuring Chuck, Flick, Wing as well as nemesis cards including Dr Mingo, Dee, Don, Dex.
Features: Interactive tutorial Beautiful Chuck Chicken artwork Simple, crisp gameplay Fast paced action card theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-and-friends-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-and-friends-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Express your creativity via this coloring book.
We&amp;rsquo;re proud to present Arty Mouse &amp;amp; Friends Coloring Book, a digital coloring book built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Multiple templates to start with Choose different brush sizes and colours Eraser mode Save your works (useful if you&amp;rsquo;d like to print the pictures) Color interesting characters from the Arty Mouse universe, including Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, and Spiro the snail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Connect the Dots</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-connect-the-dots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-connect-the-dots/</guid>
      <description>Didi and Friends, popular kids animation with over 1 billion views on Youtube is here with a brand new game.
Connect the dots to reveal interesting objects, animals and characters.
Teach your kids and toddlers to connect the dots, and get rewarded with happy smiles from Didi the Chicken and his friends!
Features: Fun and vibrant theme, guaranteed to excite kids, preschoolers and toddlers. Simple gameplay suitable for kids Fullscreen mode Learn everyday objects, animals, environmental elements and above all, the brand new set of Didi and Friends characters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kuu Kuu Harajuku Diy Kawaii Stickers</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/kuu-kuu-harajuku-diy-kawaii-stickers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/kuu-kuu-harajuku-diy-kawaii-stickers/</guid>
      <description>Tick tock, time to rock! Kuu Kuu Harajuku is an animation brand created by Grammy winner Gwen Stefani. They&amp;rsquo;re back with a game for tween and teen girls!
Create your own sticker book with characters from the hit TV series. Drag and drop stickers that represent G, Love, Angel, Music and Baby into beautiful backgrounds of Harajuku City. Start with the Clubhouse, and move your way to decorate the studio, parks, and the Harajuku City skyline!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boj Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Showcase your creativity via this coloring book, featuring Boj and friends. A fun, all-digital and reusable coloring book built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Multiple Boj themed templates to start with Choose different brush sizes and colours Did something wrong? Undo your colors via an eraser Save your works and print them. This feature is great for classrooms Color interesting characters from the Boj universe, including Boj the Bilby himself, Mimi, Pops, Denzil, Mr Cloppity, Mia Twitch, Julie Twitch and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boj Giggly Park Adventure</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-giggly-park-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-giggly-park-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Explore Giggly Park with Boj and friends.
Boj is an award winning kids television series worldwide.
Do wonderful things such as ride a bike, climb the tree, fly a kite, dig underground for treasures, ride the swing, control a helicopter remotely and more.
Interact with various characters from the Boj universe, such as Mimi, Pops, Mr Cloppity, Denzil, Mia Twitch and more.
This is a new and innovative gameplay to encourage users to explore their curiosity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Chicken Magic Egg</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-magic-egg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-magic-egg/</guid>
      <description>Chuck Chicken is on a mission. Defeat his nemesis Dee, Don, Dex, Dr Mingo and more in this exciting and fast-paced puzzle platformer game.
Chuck Chicken is a worldwide kids and tweens animation brand with over 2 billion views.
In this game, throw your egg, and watch as it bounces from wall to wall, defeating your opponents.
Collect magic eggs to transform Chuck into his alter ego super hero. For example,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oddbods Ice Cream Fight</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-ice-cream-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-ice-cream-fight/</guid>
      <description>The mischievous Oddbods are at it again! Throw delicious ice cream at them, before they throw back!
This ice cream fight is getting wild! The Oddbods can duck, run left and right, and also appear out of nowhere to attack you.
Features: battle against different Oddbods such as Fuse, Bubbles, Pogo, Zee, Slick, Jeff and Newt. boss levels with Fuse. He&amp;rsquo;s a tough one to crack! fun theme song increasingly difficult challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oddbods Soccer Challenge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-soccer-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-soccer-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Fancy a soccer game with your favourite Oddbods? Kick the ball into the goal, but beware! The mischievous Oddbods are here to stop you.
Features: Compete against Oddbods such as Fuse, Bubbles, Pogo, Zee, Slick, Jeff and Newt. Fun Oddbods theme song Each Oddbod brings something interesting to the game Over 60 levels more more to be added soon Interactive tutorial Fans of soccer or football will love this game. If you&amp;rsquo;re into the World Cup, English Premier League or UEFA Champions League, this game will be interesting too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flossy and Jim Whale Tickler</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flossy-and-jim-whale-tickler/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flossy-and-jim-whale-tickler/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a cute whale that you can tickle all day long.
Tickle and rub the whale until the bar fills up. Watch as you receive a special response from the whale.
With this game, spread the positivity and feel-good vibe with your audience.
Features: Random emotions and quotes each time Extremely cute design This whale has tusk! It&amp;rsquo;s a Narwhal! Unlimited gameplay and tickles Fun and chill music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Learn Abc</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-learn-abc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-learn-abc/</guid>
      <description>Arty Mouse is back with a new game! Teach your toddlers to trace alphabets from A to Z.
Help them recognize letter shapes and associate them with phonic sounds.
Suitable for toddlers, preschool and kindergarten kids.
Work with fun characters from the Arty Mouse universe, including Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, Spiro the snail, and more characters.
Features: Interactive tutorial Upper and lower case alphabet tracing Fun, welcoming and inclusive game for kids </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wheels on the Bus Sing Along</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/wheels-on-the-bus-sing-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/wheels-on-the-bus-sing-along/</guid>
      <description>The wheels on the bus go round and round in this kids activity game. Ride the bus with fellow animals such as Tiger the driver, Elephant, Rabbit, Monkey and Fox.
Listen to the sweet voice singing the song. Allow your kids to work on discovery activities such as tapping on the animals, activating the bus lights, making the bird sing, honking the bus and more.
Features: real vocals by voice actors cute animal characters touch-based activities for kids to keep busy This game is great for parents teaching kids sing-along songs with activities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
