<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adventure on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/adventure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Adventure on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:50:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/adventure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways to Die 2 the Games</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:50:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</guid>
      <description>Dumb Ways to Die is back with a bigger and better sequel to the original.
In Dumb Ways To Die 2 - The Games, now you can access various maps and locations to try out even more fun and dangerous challenges.
Collect tokens to unlock different aspects of the city, while complete mini challenges perfectly (or imperfectly, depending on how you play). Score points to keep your ranking high.
Play in cool locations such as Adrenaland, Drown Town, Dumbest of the Dumb, and Freezerville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Hunt</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oil-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:48:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oil-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Stretch out a pipe in order to strike oil.
Hit it big as you guide oil-hungry heroes and monsters in a mystical wasteland! Aim for the highest score, and unlock funny characters!
Explore different lands - from long stretching savannas, to green hills, sandy beaches and dark marshes - you’ll be surprised at all the places you’ll find where you can just stick a pipe and watch as tons of fantastic tasty dark stuff spill out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stupid Zombies</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stupid-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:44:27 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stupid-zombies/</guid>
      <description>One man, one shotgun and a whole lot of zombies. You are humanity&amp;rsquo;s last hope, and it&amp;rsquo;s your job to keep them brainless.
Adjust your shots and angles, and you watch your bullets ricochet from wall to wall, elegantly picking off each zombie&amp;rsquo;s arms and limbs.
Features: 4 giant stages with over 360 challenging levels Exciting zombie theme Simple and innovative ricochet based gameplay. Defeat the stupid zombies with brains and ingenuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rise Higher</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/rise-higher/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/rise-higher/</guid>
      <description>Protect your balloon with your shield.
Move your mouse or finger to block incoming threads from popping your balloon!
Features: Endless gameplay. Easy to learn, hard to master Peaceful and happy theme Very challenging obstacles as you go higher up Save your high score and beat it later </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways Jr Zanys Hospital</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-jr-zanys-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-jr-zanys-hospital/</guid>
      <description>From the creators of Dumb Ways to Die, the hit brand with over 300 million downloads total on Google Play and Apple App Store - we present to you an exciting spin-off brand called Dumb Ways JR Zany&amp;rsquo;s Hospital.
Visit Dumb Ways Hospital with Doctor Zany. Explore three main areas of play: a waiting room full of surprises to discover, a check-up room where children can play the role of doctor, and an ambulance that visits the hospital featuring fun guest appearances from the original Dumb Ways cast!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boj Giggly Park Adventure</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-giggly-park-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-giggly-park-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Explore Giggly Park with Boj and friends.
Boj is an award winning kids television series worldwide.
Do wonderful things such as ride a bike, climb the tree, fly a kite, dig underground for treasures, ride the swing, control a helicopter remotely and more.
Interact with various characters from the Boj universe, such as Mimi, Pops, Mr Cloppity, Denzil, Mia Twitch and more.
This is a new and innovative gameplay to encourage users to explore their curiosity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooking Love</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cooking-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cooking-love/</guid>
      <description>You just arrived in New York, to pursue your dream of becoming a chef.
Your plan? Work for the famed and attractive chef extraordinaire, Giovanni van Damme to gain experience.
Work your way up the culinary ladder to become Manhattan&amp;rsquo;s hottest chef, in this episode driven interactive story novel.
Discover food, friendship and love. Stumble through life and live the ups and downs of what the Big Apple has to offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Escape From Aztec</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/escape-from-aztec/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 12:42:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/escape-from-aztec/</guid>
      <description>You just stole King Aztec&amp;rsquo;s greatest treasure. Now you&amp;rsquo;re being hunted.
Run as fast as you can. Avoid tree trunks, boulders and ancient ruins. Switch lanes, jump and slide your way to freedom.
Collect treasures along the way to purchase powerups.
How far can you escape?
Features: 3D-like environment built with Aztec theme Use Aztec coins to purchase powerups in the store Use a variety of powerups such as invincibility, coin magnets, megaboost and extra lives </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
