<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Board on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/board/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Board on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:52:39 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/board/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Onet Connect</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/onect-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:52:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/onect-connect/</guid>
      <description>Connect fruit tiles of the same image.
A game of creativity, problem solving and cognitive enhancement.
Use fewer than 3 lines. Only 2 tiles per connection. This is not a match 3 game, but rather a match 2 game that focuses on spatial training and puzzle solving.
Features 3 difficulty levels. Easy, medium and hard Randomized set, every time you play. Ensure unlimited gameplay. Casual theme, suitable for all ages and families Ability to shuffle the set Huge set for long periods of gameplay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crossword Casual</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/crossword-casual/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/crossword-casual/</guid>
      <description>Solve everyday crossword puzzles involving various themes such as cities, objects, food, and buildings.
Features: Full screen mode Easy to use crossword puzzle. Regardless of device, play the same crossword puzzle as everybody else Easy selection of puzzle grid to insert answers Virtual keyboard for mobile and tablet users. Easily enter your answers to solve the puzzles Random puzzles generated from a pool of questions and answers Relaxing theme, suitable for everyone Note: if you&amp;rsquo;d like different themes, please contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese New Year Mahjong</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cny-mahjong/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cny-mahjong/</guid>
      <description>Match chinese mahjong tiles to complete the levels.
Features: beautiful chinese inspired art interactive tutorial extremely simple and addictive gameplay easy to start, hard to master fun chinese / asian theme, coupled with mahjong matching elements power ups to reward the user, such as auto solve bonuses </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backgammon</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/backgammon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/backgammon/</guid>
      <description>The objective is to move all your checkers into your home board. Then, bear them off.
Plan your strategy, roll the dice, and leave everything else to luck!
Features: Tutorial included Choose your color Three difficulty modes : easy, medium and hard Fun and casual theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spider Solitaire</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/spider-solitaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/spider-solitaire/</guid>
      <description>Spider themed solitaire game. You&amp;rsquo;ll definitely get addicted
Features: stunning spider theme tutorial feeling stuck? Use our hints system hours of repetitive gameplay. Each deck is randomly generated. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yatzy</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/yatzy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/yatzy/</guid>
      <description>Everyone loves dice games. Roll the dice, pick the combination and try to outscore your opponent.
If you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of Yacht or Yahtzee, you&amp;rsquo;ll fall in love with this game.
Features Interactive tutorial Fun theme suitable for all ages Includes a rolling cup and scorepad! Bonus animation if you get a &amp;lsquo;Yatzy&amp;rsquo; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Casual Chess</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/casual-chess/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/casual-chess/</guid>
      <description>Play classic chess against the computer. Plan your moves and execute your strategies to outwit your opponent.
Features 3 different themes Easy, moderate and hard computer AI Play as white or black in this two (2) player game Hints system to guide your moves Fun casual theme, suitable for all ages </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bingo Solo</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bingo-solo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bingo-solo/</guid>
      <description>Play bingo by yourself. A single player bingo game.
Choose from 3 different speeds, based on what you need.
Features: Simple gameplay, great for solo play Real voices that call the numbers No computer opponents No AI opponents Can be installed in offline environments Win patterns included </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dominoes</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dominoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dominoes/</guid>
      <description>Draw dominoes: Every round, match tiles until your opponent is unable to move. If you have no possible moves, draw a domino until you can match a tile. If there are no dominoes left, pass your turn until you can. Reach 100 points to win.
Block dominoes: The same as Draw Dominoes. The main difference is, if you have no possible moves, pass your turn until you can match a tile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Crossword</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/holiday-crossword/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/holiday-crossword/</guid>
      <description>Solve holiday themed crossword puzzles involving various topics such as cities, food, celebrations and gift ideas.
Features: Full screen mode Easy to use cross word puzzle. Regardless of device, play the same crossword puzzle as everybody else Easy selection of puzzle grid to insert answers Virtual keyboard for mobile and tablet users. Easily enter your answers to solve the puzzles Random puzzles generated from a pool of questions and answers Relaxing theme, suitable for everyone Note: if you&amp;rsquo;d like different themes and questions, please contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Soccer</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/smart-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/smart-soccer/</guid>
      <description>Soccer has never been this fun. Simply drag, aim and release to shoot the soccer ball.
The first to score 3 goals wins.
Features: Choose your side, from 32 nations. Smart and calculative AI. Be prepared to play hard! Tutorial to learn the ropes Exciting soccer stadium environment, perfect for soccer nuts </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
