<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cars on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/cars/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cars on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:58:19 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/cars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Connect the Roads</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/connect-the-roads/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:58:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/connect-the-roads/</guid>
      <description>Your car needs to get to work! Move the road tiles to complete the road.
Can you get three stars for each level?
Features: Simple draggable tiles Fun city theme Turn grid on or off 24 challenging levels guaranteed to twist your brain Fans of pipe games and picture sliders will love this game. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bomb the Bridge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bomb-the-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:51:50 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bomb-the-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Plant C4 bombs anywhere on the bridge.
Wait for enemy troops to cross, then detonate them.
Blow up 100% of the bridge and eliminate all troops to score 3 stars.
Features: Realistic physics Addictive theme Challenging levels Blow up armies, military trucks and tanks! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drift Boss</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/drift-boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:47:37 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/drift-boss/</guid>
      <description>Drift your car like a boss. Drift left and right with good timing.
Concentrate and anticipate your drifts and skids in tight spots.
How many points can you score?
Features: Great arcade 3d environment Unlock cool vehicles by collecting more points. Unlock trucks, taxis, police cars, ice cream trucks, ambulances, firetrucks and more. Full responsive design Full screen capability Great soundtracknd theme. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank Battle</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tank-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tank-battle/</guid>
      <description>Two tanks emerge on the battlefield. Only one will survive. Can you outsmart the other tank?
Collect ammo crates and powerups. Navigate your way to the enemy tank. Fire away!
This is the perfect game to play with friends and family.
Tip: For two player mode, play on the same device (one finger on each side). Enhance social interaction of your audience!
Features: Interactive tutorial to learn the ropes Collect different powerups such as additional health, bubble shields and speed boost Randomly generated battlefield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Megacity Hop</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/megacity-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/megacity-hop/</guid>
      <description>Cross the roads with busy traffic. Hop your way across this endless mega city!
On desktop, use your arrow keys to move.
On smartphones and tablets, simply swipe to move.
Features: Easy and intuitive controls. Tap to move forward, swipe left or ride to move horizontally Collect coins to unlock various characters in the shop Play characters such as business man, cool DJ , office lady, policeman and sheriff Dynamic generation of terrain to provide endless gameplay If you&amp;rsquo;ve played crossy type games, this is a perfect fit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Truck Driving</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/monster-truck-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/monster-truck-driving/</guid>
      <description>Control your monster truck to reach the flag.
Boost, brake and tilt your truck left/right to navigate the path.
Earn stars by completing the level in record time.
Features: Interactive tutorial Use stars to unlock cool characters such as a cool flaming truck, Batman truck, Shark truck, Hyena truck and more. Panning function to plan your routes 20 challenging levels Play repeatedly to get the best high score Upbeat theme Monster Truck and Dirt Bike enthusiasts will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valet Parking</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/valet-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/valet-parking/</guid>
      <description>A must have car parking simulator game. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to learn, and yet incredibly difficult to master.
Park your car in the perfect spot, with surgical precision. Be careful not to bump into other cars and objects.
Put on your safety belt, and let the game begin! Fans of parking frenzy games will love this.
Features: Interactive tutorial Beautiful parking spots 3 Star based system to reward precision Over 50+ parking challenges Keyboard controls for desktop, and touch controls for smartphones and tablets Drive a variety of cool cars </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confident Driver</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/confident-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/confident-driver/</guid>
      <description>How fast are your reflexes? Control your car, pick the right lanes and avoid any crashes to win the level.
Features Drive alongside other vehicles such as mini coopers, new york taxi cabs, trucks, police cars and more Precise and accurate turning, allowing users to cut really sharp corners Beautiful graphics with vehicles closely resembling real vehicles A variety of obstacles such as oil spills, roadblocks, ice and more Challenging levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Lane Racing</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/fast-lane-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/fast-lane-racing/</guid>
      <description>Race against other cars.
Tap to switch lanes. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash into other cars!
Keep on your toes and be prepared to switch lanes quickly in this fastlane game.
Features: Endless gameplay Urban hip hop racing theme Extremely simple controls Simple, linear high score system Fans of racing and driving games will love this.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
