<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Construction on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/construction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Construction on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:51:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/construction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bomb the Bridge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bomb-the-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:51:50 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bomb-the-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Plant C4 bombs anywhere on the bridge.
Wait for enemy troops to cross, then detonate them.
Blow up 100% of the bridge and eliminate all troops to score 3 stars.
Features: Realistic physics Addictive theme Challenging levels Blow up armies, military trucks and tanks! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Construct a Bridge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/construct-a-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/construct-a-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Hello Engineer! Build a bridge that does not collapse.
Connect joints with lines, to create your engineering marvel.
Then, test your bridge with real trucks passing over.
Will your bridge stand the test?
Your construction is limited by the amount of funds you have, so build your bridge wisely!
Features: Fun theme suitable for everyone Grid system enabled for easier construction Ability to edit your bridge anytime via Undo command Ability to delete portions of your bridge via the Delete command </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sky Castle</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sky-castle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sky-castle/</guid>
      <description>My liege, stack the castle parts above each other. Stack them high and strong. Be the ruler of the tallest castle in the world.
Features: Endless gameplay. Spend hours trying to perfect your placement. The castle becomes more challenging to build as they get higher Simple controls: tap to place castle blocks Use a variety of helpers such as Reverse, Repeat, Insurance, and Double Coins Beautiful graphics and ancient medieval theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stack the Pancake</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stack-the-pancake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stack-the-pancake/</guid>
      <description>Drag and drop the pancake from the pan, onto the plate. It&amp;rsquo;s that simple!
How many pancakes can you pile up? Use your creativity to build stable and towering pan cakes!
Features: Interactive tutorial Fun casual theme, suitable for everyone Addictive stacking gameplay. Make your users compete to get the highest score Intuitive touch based controls </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
