<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Puzzle on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/puzzle/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Puzzle on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:58:19 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/puzzle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Connect the Roads</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/connect-the-roads/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:58:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/connect-the-roads/</guid>
      <description>Your car needs to get to work! Move the road tiles to complete the road.
Can you get three stars for each level?
Features: Simple draggable tiles Fun city theme Turn grid on or off 24 challenging levels guaranteed to twist your brain Fans of pipe games and picture sliders will love this game. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Bears</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/love-bears/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:55:50 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/love-bears/</guid>
      <description>Draw lines and shapes to bump the bears. Find a way to bring the two love bears together.
Everything you draw turns into real objects!
Collect 3 stars for every level successfully completed.
Features: Beautiful scenery and theme. Addictive tracing gameplay. Draw anything. Over 30 challenging levels per episode. Extremely cute pastel color theme. Cute bears with hats, glasses, panda caps and more! Suitable for all ages. Fans of Love Balls and Happy Glass will enjoy this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Guess What</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:54:22 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</guid>
      <description>Didi and Friends, popular kids animation with over 1 billion views on Youtube is here with a brand new game.
Guess the hidden character, then drag and drop the matching picture to reveal it.
Teach your kids and toddlers to spot patterns, and get rewarded with happy smiles from Didi the Chicken and his friends!
Features: Fun and vibrant theme, guaranteed to excite kids, preschoolers and toddlers. Simple gameplay suitable for kids Fullscreen mode Learn everyday objects, animals, environmental elements and above all, the brand new set of Didi and Friends characters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Onet Connect</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/onect-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:52:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/onect-connect/</guid>
      <description>Connect fruit tiles of the same image.
A game of creativity, problem solving and cognitive enhancement.
Use fewer than 3 lines. Only 2 tiles per connection. This is not a match 3 game, but rather a match 2 game that focuses on spatial training and puzzle solving.
Features 3 difficulty levels. Easy, medium and hard Randomized set, every time you play. Ensure unlimited gameplay. Casual theme, suitable for all ages and families Ability to shuffle the set Huge set for long periods of gameplay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bomb the Bridge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bomb-the-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:51:50 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bomb-the-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Plant C4 bombs anywhere on the bridge.
Wait for enemy troops to cross, then detonate them.
Blow up 100% of the bridge and eliminate all troops to score 3 stars.
Features: Realistic physics Addictive theme Challenging levels Blow up armies, military trucks and tanks! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Hunt</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oil-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:48:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oil-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Stretch out a pipe in order to strike oil.
Hit it big as you guide oil-hungry heroes and monsters in a mystical wasteland! Aim for the highest score, and unlock funny characters!
Explore different lands - from long stretching savannas, to green hills, sandy beaches and dark marshes - you’ll be surprised at all the places you’ll find where you can just stick a pipe and watch as tons of fantastic tasty dark stuff spill out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kill the Spy</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/kill-the-spy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:45:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/kill-the-spy/</guid>
      <description>Armed with your trusty pistol, it&amp;rsquo;s up to you, Agent 007 to eliminate the enemy spy agents.
Tap on the correct blocks to eliminate the spy agents. Use the least amount of moves to earn more stars.
Do not hard the hostages, or else the mission will fail.
Features: Innovative physics and game mechanics. Aim your spy pistol to split structures into multiple pieces Collect treasures to increase your score Place your shots correctly to earn more stars Spy theme and sound effects Fans of James Bond , Men in Black and spy themed novels will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stupid Zombies</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stupid-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:44:27 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stupid-zombies/</guid>
      <description>One man, one shotgun and a whole lot of zombies. You are humanity&amp;rsquo;s last hope, and it&amp;rsquo;s your job to keep them brainless.
Adjust your shots and angles, and you watch your bullets ricochet from wall to wall, elegantly picking off each zombie&amp;rsquo;s arms and limbs.
Features: 4 giant stages with over 360 challenging levels Exciting zombie theme Simple and innovative ricochet based gameplay. Defeat the stupid zombies with brains and ingenuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Construct a Bridge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/construct-a-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/construct-a-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Hello Engineer! Build a bridge that does not collapse.
Connect joints with lines, to create your engineering marvel.
Then, test your bridge with real trucks passing over.
Will your bridge stand the test?
Your construction is limited by the amount of funds you have, so build your bridge wisely!
Features: Fun theme suitable for everyone Grid system enabled for easier construction Ability to edit your bridge anytime via Undo command Ability to delete portions of your bridge via the Delete command </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puzzle Slide Travel Edition</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/puzzle-slide-travel-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/puzzle-slide-travel-edition/</guid>
      <description>A picture slide game with a travel theme. Complete the puzzles in the shortest amount of time
Solve puzzles of famous locations such as New York&amp;rsquo;s Manhattan Bridge, The London Eye, Eiffel Tower of Paris, Forbidden City in Beijing, Tokyo Imperial Palace, Pyramids of Egypt, and more.
Features New-age, Instagram design for the millennial generation Easy, medium and hard modes Solve all kinds of puzzles from around the world Simple design to encourage focus Multiple puzzles to try Relaxed environment </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vampires and Garlic</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/vampires-and-garlic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/vampires-and-garlic/</guid>
      <description>Halloween and vampires are upon us! What do vampires dislike? Garlic!
Throw garlic bombs (yes, made out of garlic) at pesky vampires. Control the angle and strength of your throws.
Remember to watch your garlic count!
Features: A variety of obstacles including challenging terrain, and objects such as boxes, pulleys and TNTs. Simple point and click throwing mechanic Interactive tutorial 30 challenging levels Fun halloween theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crossword Casual</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/crossword-casual/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/crossword-casual/</guid>
      <description>Solve everyday crossword puzzles involving various themes such as cities, objects, food, and buildings.
Features: Full screen mode Easy to use crossword puzzle. Regardless of device, play the same crossword puzzle as everybody else Easy selection of puzzle grid to insert answers Virtual keyboard for mobile and tablet users. Easily enter your answers to solve the puzzles Random puzzles generated from a pool of questions and answers Relaxing theme, suitable for everyone Note: if you&amp;rsquo;d like different themes, please contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini Golf Adventure</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mini-golf-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mini-golf-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Put the ball into the hole. Use the shortest amount of putts to score maximum stars.
Collect gems to increase your score! Embark on this fun golfing adventure, as your discover new objects and power-ups to help you win.
Features: Discover new elements in this golf paradise, such as the magnet, teleportation stations, windmills, wind accelerators, and yes, a mole! Who&amp;rsquo;s the mole? Interactive tutorial to start putting away Over 24 levels and more to come Fun family oriented theme, suitable for all ages </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Crush</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jewel-crush/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jewel-crush/</guid>
      <description>Match jewels to score points. Hit the targets to complete each level.
Watch out! You only have limited moves per level.
Earn 3 stars for completing the levels successfully. Discover cool powerups such as row clearing, column clearing, jewel bombs and snowflakes.
Features: Beautiful and shiny jewels to match Over 30 challenging levels Discover cool chain reactions as you complete each level If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a challenging Match-3 game with deep levels and powerups, this is the game for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Liner</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/one-liner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/one-liner/</guid>
      <description>Draw one single line, without ever lifting your finger or mouse.
How many levels can you complete?
Deceptively simple, yet profoundly deep game.
Features: Interactive tutorial Over 120 challenging levels to keep you occupied Upbeat, rhythmic theme How difficult can this be? Just Draw 1 Line! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese New Year Mahjong</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cny-mahjong/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cny-mahjong/</guid>
      <description>Match chinese mahjong tiles to complete the levels.
Features: beautiful chinese inspired art interactive tutorial extremely simple and addictive gameplay easy to start, hard to master fun chinese / asian theme, coupled with mahjong matching elements power ups to reward the user, such as auto solve bonuses </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Hour</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/happy-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/happy-hour/</guid>
      <description>Fill up the martini glass. It&amp;rsquo;s Happy Hour!
Control the flow of drinks to fill up your glass! Everything you draw turns into real objects.
Come up with your own solution to each level.
Features: Funny Happy Hour quotes. Work on multiple drinks including cocktails, wine, spirits, beer and other alcohol related items. Beautiful bar scene and nightlife theme Chill vibe Addictive tracing gameplay. Draw anything. Over 30 challenging levels per city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spidey Swing</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/spidey-swing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/spidey-swing/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the adventures of Spidey. Shoot webs, grab on and swing like a spider pro. Avoid things such as sharp edges, rotating chainsaws, arrows, mace and other deadly objects.
Keep the majority of your body parts intact, and get to the finish line. Keep our beloved Spidey alive!
Features Interactive tutorial Touch, keyboard and mouse controls City skyscraper theme Update: Over 48 extremely challenging levels. Test your spider-man skills. Presence of blood and gore (can be turned off by request) Fans of spiderman and marvel superheroes will love the game </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Truck Driving</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/monster-truck-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/monster-truck-driving/</guid>
      <description>Control your monster truck to reach the flag.
Boost, brake and tilt your truck left/right to navigate the path.
Earn stars by completing the level in record time.
Features: Interactive tutorial Use stars to unlock cool characters such as a cool flaming truck, Batman truck, Shark truck, Hyena truck and more. Panning function to plan your routes 20 challenging levels Play repeatedly to get the best high score Upbeat theme Monster Truck and Dirt Bike enthusiasts will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Baseball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/extreme-baseball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/extreme-baseball/</guid>
      <description>Aim and release your baseball to knock out your opponents.
Bounce the ball off the walls to cleverly knock out multiple enemies in one attempt.
Collect baseball cards to increase your score.
Features: Tutorial to learn the ropes Interact with multiple elements such as glass, wood boxes, TNTs, buttons, moving platforms and more. Over 20 challenging levels Baseball card collectors will love this High tempo music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unblocked</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/unblocked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/unblocked/</guid>
      <description>Clear a path for the red block. How many moves do you need, to win?
Features: Bright and positive theme 24 challenging levels Interactive hint system to help solve the puzzle </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valet Parking</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/valet-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/valet-parking/</guid>
      <description>A must have car parking simulator game. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to learn, and yet incredibly difficult to master.
Park your car in the perfect spot, with surgical precision. Be careful not to bump into other cars and objects.
Put on your safety belt, and let the game begin! Fans of parking frenzy games will love this.
Features: Interactive tutorial Beautiful parking spots 3 Star based system to reward precision Over 50+ parking challenges Keyboard controls for desktop, and touch controls for smartphones and tablets Drive a variety of cool cars </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Soccer</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-soccer/</guid>
      <description>Aim and shoot the ball into the goal. Collect the starfish to gain maximum score.
With golden sand, coconut trees, sand castles, crabs, and a gorgeous sunshine, what more do you need?
Features: Interactive tutorial Over 20 challenging levels. Put your thinking cap on. Fun beach theme and music Interact with challenging obstacles such as crabs, sandcastles, and more. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drone Pickup Service</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/drone-pickup-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/drone-pickup-service/</guid>
      <description>The drone revolution has arrived. You operate a Drone pick up service.
Your goal is to navigate the drones into difficult conditions, pick up the packages and return to base.
Fly around trees, hills, cars, airplanes and wind mills to pick up your package.
Complete your tasks in the fastest time to achieve 3 stars.
Features: easy left/right tapping mechanics to navigate extremely challenging levels with various obstacles Play with keyboard , mouse or touch Fun theme and music, suitable for a techy audience who grows up with Uber, Amazon, Instacart and on-demand delivery services </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Piggy Piggy Farm</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-farm/</guid>
      <description>Mango Piggy Piggy is HUNGRY. He comes across a mango farm. The mangoes look sweet and juicy, just like how he likes it.
Drag and aim to launch Mango Piggy Piggy towards the mangos. Eat them all to earn 3 stars!
Features: Fun, positive and ridiculously cute character. MPP bounces around and squeals almost like a soft toy. Innovative touch and drag mechanic Over 30 levels Unlock a hidden level Don&amp;rsquo;t eat the red mango!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Horace vs Cheese</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/horace-vs-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/horace-vs-cheese/</guid>
      <description>Pull and launch Horace the Hamster into the cheese. Eat them all to earn 3 stars.
Then, land safely into the cheese house.
From the creators of Flossy and Jim, we bring you a new brand called Horace and co.
Features: Fun, positive and ridiculously cute character. Horace bounces around and squeals almost like a soft toy. Innovative touch and drag mechanic Over 30 levels Unlock a hidden level Don&amp;rsquo;t eat the blue cheese!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Chicken Memory Match</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-memory-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-memory-match/</guid>
      <description>From the hit animation series Chuck Chicken, we bring you this exciting memory match game.
Match your favorite Chuck Chicken cards, and do it in the shortest amount of time!
Discover cool cards featuring Chuck, Flick, Wing as well as nemesis cards including Dr Mingo, Dee, Don, Dex.
Features: Interactive tutorial Beautiful Chuck Chicken artwork Simple, crisp gameplay Fast paced action card theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Connect the Dots</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-connect-the-dots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-connect-the-dots/</guid>
      <description>Didi and Friends, popular kids animation with over 1 billion views on Youtube is here with a brand new game.
Connect the dots to reveal interesting objects, animals and characters.
Teach your kids and toddlers to connect the dots, and get rewarded with happy smiles from Didi the Chicken and his friends!
Features: Fun and vibrant theme, guaranteed to excite kids, preschoolers and toddlers. Simple gameplay suitable for kids Fullscreen mode Learn everyday objects, animals, environmental elements and above all, the brand new set of Didi and Friends characters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Piggy Piggy Hero</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-hero/</guid>
      <description>Mango Piggy Piggy is back with a brand new series and new episodes.
In his hero edition, control different superhero piggies, as you attempt to defend your town against the invasion of enemy robots.
Whats New:
Activate Panther Piggy to dash through obstacles. Activate Hulk Piggy to create a memorable, powerful smash attack. Activate Marvel Piggy to deal widespread damage to enemies. Activate Antman Piggy to suddenly become huge and inflict crazy damage Activate Spider Piggy to pull targets towards it Launch your hero piggy against the enemy, in Angry Birds fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Chicken Magic Egg</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-magic-egg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-magic-egg/</guid>
      <description>Chuck Chicken is on a mission. Defeat his nemesis Dee, Don, Dex, Dr Mingo and more in this exciting and fast-paced puzzle platformer game.
Chuck Chicken is a worldwide kids and tweens animation brand with over 2 billion views.
In this game, throw your egg, and watch as it bounces from wall to wall, defeating your opponents.
Collect magic eggs to transform Chuck into his alter ego super hero. For example,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oddbods Soccer Challenge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-soccer-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-soccer-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Fancy a soccer game with your favourite Oddbods? Kick the ball into the goal, but beware! The mischievous Oddbods are here to stop you.
Features: Compete against Oddbods such as Fuse, Bubbles, Pogo, Zee, Slick, Jeff and Newt. Fun Oddbods theme song Each Oddbod brings something interesting to the game Over 60 levels more more to be added soon Interactive tutorial Fans of soccer or football will love this game. If you&amp;rsquo;re into the World Cup, English Premier League or UEFA Champions League, this game will be interesting too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stick Golf</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stick-golf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stick-golf/</guid>
      <description>Aim, adjust the club power and go! Playing golf has never been this easy.
From easy to challenging terrains, use your acute golf senses to land a hole in one.
Avoid bunkers and water hazards!
Features: interactive tutorial to help your audience relaxed theme and background. Playing golf has never been this relaxing. earn coins from successful holes use coins at the shop, to purchase fun skins such as top hat, pirate hat, bunny hats and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biker Lane</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/biker-lane/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/biker-lane/</guid>
      <description>Control your bike rider to reach the flag.
Boost, brake and tilt your bike left/right to navigate the tricky roads.
Earn stars by completing the level in record time.
Features: Interactive tutorial Use stars to unlock cool characters such as grandma biker, traffic police biker, punk biker, and pro biker. Panning function to plan your routes 20 challenging levels Play repeatedly to get the best high score Upbeat theme Motorcycle and moto x3m enthusiasts will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Castle Siege</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/castle-siege/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/castle-siege/</guid>
      <description>Use your cannon ball to destroy the foundations of the castle structure.
When the castle structure falls, the guards will be eliminated. Remember to avoid hurting the hostages!
Features: Innovative splitting mechanic. Aim your cannonball to split structures into multiple pieces Collect treasures to increase your score Place your shots correctly to earn more crowns Comedic sound effects Fun relaxed puzzle game </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spider Solitaire</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/spider-solitaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/spider-solitaire/</guid>
      <description>Spider themed solitaire game. You&amp;rsquo;ll definitely get addicted
Features: stunning spider theme tutorial feeling stuck? Use our hints system hours of repetitive gameplay. Each deck is randomly generated. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Echo Simon</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/echo-simon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/echo-simon/</guid>
      <description>Simon says &amp;hellip; watch the sequence.
Memorize the sequence, then recreate it.
How high can you score?
Features: interactive tutorial endless gameplay easy to learn, difficult to master be prepared for surprises at later levels </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trixology</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/trixology/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/trixology/</guid>
      <description>Rotate the piece to fit the grid below. Fans of modern tetris, you&amp;rsquo;ll love this game.
Cover a full row without gaps, and earn yourself bonus points.
How high is your score?
Features: Clear instructions to learn the ropes Minimalist theme ensures focus for long gameplay and time spent Additional controls such as speed down, accelerate, and rotate clockwise / counterclockwise Increasingly difficult as the level progresses </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Line</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/draw-one-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/draw-one-line/</guid>
      <description>Draw one single line, without ever lifting your finger or mouse.
How many levels can you complete?
Deceptively simple, yet profoundly deep game.
Features: Interactive tutorial Over 120 challenging levels to keep you occupied Upbeat, rhythmic theme How difficult can this be? Just Draw 1 Line! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hardest Game on Earth</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/hardest-game-on-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/hardest-game-on-earth/</guid>
      <description>The title says it all! This is the world&amp;rsquo;s hardest game.
Navigate your way through the maze.
Collect coins, keys and avoid obstacles. Don&amp;rsquo;t break your glass!
Features: Tutorial included. Fun earth theme Extremely challenging levels. Be mentally and emotionally prepared! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stack the Pancake</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stack-the-pancake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stack-the-pancake/</guid>
      <description>Drag and drop the pancake from the pan, onto the plate. It&amp;rsquo;s that simple!
How many pancakes can you pile up? Use your creativity to build stable and towering pan cakes!
Features: Interactive tutorial Fun casual theme, suitable for everyone Addictive stacking gameplay. Make your users compete to get the highest score Intuitive touch based controls </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create rows of jewels to win</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jewels-blocks-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jewels-blocks-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Drag and drop jewel blocks to fill the empty gap.
Complete a row of beautiful jewels to score points. Complete 2 rows or more to score bonus points.
How high can you score?
Features: Interactive tutorial Endless gameplay. Play until you run out of turns. Mesmerizing jewel theme to encourage focus and productivity. Fans of tetris and trixology will love this. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bricked</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bricked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bricked/</guid>
      <description>Tap and match bricks of the same color.
Plan your moves carefully, to ensure perfect elimination of the remaining bricks.
How high can you score?
Features: Ability to rewind. You have 3 wishes. Unlimited gameplay. Fun theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Crossword</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/holiday-crossword/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/holiday-crossword/</guid>
      <description>Solve holiday themed crossword puzzles involving various topics such as cities, food, celebrations and gift ideas.
Features: Full screen mode Easy to use cross word puzzle. Regardless of device, play the same crossword puzzle as everybody else Easy selection of puzzle grid to insert answers Virtual keyboard for mobile and tablet users. Easily enter your answers to solve the puzzles Random puzzles generated from a pool of questions and answers Relaxing theme, suitable for everyone Note: if you&amp;rsquo;d like different themes and questions, please contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pipe Master</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pipe-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pipe-master/</guid>
      <description>Rearrange the pipes to make the water flow.
Build your pipe line and convey water from starting to end point. Don&amp;rsquo;t run out of moves!
Features: Beautiful pipe and water graphics Interactive tutorial Over 24 challenging levels. Level 1 is easy, but start wrecking your head with Level 2. Great music and sound effects Full screen version available This game is great for puzzle and cognitive game fans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Colors</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/amazing-colors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/amazing-colors/</guid>
      <description>Swipe to paint in each direction.
Color the floors with the least amount of moves.
Can you beat your own high score?
Painting has never been this fun!
Features: Zen and minimalist theme. Over 60 challenging levels that will amaze you. Interactive tutorial Fully responsive design Colour the floor with a variety of different balls </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lock Master</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/lock-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/lock-master/</guid>
      <description>Tap to start the lock picking process.
Be patient, concentrate and wait until the key touches the orange dot.
When the moment is right, tap to unlock and score a point in this fast, hypercasual game.
How many locks can you unlock?
Features: Easy to play, hard to master Great spy and thief theme Overcome distractions and obstacles in each level </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teddy Bubble Rescue</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/teddy-bubble-rescue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/teddy-bubble-rescue/</guid>
      <description>Big Teddy needs your help! Pop the objects to rescue the mini teddy bears.
Place your shooter aim carefully to clear the maximum amount of objects in each level.
Features: Interactive tutorial 20 challenging levels Fun theme Solve sets using a variety of tactics. Use clever theory of angles, target higher objects and other tactics to solve each level </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
