<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Halloween on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/halloween/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Halloween on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:44:27 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/halloween/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stupid Zombies</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stupid-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:44:27 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stupid-zombies/</guid>
      <description>One man, one shotgun and a whole lot of zombies. You are humanity&amp;rsquo;s last hope, and it&amp;rsquo;s your job to keep them brainless.
Adjust your shots and angles, and you watch your bullets ricochet from wall to wall, elegantly picking off each zombie&amp;rsquo;s arms and limbs.
Features: 4 giant stages with over 360 challenging levels Exciting zombie theme Simple and innovative ricochet based gameplay. Defeat the stupid zombies with brains and ingenuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vampires and Garlic</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/vampires-and-garlic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/vampires-and-garlic/</guid>
      <description>Halloween and vampires are upon us! What do vampires dislike? Garlic!
Throw garlic bombs (yes, made out of garlic) at pesky vampires. Control the angle and strength of your throws.
Remember to watch your garlic count!
Features: A variety of obstacles including challenging terrain, and objects such as boxes, pulleys and TNTs. Simple point and click throwing mechanic Interactive tutorial 30 challenging levels Fun halloween theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Survival</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/zombie-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/zombie-survival/</guid>
      <description>A strange virus outbreak turned your friends into zombies. Armed with a basic pistol, make your way through hordes of zombies.
How many days can you survive, before you become one of them?
Features: 3D like isometric graphics Collect coins with each zombie kill Multiple weapons to purchase. Try the machine gun, shotgun, rifle and laser gun Fun stats to review after each day 3 different gameplay modes: Survival, Hard Point and Nuke Tutorial to learn the ropes Yes, you can blow up barrels to burn the zombies </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skeleton Defense</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/skeleton-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/skeleton-defense/</guid>
      <description>Soldier! You&amp;rsquo;re the last hope for humanity. It&amp;rsquo;s up to you to stop the waves of undead skeletons.
Features: Interactive tutorial to learn the ropes Scary skeleton theme 7 different weapons. Use rifles, grenades, rockets, molotov cocktails and other impressive weapons to stop these skeletons 5 different skeleton types Unlimited gameplay A shop to upgrade and unlock new weapons </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
