<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trivia on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/trivia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trivia on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:58 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/trivia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Trivia Quiz</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/trivia-quiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/trivia-quiz/</guid>
      <description>Test your general knowledge in this trivia quiz game.
How many questions can you answer correctly?
Features: Simple, clean and welcoming theme Easy to configure Trivia Quiz. Let us know what you need, and we&amp;rsquo;ll customize it for you. Question separated into different difficulty levels (easy questions first, followed by more challenging questions) 30 randomly rotated questions per round Over 100 different questions in the pool Fullscreen mode </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sort the Trash</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sort-the-trash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sort-the-trash/</guid>
      <description>Protect the environment by learning how to recycle correctly.
Collect items that can be recycled only. Avoid collecting contaminators such as organic waste, disposable coffee cups, plastic straws, ceramic dishware and lithium ion batteries.
Go green and save the Earth. Start becoming eco-friendly today!
Features: Simple elegant design Responsive design Positive them with recycling facts </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Crossword</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/holiday-crossword/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/holiday-crossword/</guid>
      <description>Solve holiday themed crossword puzzles involving various topics such as cities, food, celebrations and gift ideas.
Features: Full screen mode Easy to use cross word puzzle. Regardless of device, play the same crossword puzzle as everybody else Easy selection of puzzle grid to insert answers Virtual keyboard for mobile and tablet users. Easily enter your answers to solve the puzzles Random puzzles generated from a pool of questions and answers Relaxing theme, suitable for everyone Note: if you&amp;rsquo;d like different themes and questions, please contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
