<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Girls on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/girls/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Girls on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:55:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/girls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Love Bears</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/love-bears/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:55:50 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/love-bears/</guid>
      <description>Draw lines and shapes to bump the bears. Find a way to bring the two love bears together.
Everything you draw turns into real objects!
Collect 3 stars for every level successfully completed.
Features: Beautiful scenery and theme. Addictive tracing gameplay. Draw anything. Over 30 challenging levels per episode. Extremely cute pastel color theme. Cute bears with hats, glasses, panda caps and more! Suitable for all ages. Fans of Love Balls and Happy Glass will enjoy this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agent Curiosa vs Rogue Robots</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/agent-curiosa-vs-rogue-robots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/agent-curiosa-vs-rogue-robots/</guid>
      <description>The robots have gone rogue! It&amp;rsquo;s up to teen hacker, Agent Curiosa to save the world.
Armed with your DIY electric zapper, zap these robots out of existence!
Features: Over 30 challenging levels. Fight robots of all kinds. Face big, bad drones in boss levels. Collect items such as extra bonus scores, invisibility, extra life and score boost. Interactive tutorial. Techy theme suitable for tweens and teens alike. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cash Back</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cash-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cash-back/</guid>
      <description>Calculate and return the correct change to customers. Return a combination of dollar notes and coins to customers who purchase items from your store.
Score correctly and generate sales for your store!
Features: Interactive tutorial Hints system 3 difficulty modes Happy theme suitable for young kids </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Baseball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/extreme-baseball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/extreme-baseball/</guid>
      <description>Aim and release your baseball to knock out your opponents.
Bounce the ball off the walls to cleverly knock out multiple enemies in one attempt.
Collect baseball cards to increase your score.
Features: Tutorial to learn the ropes Interact with multiple elements such as glass, wood boxes, TNTs, buttons, moving platforms and more. Over 20 challenging levels Baseball card collectors will love this High tempo music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Faces</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/funny-faces/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/funny-faces/</guid>
      <description>Quick, you have 5 seconds to remember the face.
Then, drag and drop face parts into the correct positions.
How fast can you reconstruct each face?
Features: Fun and uplifting theme Increasingly complex faces to reconstruct. It gets challenging! Interactive tutorial Attention to detail. Players get to work on hair, eyes, eyebrows, nose, mouth, glasses, moustache and more. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Piggy Piggy Farm</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-farm/</guid>
      <description>Mango Piggy Piggy is HUNGRY. He comes across a mango farm. The mangoes look sweet and juicy, just like how he likes it.
Drag and aim to launch Mango Piggy Piggy towards the mangos. Eat them all to earn 3 stars!
Features: Fun, positive and ridiculously cute character. MPP bounces around and squeals almost like a soft toy. Innovative touch and drag mechanic Over 30 levels Unlock a hidden level Don&amp;rsquo;t eat the red mango!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Ball Dunkin</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/city-ball-dunkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/city-ball-dunkin/</guid>
      <description>Dunk the basketball into each hoop.
Time your dunks well. Make sure you don&amp;rsquo;t hit the ceiling, or fall to the group.
Collect points to unlock different cool balls from the store.
Beware, the challenges get more difficult over time!
Make your way past tricky hoops that move in weird ways.
How high can you score?
Features: A store to unlock different balls. Really cool ones. Fun theme Day and night transition Increasingly challenging gameplay </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Connect the Dots</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-connect-the-dots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-connect-the-dots/</guid>
      <description>Didi and Friends, popular kids animation with over 1 billion views on Youtube is here with a brand new game.
Connect the dots to reveal interesting objects, animals and characters.
Teach your kids and toddlers to connect the dots, and get rewarded with happy smiles from Didi the Chicken and his friends!
Features: Fun and vibrant theme, guaranteed to excite kids, preschoolers and toddlers. Simple gameplay suitable for kids Fullscreen mode Learn everyday objects, animals, environmental elements and above all, the brand new set of Didi and Friends characters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kuu Kuu Harajuku Diy Kawaii Stickers</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/kuu-kuu-harajuku-diy-kawaii-stickers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/kuu-kuu-harajuku-diy-kawaii-stickers/</guid>
      <description>Tick tock, time to rock! Kuu Kuu Harajuku is an animation brand created by Grammy winner Gwen Stefani. They&amp;rsquo;re back with a game for tween and teen girls!
Create your own sticker book with characters from the hit TV series. Drag and drop stickers that represent G, Love, Angel, Music and Baby into beautiful backgrounds of Harajuku City. Start with the Clubhouse, and move your way to decorate the studio, parks, and the Harajuku City skyline!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oddbods Ice Cream Fight</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-ice-cream-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-ice-cream-fight/</guid>
      <description>The mischievous Oddbods are at it again! Throw delicious ice cream at them, before they throw back!
This ice cream fight is getting wild! The Oddbods can duck, run left and right, and also appear out of nowhere to attack you.
Features: battle against different Oddbods such as Fuse, Bubbles, Pogo, Zee, Slick, Jeff and Newt. boss levels with Fuse. He&amp;rsquo;s a tough one to crack! fun theme song increasingly difficult challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penalty Kick</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/penalty-kick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/penalty-kick/</guid>
      <description>The pitch is set. The stadium is packed full. The fans are chanting. The spotlight is on you.
Swipe the ball towards the goal. Avoid goalies and defenders.
How many goals can you score past the goalkeeper?
Features: fun, arcade style theme fast paced action goalie has varying degrees of intelligence unlock different balls based on high score </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flossy and Jim Whale Tickler</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flossy-and-jim-whale-tickler/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flossy-and-jim-whale-tickler/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a cute whale that you can tickle all day long.
Tickle and rub the whale until the bar fills up. Watch as you receive a special response from the whale.
With this game, spread the positivity and feel-good vibe with your audience.
Features: Random emotions and quotes each time Extremely cute design This whale has tusk! It&amp;rsquo;s a Narwhal! Unlimited gameplay and tickles Fun and chill music </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
