<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Flappy Bird on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/flappy-bird/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Flappy Bird on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:01 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/flappy-bird/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chroma Challenge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chroma-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chroma-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Tap to get the ball past the color switching gates.
The gates will only allow the ball with the matching color to pass.
Don&amp;rsquo;t touch the obstacles! You&amp;rsquo;ll explode.
The obstacles are tricky, so time your jumps.
Features: Extremely addictive and challenging gameplay Easy to learn, hard to master. If you can collect more than 3 stars, you&amp;rsquo;re pretty good! Zen theme for focus Fans of color switch type mechanics will appreciate this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Ball Dunkin</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/city-ball-dunkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/city-ball-dunkin/</guid>
      <description>Dunk the basketball into each hoop.
Time your dunks well. Make sure you don&amp;rsquo;t hit the ceiling, or fall to the group.
Collect points to unlock different cool balls from the store.
Beware, the challenges get more difficult over time!
Make your way past tricky hoops that move in weird ways.
How high can you score?
Features: A store to unlock different balls. Really cool ones. Fun theme Day and night transition Increasingly challenging gameplay </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jumping Burger</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jumping-burger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jumping-burger/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re a sliding burger with jumping ability.
Avoid obstacles such as ketchup bottles, birds and tiny mice as you slide forward, while collecting ingredients to unlock the perfect burger.
Ingredients include lettuce, tomato, cheese, burger patties, mushroom and salmon fillets.
Grab Chillis to be come temporarily invincible.
How far can you go?
Features: Cute restaurant diner setting Easy to play, hard to master. This game is very challenging. A shop to unlock your burgers </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
