<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Simulation on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/simulation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Simulation on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/simulation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alpha Space Invasion</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/alpha-space-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:58 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/alpha-space-invasion/</guid>
      <description>Alpha sector is under invasion. Young pilot, your task is simple. Warp into the sector, and destroy enemy spacecraft before they destroy you.
Avoid the asteroids and keep your shields high. Rake up as many hits as you can!
Features: Interactive tutorial Simple controls (keyboard on desktop, touch controls on mobile) Endless gameplay Fans of sci-fi movies such as Star Wars, Star Trek, Battlestar Galactica and Guardians of the Galaxy will - love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bomb the Bridge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bomb-the-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:51:50 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bomb-the-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Plant C4 bombs anywhere on the bridge.
Wait for enemy troops to cross, then detonate them.
Blow up 100% of the bridge and eliminate all troops to score 3 stars.
Features: Realistic physics Addictive theme Challenging levels Blow up armies, military trucks and tanks! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Bottle Shooter</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/3d-bottle-shoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/3d-bottle-shoot/</guid>
      <description>Aim and shoot glass bottles. It&amp;rsquo;s so simple, yet so addictive.
Listen to the harmonic sounds of glass shattering amidst the peaceful countryside.
Aim for 3 stars in each level.
Features: Over 30 challenging levels Serene and peaceful countryside vibe Simple controls for the casual user Beautiful, low-poly gun, countryside, trees and mountains. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pro Bowling 3D</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pro-bowling-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pro-bowling-3d/</guid>
      <description>Position the bowling ball. Then, flick or trace a curve to roll the ball.
How many strikes can you accumulate? Are you the bowling king?
Features: Beautiful bowling arcade. Intuitive tap-and-swipe control. Gorgeous balls. Bowl like a pro. Light background noise for ambience effect. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classic Pinball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/classic-pinball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/classic-pinball/</guid>
      <description>Move your paddle to hit the steel ball. Watch as the ball bounces around the arcade machine, raking up points for you.
You only have three balls. Make them count!
Features: Interactive tutorial Easy to learn, hard to master Classic theme Pumping background music and sound effects </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Construct a Bridge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/construct-a-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/construct-a-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Hello Engineer! Build a bridge that does not collapse.
Connect joints with lines, to create your engineering marvel.
Then, test your bridge with real trucks passing over.
Will your bridge stand the test?
Your construction is limited by the amount of funds you have, so build your bridge wisely!
Features: Fun theme suitable for everyone Grid system enabled for easier construction Ability to edit your bridge anytime via Undo command Ability to delete portions of your bridge via the Delete command </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Badminton</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/power-badminton/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/power-badminton/</guid>
      <description>Play badminton against clever opponents. Hit short, hit long and smash your way to victory in this badminton league!
Activate power ups to give you an unfair advantage over your opponent. Beware, your opponent has powerups too!
Use your racquet to make cool net shots. Bait them to do a high ball and finish with a smash! Or, play long rallies until your opponent gives up.
Not sure how to play?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini Golf Adventure</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mini-golf-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mini-golf-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Put the ball into the hole. Use the shortest amount of putts to score maximum stars.
Collect gems to increase your score! Embark on this fun golfing adventure, as your discover new objects and power-ups to help you win.
Features: Discover new elements in this golf paradise, such as the magnet, teleportation stations, windmills, wind accelerators, and yes, a mole! Who&amp;rsquo;s the mole? Interactive tutorial to start putting away Over 24 levels and more to come Fun family oriented theme, suitable for all ages </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ski Hero</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ski-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ski-hero/</guid>
      <description>Ski down the mountain, while avoiding the obstacles. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash!
Features: Interactive tutorial. Anyone can play this game! Family friendly theme, suitable for all ages. Beautiful winter christmas landscape. Collect banners to earn extra points. Fans of winter skifree xmas will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways to Die 3 World Tour</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-3-world-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-3-world-tour/</guid>
      <description>Play mini games featuring the characters from Dumb Ways to Die.
Dumb Ways to Die is a worldwide brand with over 300 million downloads on Apple App Store and Google Play combined.
Test your reflexes in this challenging series of mini games, where a milisecond can make the difference between winning and losing.
Score coins for each challenge, and use the to repair the once great town of Dumbville.
Features: Extremely challenging levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Running</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/banana-running/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/banana-running/</guid>
      <description>Play as Mr. Nanners, the funniest banana in town with a unique voice.
Unfortunately, Mrs. Nanners is missing, and it&amp;rsquo;s your job to find her in this endless runner.
Run along the city streets in your quest to find Mrs. Nanners. Slide left, right, and under obstacles while collecting Mrs Nanners dolls.
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to collect Banana Balls, and use them to upgrade your gear.
Features: Funny banana theme. Funny banana jokes with voiceover dialogues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penalty Kick</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/penalty-kick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/penalty-kick/</guid>
      <description>The pitch is set. The stadium is packed full. The fans are chanting. The spotlight is on you.
Swipe the ball towards the goal. Avoid goalies and defenders.
How many goals can you score past the goalkeeper?
Features: fun, arcade style theme fast paced action goalie has varying degrees of intelligence unlock different balls based on high score </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowboard Hero</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/snowboard-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/snowboard-hero/</guid>
      <description>Snowboard your way down the mountain, while avoiding the obstacles. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash!
Features: Interactive tutorial. Anyone can play this game! Fast, pumping music suitable for X sports. Beautiful winter christmas landscape. Collect banners to earn extra points. Fans of winter skifree xmas or snowboarding will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oddbods Monster Truck Driving</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-monster-truck-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-monster-truck-driving/</guid>
      <description>Control your Oddbods monster truck to reach the flag.
Boost, brake and tilt your truck left/right to navigate the path.
Earn stars by completing the level in record time.
Features: Drive with all 7 Oddbods, including Fuse, Bubbles, Pogo, Zee, Slick, Jeff and Newt. Interactive tutorial Each Oddbod brings something special Use stars to unlock cool vehicles Panning function to plan your routes 20 challenging levels Play repeatedly to get the best high score Upbeat theme Monster Truck and Dirt Bike enthusiasts will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soda Can Knockdown</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soda-can-knockout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soda-can-knockout/</guid>
      <description>Knock down soda cans with balls. Earn 3 stars for completing each level perfectly.
Features: Challenging levels. Encounter different sets with different soda cans Wide landscape (horizontal) design, with fullscreen mode Beautiful 3D carnival theme. Simple and addictive gameplay. Realistic physics This game is great for fans of various beverage brands such as Coca Cola, Pepsi, Red Bull, Monster and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkour Run</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-run/</guid>
      <description>Run along rooftops, jump through windows, hang from ledges, and slide under giant water tanks.
Perform various cool parkour inspired tricks using various vectors and angles, but be careful not to fall!
How far can you go in this endless runner platformer game?
Features: Exciting and fast paced music beats Simple minimalist graphics and urban style Addictive and repetitive gameplay, perfect for high score seekers Desktop and mobile friendly controls </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Lane Racing</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/fast-lane-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/fast-lane-racing/</guid>
      <description>Race against other cars.
Tap to switch lanes. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash into other cars!
Keep on your toes and be prepared to switch lanes quickly in this fastlane game.
Features: Endless gameplay Urban hip hop racing theme Extremely simple controls Simple, linear high score system Fans of racing and driving games will love this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climb the Rocks</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/climb-the-rocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/climb-the-rocks/</guid>
      <description>Wait for the right moment to grab the next rock.
Climb one rock at a time. Avoid unstable rocks, while keeping an eye at the prize.
Can you conquer Mount Narya?
Features: Feeling strong like Rocky? Try other more challenging mountains such as Mount Kibar, Alru, Chota, Ordh and Ucca. Endless gameplay Collect diamonds to unlock new mountain climbing characters. Challenging outdoor environment Great theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
