<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Memory on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/memory/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Memory on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:42:41 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/memory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Seashore Treasure</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/seashore-treasure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:42:41 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/seashore-treasure/</guid>
      <description>Tap an item to pick it up.
Next, pick up a new item that you haven&amp;rsquo;t picked up before.
Continue doing so, until you reach the limit.
Pick up cool items such as sun shades, sea shells, turtles, jellyfish, shorts, sun screen, fish, seahorses and more.
Features: Fun, relaxed beach and sunny theme Measure your cognitive ability and improve your memory 3 different beaches Beautiful sea shore graphics and animation </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scratch and Match Animal</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/scratch-and-match-animal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/scratch-and-match-animal/</guid>
      <description>You have 3 minutes to scratch and match the animal cards. Beat the time and your high score!
Scratch and match beautifully done cards featuring giraffes, elephants, monkeys, tigers, rabbits, cheetahs, polar bears and elephants.
Features: Tutorial Intuitive scratching interface Fun and positive vibe for all ages </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Faces</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/funny-faces/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/funny-faces/</guid>
      <description>Quick, you have 5 seconds to remember the face.
Then, drag and drop face parts into the correct positions.
How fast can you reconstruct each face?
Features: Fun and uplifting theme Increasingly complex faces to reconstruct. It gets challenging! Interactive tutorial Attention to detail. Players get to work on hair, eyes, eyebrows, nose, mouth, glasses, moustache and more. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Chicken Memory Match</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-memory-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-memory-match/</guid>
      <description>From the hit animation series Chuck Chicken, we bring you this exciting memory match game.
Match your favorite Chuck Chicken cards, and do it in the shortest amount of time!
Discover cool cards featuring Chuck, Flick, Wing as well as nemesis cards including Dr Mingo, Dee, Don, Dex.
Features: Interactive tutorial Beautiful Chuck Chicken artwork Simple, crisp gameplay Fast paced action card theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Echo Simon</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/echo-simon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/echo-simon/</guid>
      <description>Simon says &amp;hellip; watch the sequence.
Memorize the sequence, then recreate it.
How high can you score?
Features: interactive tutorial endless gameplay easy to learn, difficult to master be prepared for surprises at later levels </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sort the Trash</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sort-the-trash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sort-the-trash/</guid>
      <description>Protect the environment by learning how to recycle correctly.
Collect items that can be recycled only. Avoid collecting contaminators such as organic waste, disposable coffee cups, plastic straws, ceramic dishware and lithium ion batteries.
Go green and save the Earth. Start becoming eco-friendly today!
Features: Simple elegant design Responsive design Positive them with recycling facts </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
