<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Strategy on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/strategy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Strategy on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/strategy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Protect the Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/protect-the-kingdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:57 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/protect-the-kingdom/</guid>
      <description>Swing high, middle or low to hit the ball. Find your sweet spot and perfect timing. Hit correctly and score a baseball home run!
A simple arcade style baseball game for the fans.
Features: Simple controls to hit high, medium or low Baseball stadium theme, great for brand exposure The game gets more challenging as you score more home runs! Possibility of integrating a high score leaderboard to compete with other players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank Battle</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tank-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tank-battle/</guid>
      <description>Two tanks emerge on the battlefield. Only one will survive. Can you outsmart the other tank?
Collect ammo crates and powerups. Navigate your way to the enemy tank. Fire away!
This is the perfect game to play with friends and family.
Tip: For two player mode, play on the same device (one finger on each side). Enhance social interaction of your audience!
Features: Interactive tutorial to learn the ropes Collect different powerups such as additional health, bubble shields and speed boost Randomly generated battlefield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backgammon</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/backgammon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/backgammon/</guid>
      <description>The objective is to move all your checkers into your home board. Then, bear them off.
Plan your strategy, roll the dice, and leave everything else to luck!
Features: Tutorial included Choose your color Three difficulty modes : easy, medium and hard Fun and casual theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Casual Chess</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/casual-chess/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/casual-chess/</guid>
      <description>Play classic chess against the computer. Plan your moves and execute your strategies to outwit your opponent.
Features 3 different themes Easy, moderate and hard computer AI Play as white or black in this two (2) player game Hints system to guide your moves Fun casual theme, suitable for all ages </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Soccer</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/smart-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/smart-soccer/</guid>
      <description>Soccer has never been this fun. Simply drag, aim and release to shoot the soccer ball.
The first to score 3 goals wins.
Features: Choose your side, from 32 nations. Smart and calculative AI. Be prepared to play hard! Tutorial to learn the ropes Exciting soccer stadium environment, perfect for soccer nuts </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
