<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Animals on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/animals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Animals on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:55:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/animals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Love Bears</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/love-bears/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:55:50 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/love-bears/</guid>
      <description>Draw lines and shapes to bump the bears. Find a way to bring the two love bears together.
Everything you draw turns into real objects!
Collect 3 stars for every level successfully completed.
Features: Beautiful scenery and theme. Addictive tracing gameplay. Draw anything. Over 30 challenging levels per episode. Extremely cute pastel color theme. Cute bears with hats, glasses, panda caps and more! Suitable for all ages. Fans of Love Balls and Happy Glass will enjoy this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cam and Leon Donut Hop</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cam-and-leon-donut-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:55:10 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cam-and-leon-donut-hop/</guid>
      <description>Brought to you by the creators of a 3D animation, Cam and Leon Donut Hop features 2 funny and cute characters, hopping their way around the park.
Hop in and out of donuts, but don&amp;rsquo;t hit the obstacles!
Features Interactive tutorial Easy to play, hard to master Increasingly challenging obstacles Unlock different characters as you progress. Gain access to Leon, Ladybird, Ice Cube and Pepper Shaker! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Guess What</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:54:22 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</guid>
      <description>Didi and Friends, popular kids animation with over 1 billion views on Youtube is here with a brand new game.
Guess the hidden character, then drag and drop the matching picture to reveal it.
Teach your kids and toddlers to spot patterns, and get rewarded with happy smiles from Didi the Chicken and his friends!
Features: Fun and vibrant theme, guaranteed to excite kids, preschoolers and toddlers. Simple gameplay suitable for kids Fullscreen mode Learn everyday objects, animals, environmental elements and above all, the brand new set of Didi and Friends characters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:53:32 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Showcase your kids creativity via this coloring book, featuring Didi and Friends.
A fun, all-digital and reusable coloring book built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Multiple Didi &amp;amp; Friends themed templates to start with Choose different brush sizes and colours Full screen mode for immersive experience Did something wrong? Undo your colors via an eraser Save your works and print them. This feature is great for classrooms Color interesting characters from the Didi &amp;amp; Friends universe, including Didi, Nana, Jojo, Tatak, Bingo and Pak Atan, Positive theme, to foster good vibes via colouring </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways to Die 2 the Games</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:50:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</guid>
      <description>Dumb Ways to Die is back with a bigger and better sequel to the original.
In Dumb Ways To Die 2 - The Games, now you can access various maps and locations to try out even more fun and dangerous challenges.
Collect tokens to unlock different aspects of the city, while complete mini challenges perfectly (or imperfectly, depending on how you play). Score points to keep your ranking high.
Play in cool locations such as Adrenaland, Drown Town, Dumbest of the Dumb, and Freezerville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Hunt</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oil-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:48:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oil-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Stretch out a pipe in order to strike oil.
Hit it big as you guide oil-hungry heroes and monsters in a mystical wasteland! Aim for the highest score, and unlock funny characters!
Explore different lands - from long stretching savannas, to green hills, sandy beaches and dark marshes - you’ll be surprised at all the places you’ll find where you can just stick a pipe and watch as tons of fantastic tasty dark stuff spill out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinosaur Run</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dinosaur-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:46:46 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dinosaur-run/</guid>
      <description>Play a cute and lovable T-Rex running across a desert.
Time your dino jumps to avoid the different obstacles.
How high can you score?
Features: Cool pixel artwork with T Rex dinosaur. Classic grayscale theme set in prehistoric era. Jump over a variety of plants and cactus. Easy to play, hard to master. The background accelerates and decelerates occasionally, to keep you on your toes. Responsive design with fullscreen capability Works great on Chrome and any modern HTML5 browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seashore Treasure</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/seashore-treasure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:42:41 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/seashore-treasure/</guid>
      <description>Tap an item to pick it up.
Next, pick up a new item that you haven&amp;rsquo;t picked up before.
Continue doing so, until you reach the limit.
Pick up cool items such as sun shades, sea shells, turtles, jellyfish, shorts, sun screen, fish, seahorses and more.
Features: Fun, relaxed beach and sunny theme Measure your cognitive ability and improve your memory 3 different beaches Beautiful sea shore graphics and animation </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duck Carnival Shoot</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/duck-carnival-shoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/duck-carnival-shoot/</guid>
      <description>Take aim and shoot the ducks, before the time runs out!
Earn coins to upgrade your accuracy.
Complete mini missions to earn more coins.
Features: Cute ducks with funny outfits Fun and challenging gameplay. These ducks will surprise you. Interactive tutorial Play interesting mini missions. Gun down Mafia Duck Boss, Hunt the Police, and shoot all Ducks in Business Suits! Disclaimer: No real ducks are harmed in the production of this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flip Jump</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flip-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flip-jump/</guid>
      <description>Tap, hold and release to jump.
Jump from one platform to the next.
How far can you jump?
Features: Extremely cute and positive jumper game theme, great for brands Simple, 1 touch gameplay Unlock more characters by reaching certain milestones Beautiful 3d artwork Fans of Tiao Yi Tiao and Bottle Flip will love this jumper game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese New Year Mahjong</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cny-mahjong/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cny-mahjong/</guid>
      <description>Match chinese mahjong tiles to complete the levels.
Features: beautiful chinese inspired art interactive tutorial extremely simple and addictive gameplay easy to start, hard to master fun chinese / asian theme, coupled with mahjong matching elements power ups to reward the user, such as auto solve bonuses </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scratch and Match Animal</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/scratch-and-match-animal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/scratch-and-match-animal/</guid>
      <description>You have 3 minutes to scratch and match the animal cards. Beat the time and your high score!
Scratch and match beautifully done cards featuring giraffes, elephants, monkeys, tigers, rabbits, cheetahs, polar bears and elephants.
Features: Tutorial Intuitive scratching interface Fun and positive vibe for all ages </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Soccer</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-soccer/</guid>
      <description>Aim and shoot the ball into the goal. Collect the starfish to gain maximum score.
With golden sand, coconut trees, sand castles, crabs, and a gorgeous sunshine, what more do you need?
Features: Interactive tutorial Over 20 challenging levels. Put your thinking cap on. Fun beach theme and music Interact with challenging obstacles such as crabs, sandcastles, and more. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Piggy Piggy Farm</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-farm/</guid>
      <description>Mango Piggy Piggy is HUNGRY. He comes across a mango farm. The mangoes look sweet and juicy, just like how he likes it.
Drag and aim to launch Mango Piggy Piggy towards the mangos. Eat them all to earn 3 stars!
Features: Fun, positive and ridiculously cute character. MPP bounces around and squeals almost like a soft toy. Innovative touch and drag mechanic Over 30 levels Unlock a hidden level Don&amp;rsquo;t eat the red mango!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Horace vs Cheese</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/horace-vs-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/horace-vs-cheese/</guid>
      <description>Pull and launch Horace the Hamster into the cheese. Eat them all to earn 3 stars.
Then, land safely into the cheese house.
From the creators of Flossy and Jim, we bring you a new brand called Horace and co.
Features: Fun, positive and ridiculously cute character. Horace bounces around and squeals almost like a soft toy. Innovative touch and drag mechanic Over 30 levels Unlock a hidden level Don&amp;rsquo;t eat the blue cheese!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Chicken Memory Match</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-memory-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-memory-match/</guid>
      <description>From the hit animation series Chuck Chicken, we bring you this exciting memory match game.
Match your favorite Chuck Chicken cards, and do it in the shortest amount of time!
Discover cool cards featuring Chuck, Flick, Wing as well as nemesis cards including Dr Mingo, Dee, Don, Dex.
Features: Interactive tutorial Beautiful Chuck Chicken artwork Simple, crisp gameplay Fast paced action card theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-and-friends-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-and-friends-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Express your creativity via this coloring book.
We&amp;rsquo;re proud to present Arty Mouse &amp;amp; Friends Coloring Book, a digital coloring book built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Multiple templates to start with Choose different brush sizes and colours Eraser mode Save your works (useful if you&amp;rsquo;d like to print the pictures) Color interesting characters from the Arty Mouse universe, including Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, and Spiro the snail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Connect the Dots</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-connect-the-dots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-connect-the-dots/</guid>
      <description>Didi and Friends, popular kids animation with over 1 billion views on Youtube is here with a brand new game.
Connect the dots to reveal interesting objects, animals and characters.
Teach your kids and toddlers to connect the dots, and get rewarded with happy smiles from Didi the Chicken and his friends!
Features: Fun and vibrant theme, guaranteed to excite kids, preschoolers and toddlers. Simple gameplay suitable for kids Fullscreen mode Learn everyday objects, animals, environmental elements and above all, the brand new set of Didi and Friends characters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Piggy Piggy Hero</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-hero/</guid>
      <description>Mango Piggy Piggy is back with a brand new series and new episodes.
In his hero edition, control different superhero piggies, as you attempt to defend your town against the invasion of enemy robots.
Whats New:
Activate Panther Piggy to dash through obstacles. Activate Hulk Piggy to create a memorable, powerful smash attack. Activate Marvel Piggy to deal widespread damage to enemies. Activate Antman Piggy to suddenly become huge and inflict crazy damage Activate Spider Piggy to pull targets towards it Launch your hero piggy against the enemy, in Angry Birds fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boj Giggly Park Adventure</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-giggly-park-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-giggly-park-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Explore Giggly Park with Boj and friends.
Boj is an award winning kids television series worldwide.
Do wonderful things such as ride a bike, climb the tree, fly a kite, dig underground for treasures, ride the swing, control a helicopter remotely and more.
Interact with various characters from the Boj universe, such as Mimi, Pops, Mr Cloppity, Denzil, Mia Twitch and more.
This is a new and innovative gameplay to encourage users to explore their curiosity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Chicken Magic Egg</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-magic-egg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-magic-egg/</guid>
      <description>Chuck Chicken is on a mission. Defeat his nemesis Dee, Don, Dex, Dr Mingo and more in this exciting and fast-paced puzzle platformer game.
Chuck Chicken is a worldwide kids and tweens animation brand with over 2 billion views.
In this game, throw your egg, and watch as it bounces from wall to wall, defeating your opponents.
Collect magic eggs to transform Chuck into his alter ego super hero. For example,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spider Solitaire</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/spider-solitaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/spider-solitaire/</guid>
      <description>Spider themed solitaire game. You&amp;rsquo;ll definitely get addicted
Features: stunning spider theme tutorial feeling stuck? Use our hints system hours of repetitive gameplay. Each deck is randomly generated. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Volley</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-volley/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-volley/</guid>
      <description>Move your turtle to hit the ball.
Keep the ball from falling into your own court.
First to score 10 wins!
Features: Beautiful and minimalist beach theme Really cute sea turtles Challenging AI </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flossy and Jim Whale Tickler</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flossy-and-jim-whale-tickler/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flossy-and-jim-whale-tickler/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a cute whale that you can tickle all day long.
Tickle and rub the whale until the bar fills up. Watch as you receive a special response from the whale.
With this game, spread the positivity and feel-good vibe with your audience.
Features: Random emotions and quotes each time Extremely cute design This whale has tusk! It&amp;rsquo;s a Narwhal! Unlimited gameplay and tickles Fun and chill music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wheels on the Bus Sing Along</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/wheels-on-the-bus-sing-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/wheels-on-the-bus-sing-along/</guid>
      <description>The wheels on the bus go round and round in this kids activity game. Ride the bus with fellow animals such as Tiger the driver, Elephant, Rabbit, Monkey and Fox.
Listen to the sweet voice singing the song. Allow your kids to work on discovery activities such as tapping on the animals, activating the bus lights, making the bird sing, honking the bus and more.
Features: real vocals by voice actors cute animal characters touch-based activities for kids to keep busy This game is great for parents teaching kids sing-along songs with activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teddy Bubble Rescue</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/teddy-bubble-rescue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/teddy-bubble-rescue/</guid>
      <description>Big Teddy needs your help! Pop the objects to rescue the mini teddy bears.
Place your shooter aim carefully to clear the maximum amount of objects in each level.
Features: Interactive tutorial 20 challenging levels Fun theme Solve sets using a variety of tactics. Use clever theory of angles, target higher objects and other tactics to solve each level </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
