<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Clicker on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/clicker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Clicker on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:50:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/clicker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways to Die 2 the Games</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:50:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</guid>
      <description>Dumb Ways to Die is back with a bigger and better sequel to the original.
In Dumb Ways To Die 2 - The Games, now you can access various maps and locations to try out even more fun and dangerous challenges.
Collect tokens to unlock different aspects of the city, while complete mini challenges perfectly (or imperfectly, depending on how you play). Score points to keep your ranking high.
Play in cool locations such as Adrenaland, Drown Town, Dumbest of the Dumb, and Freezerville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitchie Clicker</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/twitchie-clicker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/twitchie-clicker/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Twitchie Clicker! If you&amp;rsquo;ve got twitchy fingers, this is the game for you.
Nicknamed H0lyThund3rDude with a cool beanie hat, you have your work cut out for you. Build your streaming empire from nothing. Earn one gamer view at the time, while generating cash.
Upgrade your fame factors to generate more views per second. Unlock cool videos that you can upload to your fans.
Grow your subscriber base to millions of passionate gamers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Survival</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/zombie-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/zombie-survival/</guid>
      <description>A strange virus outbreak turned your friends into zombies. Armed with a basic pistol, make your way through hordes of zombies.
How many days can you survive, before you become one of them?
Features: 3D like isometric graphics Collect coins with each zombie kill Multiple weapons to purchase. Try the machine gun, shotgun, rifle and laser gun Fun stats to review after each day 3 different gameplay modes: Survival, Hard Point and Nuke Tutorial to learn the ropes Yes, you can blow up barrels to burn the zombies </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
