<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shooting on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/shooting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shooting on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:30 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/shooting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3D Bottle Shooter</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/3d-bottle-shoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/3d-bottle-shoot/</guid>
      <description>Aim and shoot glass bottles. It&amp;rsquo;s so simple, yet so addictive.
Listen to the harmonic sounds of glass shattering amidst the peaceful countryside.
Aim for 3 stars in each level.
Features: Over 30 challenging levels Serene and peaceful countryside vibe Simple controls for the casual user Beautiful, low-poly gun, countryside, trees and mountains. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duck Carnival Shoot</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/duck-carnival-shoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/duck-carnival-shoot/</guid>
      <description>Take aim and shoot the ducks, before the time runs out!
Earn coins to upgrade your accuracy.
Complete mini missions to earn more coins.
Features: Cute ducks with funny outfits Fun and challenging gameplay. These ducks will surprise you. Interactive tutorial Play interesting mini missions. Gun down Mafia Duck Boss, Hunt the Police, and shoot all Ducks in Business Suits! Disclaimer: No real ducks are harmed in the production of this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Triangle Wars</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/triangle-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/triangle-wars/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re a lone spaceship lost in space. Attack other spaceships to survive in the vastness of space. Aim for the highest score.
Features: Interactive tutorial to ease learning curve Endless gameplay Space like physics, for fans of Space Invaders 90s retro games Pick up a variety of powerups such as bombs, splash bullets and extra lives Battle intelligent boss ships Energetic theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Survival</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/zombie-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/zombie-survival/</guid>
      <description>A strange virus outbreak turned your friends into zombies. Armed with a basic pistol, make your way through hordes of zombies.
How many days can you survive, before you become one of them?
Features: 3D like isometric graphics Collect coins with each zombie kill Multiple weapons to purchase. Try the machine gun, shotgun, rifle and laser gun Fun stats to review after each day 3 different gameplay modes: Survival, Hard Point and Nuke Tutorial to learn the ropes Yes, you can blow up barrels to burn the zombies </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skeleton Defense</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/skeleton-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/skeleton-defense/</guid>
      <description>Soldier! You&amp;rsquo;re the last hope for humanity. It&amp;rsquo;s up to you to stop the waves of undead skeletons.
Features: Interactive tutorial to learn the ropes Scary skeleton theme 7 different weapons. Use rifles, grenades, rockets, molotov cocktails and other impressive weapons to stop these skeletons 5 different skeleton types Unlimited gameplay A shop to upgrade and unlock new weapons </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soda Can Knockdown</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soda-can-knockout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soda-can-knockout/</guid>
      <description>Knock down soda cans with balls. Earn 3 stars for completing each level perfectly.
Features: Challenging levels. Encounter different sets with different soda cans Wide landscape (horizontal) design, with fullscreen mode Beautiful 3D carnival theme. Simple and addictive gameplay. Realistic physics This game is great for fans of various beverage brands such as Coca Cola, Pepsi, Red Bull, Monster and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commando Boat</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/commando-boat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/commando-boat/</guid>
      <description>Commando! Drive your speed boat behind enemy lines.
Avoid incoming obstacles such as river mines, tree logs, rocks and other boats.
Shoot and destroy obstacles with bullets.
This is a new and reimagined casual shoot em up game featuring a marine theme.
Features: Collect coins to purchase cool boat models such water raft, speed boat, hovercrafts, and more. Collect powerups including coin magnets, bullets and bubble shields Take ramp to get a cool boost forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knife Master</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/knife-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/knife-master/</guid>
      <description>Throw the knife at the target board.
Score double points for hitting the bullsye.
Sounds easy? As you progress further, you&amp;rsquo;ll need every single ounce of skill and finesse in knife throwing.
Not to mention, you&amp;rsquo;ll need impeccable timing too.
One miss of the knife, and you&amp;rsquo;re out!
Similar to darts, fans of knife throwing and all throwing sports will love this game.
Features: Fast paced knife throwing theme Minimalist look and feel Every challenge is designed exactly the same for each player.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
