<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Preschool on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/preschool/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Preschool on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:53:32 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/preschool/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:53:32 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Showcase your kids creativity via this coloring book, featuring Didi and Friends.
A fun, all-digital and reusable coloring book built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Multiple Didi &amp;amp; Friends themed templates to start with Choose different brush sizes and colours Full screen mode for immersive experience Did something wrong? Undo your colors via an eraser Save your works and print them. This feature is great for classrooms Color interesting characters from the Didi &amp;amp; Friends universe, including Didi, Nana, Jojo, Tatak, Bingo and Pak Atan, Positive theme, to foster good vibes via colouring </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways Jr Zanys Hospital</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-jr-zanys-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-jr-zanys-hospital/</guid>
      <description>From the creators of Dumb Ways to Die, the hit brand with over 300 million downloads total on Google Play and Apple App Store - we present to you an exciting spin-off brand called Dumb Ways JR Zany&amp;rsquo;s Hospital.
Visit Dumb Ways Hospital with Doctor Zany. Explore three main areas of play: a waiting room full of surprises to discover, a check-up room where children can play the role of doctor, and an ambulance that visits the hospital featuring fun guest appearances from the original Dumb Ways cast!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Build Me</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-build-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-build-me/</guid>
      <description>Remember the parts, then drag and drop the parts to form a complete character.
We&amp;rsquo;re proud to present Arty Mouse - Build Me, a branded game built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Interactive tutorial Fun theme for kids of all ages - helps to train cognitive abilities and memory Work with a variety of interesting characters from the Arty Mouse universe, including Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, and Spiro the snail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Sticker Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-sticker-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-sticker-book/</guid>
      <description>Now, your kids can express themselves through art.
Place your favourite Arty Mouse stickers onto the board, decorate them as you wish.
Drag and drop, resize and reposition them to your hearts content. Need to erase a sticker? No problem.
Create millions of sticker combinations using different Arty Mouse characters, objects and backgrounds. Work with Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, Spiro the snail, and more characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-and-friends-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-and-friends-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Express your creativity via this coloring book.
We&amp;rsquo;re proud to present Arty Mouse &amp;amp; Friends Coloring Book, a digital coloring book built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Multiple templates to start with Choose different brush sizes and colours Eraser mode Save your works (useful if you&amp;rsquo;d like to print the pictures) Color interesting characters from the Arty Mouse universe, including Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, and Spiro the snail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Connect the Dots</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-connect-the-dots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-connect-the-dots/</guid>
      <description>Didi and Friends, popular kids animation with over 1 billion views on Youtube is here with a brand new game.
Connect the dots to reveal interesting objects, animals and characters.
Teach your kids and toddlers to connect the dots, and get rewarded with happy smiles from Didi the Chicken and his friends!
Features: Fun and vibrant theme, guaranteed to excite kids, preschoolers and toddlers. Simple gameplay suitable for kids Fullscreen mode Learn everyday objects, animals, environmental elements and above all, the brand new set of Didi and Friends characters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boj Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Showcase your creativity via this coloring book, featuring Boj and friends. A fun, all-digital and reusable coloring book built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Multiple Boj themed templates to start with Choose different brush sizes and colours Did something wrong? Undo your colors via an eraser Save your works and print them. This feature is great for classrooms Color interesting characters from the Boj universe, including Boj the Bilby himself, Mimi, Pops, Denzil, Mr Cloppity, Mia Twitch, Julie Twitch and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boj Giggly Park Adventure</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-giggly-park-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-giggly-park-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Explore Giggly Park with Boj and friends.
Boj is an award winning kids television series worldwide.
Do wonderful things such as ride a bike, climb the tree, fly a kite, dig underground for treasures, ride the swing, control a helicopter remotely and more.
Interact with various characters from the Boj universe, such as Mimi, Pops, Mr Cloppity, Denzil, Mia Twitch and more.
This is a new and innovative gameplay to encourage users to explore their curiosity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wheels on the Bus Sing Along</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/wheels-on-the-bus-sing-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/wheels-on-the-bus-sing-along/</guid>
      <description>The wheels on the bus go round and round in this kids activity game. Ride the bus with fellow animals such as Tiger the driver, Elephant, Rabbit, Monkey and Fox.
Listen to the sweet voice singing the song. Allow your kids to work on discovery activities such as tapping on the animals, activating the bus lights, making the bird sing, honking the bus and more.
Features: real vocals by voice actors cute animal characters touch-based activities for kids to keep busy This game is great for parents teaching kids sing-along songs with activities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
