<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Management on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Management on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Protect the Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/protect-the-kingdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:57 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/protect-the-kingdom/</guid>
      <description>Swing high, middle or low to hit the ball. Find your sweet spot and perfect timing. Hit correctly and score a baseball home run!
A simple arcade style baseball game for the fans.
Features: Simple controls to hit high, medium or low Baseball stadium theme, great for brand exposure The game gets more challenging as you score more home runs! Possibility of integrating a high score leaderboard to compete with other players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitchie Clicker</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/twitchie-clicker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/twitchie-clicker/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Twitchie Clicker! If you&amp;rsquo;ve got twitchy fingers, this is the game for you.
Nicknamed H0lyThund3rDude with a cool beanie hat, you have your work cut out for you. Build your streaming empire from nothing. Earn one gamer view at the time, while generating cash.
Upgrade your fame factors to generate more views per second. Unlock cool videos that you can upload to your fans.
Grow your subscriber base to millions of passionate gamers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways Jr Zanys Hospital</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-jr-zanys-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-jr-zanys-hospital/</guid>
      <description>From the creators of Dumb Ways to Die, the hit brand with over 300 million downloads total on Google Play and Apple App Store - we present to you an exciting spin-off brand called Dumb Ways JR Zany&amp;rsquo;s Hospital.
Visit Dumb Ways Hospital with Doctor Zany. Explore three main areas of play: a waiting room full of surprises to discover, a check-up room where children can play the role of doctor, and an ambulance that visits the hospital featuring fun guest appearances from the original Dumb Ways cast!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
