<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Word on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/word/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Word on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/word/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crossword Casual</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/crossword-casual/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/crossword-casual/</guid>
      <description>Solve everyday crossword puzzles involving various themes such as cities, objects, food, and buildings.
Features: Full screen mode Easy to use crossword puzzle. Regardless of device, play the same crossword puzzle as everybody else Easy selection of puzzle grid to insert answers Virtual keyboard for mobile and tablet users. Easily enter your answers to solve the puzzles Random puzzles generated from a pool of questions and answers Relaxing theme, suitable for everyone Note: if you&amp;rsquo;d like different themes, please contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typing Fighter</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/typing-fighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/typing-fighter/</guid>
      <description>Type fast, type accurate and fight hard in this innovative street fighter style typing game.
Charge up your typing and deliver killer power moves.
Get inspired by motivational phrases and quotes while you type.
Fight against a variety of opponents.
Features: Beautifully designed street fight urban setting Fluid character animations Over 200 motivational quotes and phrases to keep you going </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Crossword</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/holiday-crossword/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/holiday-crossword/</guid>
      <description>Solve holiday themed crossword puzzles involving various topics such as cities, food, celebrations and gift ideas.
Features: Full screen mode Easy to use cross word puzzle. Regardless of device, play the same crossword puzzle as everybody else Easy selection of puzzle grid to insert answers Virtual keyboard for mobile and tablet users. Easily enter your answers to solve the puzzles Random puzzles generated from a pool of questions and answers Relaxing theme, suitable for everyone Note: if you&amp;rsquo;d like different themes and questions, please contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
