<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Game Catalog on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Game Catalog on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 17:18:15 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alpha Space Invasion</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/alpha-space-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:58 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/alpha-space-invasion/</guid>
      <description>Alpha sector is under invasion. Young pilot, your task is simple. Warp into the sector, and destroy enemy spacecraft before they destroy you.
Avoid the asteroids and keep your shields high. Rake up as many hits as you can!
Features: Interactive tutorial Simple controls (keyboard on desktop, touch controls on mobile) Endless gameplay Fans of sci-fi movies such as Star Wars, Star Trek, Battlestar Galactica and Guardians of the Galaxy will - love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protect the Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/protect-the-kingdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:57 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/protect-the-kingdom/</guid>
      <description>Swing high, middle or low to hit the ball. Find your sweet spot and perfect timing. Hit correctly and score a baseball home run!
A simple arcade style baseball game for the fans.
Features: Simple controls to hit high, medium or low Baseball stadium theme, great for brand exposure The game gets more challenging as you score more home runs! Possibility of integrating a high score leaderboard to compete with other players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect the Roads</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/connect-the-roads/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:58:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/connect-the-roads/</guid>
      <description>Your car needs to get to work! Move the road tiles to complete the road.
Can you get three stars for each level?
Features: Simple draggable tiles Fun city theme Turn grid on or off 24 challenging levels guaranteed to twist your brain Fans of pipe games and picture sliders will love this game. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bobblehead Soccer Royale</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bobblehead-soccer-royale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:56:54 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bobblehead-soccer-royale/</guid>
      <description>Move your bobblehead soccer stars around the field. Kick the goals into the opponent&amp;rsquo;s goal.
Collect the powerups to gain an edge over your opponents.
Features: Mad physics that trumps realism Fun and vibrant soccer atmosphere Funny caricature expressions Challenge over 20+ top soccer players in the world Increasingly challenging levels. Get to Level 3 and the game really heats up. Forget FIFA World Cup, fans of puppet soccer fans will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Bears</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/love-bears/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:55:50 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/love-bears/</guid>
      <description>Draw lines and shapes to bump the bears. Find a way to bring the two love bears together.
Everything you draw turns into real objects!
Collect 3 stars for every level successfully completed.
Features: Beautiful scenery and theme. Addictive tracing gameplay. Draw anything. Over 30 challenging levels per episode. Extremely cute pastel color theme. Cute bears with hats, glasses, panda caps and more! Suitable for all ages. Fans of Love Balls and Happy Glass will enjoy this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cam and Leon Donut Hop</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cam-and-leon-donut-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:55:10 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cam-and-leon-donut-hop/</guid>
      <description>Brought to you by the creators of a 3D animation, Cam and Leon Donut Hop features 2 funny and cute characters, hopping their way around the park.
Hop in and out of donuts, but don&amp;rsquo;t hit the obstacles!
Features Interactive tutorial Easy to play, hard to master Increasingly challenging obstacles Unlock different characters as you progress. Gain access to Leon, Ladybird, Ice Cube and Pepper Shaker! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Guess What</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:54:22 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</guid>
      <description>Didi and Friends, popular kids animation with over 1 billion views on Youtube is here with a brand new game.
Guess the hidden character, then drag and drop the matching picture to reveal it.
Teach your kids and toddlers to spot patterns, and get rewarded with happy smiles from Didi the Chicken and his friends!
Features: Fun and vibrant theme, guaranteed to excite kids, preschoolers and toddlers. Simple gameplay suitable for kids Fullscreen mode Learn everyday objects, animals, environmental elements and above all, the brand new set of Didi and Friends characters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:53:32 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Showcase your kids creativity via this coloring book, featuring Didi and Friends.
A fun, all-digital and reusable coloring book built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Multiple Didi &amp;amp; Friends themed templates to start with Choose different brush sizes and colours Full screen mode for immersive experience Did something wrong? Undo your colors via an eraser Save your works and print them. This feature is great for classrooms Color interesting characters from the Didi &amp;amp; Friends universe, including Didi, Nana, Jojo, Tatak, Bingo and Pak Atan, Positive theme, to foster good vibes via colouring </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Onet Connect</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/onect-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:52:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/onect-connect/</guid>
      <description>Connect fruit tiles of the same image.
A game of creativity, problem solving and cognitive enhancement.
Use fewer than 3 lines. Only 2 tiles per connection. This is not a match 3 game, but rather a match 2 game that focuses on spatial training and puzzle solving.
Features 3 difficulty levels. Easy, medium and hard Randomized set, every time you play. Ensure unlimited gameplay. Casual theme, suitable for all ages and families Ability to shuffle the set Huge set for long periods of gameplay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bomb the Bridge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bomb-the-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:51:50 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bomb-the-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Plant C4 bombs anywhere on the bridge.
Wait for enemy troops to cross, then detonate them.
Blow up 100% of the bridge and eliminate all troops to score 3 stars.
Features: Realistic physics Addictive theme Challenging levels Blow up armies, military trucks and tanks! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways to Die 2 the Games</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:50:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</guid>
      <description>Dumb Ways to Die is back with a bigger and better sequel to the original.
In Dumb Ways To Die 2 - The Games, now you can access various maps and locations to try out even more fun and dangerous challenges.
Collect tokens to unlock different aspects of the city, while complete mini challenges perfectly (or imperfectly, depending on how you play). Score points to keep your ranking high.
Play in cool locations such as Adrenaland, Drown Town, Dumbest of the Dumb, and Freezerville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Hunt</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oil-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:48:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oil-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Stretch out a pipe in order to strike oil.
Hit it big as you guide oil-hungry heroes and monsters in a mystical wasteland! Aim for the highest score, and unlock funny characters!
Explore different lands - from long stretching savannas, to green hills, sandy beaches and dark marshes - you’ll be surprised at all the places you’ll find where you can just stick a pipe and watch as tons of fantastic tasty dark stuff spill out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drift Boss</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/drift-boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:47:37 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/drift-boss/</guid>
      <description>Drift your car like a boss. Drift left and right with good timing.
Concentrate and anticipate your drifts and skids in tight spots.
How many points can you score?
Features: Great arcade 3d environment Unlock cool vehicles by collecting more points. Unlock trucks, taxis, police cars, ice cream trucks, ambulances, firetrucks and more. Full responsive design Full screen capability Great soundtracknd theme. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinosaur Run</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dinosaur-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:46:46 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dinosaur-run/</guid>
      <description>Play a cute and lovable T-Rex running across a desert.
Time your dino jumps to avoid the different obstacles.
How high can you score?
Features: Cool pixel artwork with T Rex dinosaur. Classic grayscale theme set in prehistoric era. Jump over a variety of plants and cactus. Easy to play, hard to master. The background accelerates and decelerates occasionally, to keep you on your toes. Responsive design with fullscreen capability Works great on Chrome and any modern HTML5 browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kill the Spy</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/kill-the-spy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:45:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/kill-the-spy/</guid>
      <description>Armed with your trusty pistol, it&amp;rsquo;s up to you, Agent 007 to eliminate the enemy spy agents.
Tap on the correct blocks to eliminate the spy agents. Use the least amount of moves to earn more stars.
Do not hard the hostages, or else the mission will fail.
Features: Innovative physics and game mechanics. Aim your spy pistol to split structures into multiple pieces Collect treasures to increase your score Place your shots correctly to earn more stars Spy theme and sound effects Fans of James Bond , Men in Black and spy themed novels will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stupid Zombies</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stupid-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:44:27 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stupid-zombies/</guid>
      <description>One man, one shotgun and a whole lot of zombies. You are humanity&amp;rsquo;s last hope, and it&amp;rsquo;s your job to keep them brainless.
Adjust your shots and angles, and you watch your bullets ricochet from wall to wall, elegantly picking off each zombie&amp;rsquo;s arms and limbs.
Features: 4 giant stages with over 360 challenging levels Exciting zombie theme Simple and innovative ricochet based gameplay. Defeat the stupid zombies with brains and ingenuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seashore Treasure</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/seashore-treasure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:42:41 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/seashore-treasure/</guid>
      <description>Tap an item to pick it up.
Next, pick up a new item that you haven&amp;rsquo;t picked up before.
Continue doing so, until you reach the limit.
Pick up cool items such as sun shades, sea shells, turtles, jellyfish, shorts, sun screen, fish, seahorses and more.
Features: Fun, relaxed beach and sunny theme Measure your cognitive ability and improve your memory 3 different beaches Beautiful sea shore graphics and animation </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Bottle Shooter</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/3d-bottle-shoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/3d-bottle-shoot/</guid>
      <description>Aim and shoot glass bottles. It&amp;rsquo;s so simple, yet so addictive.
Listen to the harmonic sounds of glass shattering amidst the peaceful countryside.
Aim for 3 stars in each level.
Features: Over 30 challenging levels Serene and peaceful countryside vibe Simple controls for the casual user Beautiful, low-poly gun, countryside, trees and mountains. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classic Solitaire</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/classic-solitaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/classic-solitaire/</guid>
      <description>Build suit piles in ascending order, from Ace to King.
Re-arrange face-up cards in descending order and alternating colors.
Features: tutorial beautiful graphics hours of repetitive gameplay relaxed theme and music undo function </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duck Carnival Shoot</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/duck-carnival-shoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/duck-carnival-shoot/</guid>
      <description>Take aim and shoot the ducks, before the time runs out!
Earn coins to upgrade your accuracy.
Complete mini missions to earn more coins.
Features: Cute ducks with funny outfits Fun and challenging gameplay. These ducks will surprise you. Interactive tutorial Play interesting mini missions. Gun down Mafia Duck Boss, Hunt the Police, and shoot all Ducks in Business Suits! Disclaimer: No real ducks are harmed in the production of this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pro Bowling 3D</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pro-bowling-3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pro-bowling-3d/</guid>
      <description>Position the bowling ball. Then, flick or trace a curve to roll the ball.
How many strikes can you accumulate? Are you the bowling king?
Features: Beautiful bowling arcade. Intuitive tap-and-swipe control. Gorgeous balls. Bowl like a pro. Light background noise for ambience effect. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classic Pinball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/classic-pinball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/classic-pinball/</guid>
      <description>Move your paddle to hit the steel ball. Watch as the ball bounces around the arcade machine, raking up points for you.
You only have three balls. Make them count!
Features: Interactive tutorial Easy to learn, hard to master Classic theme Pumping background music and sound effects </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Construct a Bridge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/construct-a-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/construct-a-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Hello Engineer! Build a bridge that does not collapse.
Connect joints with lines, to create your engineering marvel.
Then, test your bridge with real trucks passing over.
Will your bridge stand the test?
Your construction is limited by the amount of funds you have, so build your bridge wisely!
Features: Fun theme suitable for everyone Grid system enabled for easier construction Ability to edit your bridge anytime via Undo command Ability to delete portions of your bridge via the Delete command </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puzzle Slide Travel Edition</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/puzzle-slide-travel-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/puzzle-slide-travel-edition/</guid>
      <description>A picture slide game with a travel theme. Complete the puzzles in the shortest amount of time
Solve puzzles of famous locations such as New York&amp;rsquo;s Manhattan Bridge, The London Eye, Eiffel Tower of Paris, Forbidden City in Beijing, Tokyo Imperial Palace, Pyramids of Egypt, and more.
Features New-age, Instagram design for the millennial generation Easy, medium and hard modes Solve all kinds of puzzles from around the world Simple design to encourage focus Multiple puzzles to try Relaxed environment </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank Battle</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tank-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tank-battle/</guid>
      <description>Two tanks emerge on the battlefield. Only one will survive. Can you outsmart the other tank?
Collect ammo crates and powerups. Navigate your way to the enemy tank. Fire away!
This is the perfect game to play with friends and family.
Tip: For two player mode, play on the same device (one finger on each side). Enhance social interaction of your audience!
Features: Interactive tutorial to learn the ropes Collect different powerups such as additional health, bubble shields and speed boost Randomly generated battlefield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Piggy Piggy vs Bad Veggies</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-vs-bad-veggies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-vs-bad-veggies/</guid>
      <description>Mango Piggy Piggy is back. This time, you&amp;rsquo;re up against Bad Veggies.
Knock out the Boss Veggie, then bounce on as many Bad Veggies as possible.
Collect powerups to extend your streak, while collecting more mango points. Use collected mango points to purchase cool upgrades.
Features: Interactive tutorial Fun Mango Piggy Piggy theme Collect your Slam points to use the Piggy Slam ability Collect cool powerups such as bombs, stomping machines, and yes, rockets!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Badminton</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/power-badminton/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/power-badminton/</guid>
      <description>Play badminton against clever opponents. Hit short, hit long and smash your way to victory in this badminton league!
Activate power ups to give you an unfair advantage over your opponent. Beware, your opponent has powerups too!
Use your racquet to make cool net shots. Bait them to do a high ball and finish with a smash! Or, play long rallies until your opponent gives up.
Not sure how to play?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pro Wrestling Action</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pro-wrestling-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pro-wrestling-action/</guid>
      <description>Get ready to rumble! Punch, kick, and wrestle your way through to be the last man standing.
Knock out your opponents, then throw them out of the ring!
Need to perform a spectacular feat? Climb the ropes, time your jumps and dive on the opponent.
Collect coins to upgrade your favourite wrestler in the shop.
Features: Simple controls to maximize fun. Start kicking and punching right away! Entertaining wrestling theme Clever and not so clever computer opponents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rugby Extreme</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/rugby-extreme-flick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/rugby-extreme-flick/</guid>
      <description>Flick the ball into the goal post. How many goals can you score?
Features: Easy to play, difficult to master Get extra points for scoring in designated target areas Beware of the changing wind speeds at higher levels Flying capemen will try to block your shots Unlock different objects such as beer bottles, watermelon, easter eggs and rockets Fans of flick kick rugby, american football and rugby world cup will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chroma Challenge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chroma-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chroma-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Tap to get the ball past the color switching gates.
The gates will only allow the ball with the matching color to pass.
Don&amp;rsquo;t touch the obstacles! You&amp;rsquo;ll explode.
The obstacles are tricky, so time your jumps.
Features: Extremely addictive and challenging gameplay Easy to learn, hard to master. If you can collect more than 3 stars, you&amp;rsquo;re pretty good! Zen theme for focus Fans of color switch type mechanics will appreciate this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Megacity Hop</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/megacity-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/megacity-hop/</guid>
      <description>Cross the roads with busy traffic. Hop your way across this endless mega city!
On desktop, use your arrow keys to move.
On smartphones and tablets, simply swipe to move.
Features: Easy and intuitive controls. Tap to move forward, swipe left or ride to move horizontally Collect coins to unlock various characters in the shop Play characters such as business man, cool DJ , office lady, policeman and sheriff Dynamic generation of terrain to provide endless gameplay If you&amp;rsquo;ve played crossy type games, this is a perfect fit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vampires and Garlic</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/vampires-and-garlic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/vampires-and-garlic/</guid>
      <description>Halloween and vampires are upon us! What do vampires dislike? Garlic!
Throw garlic bombs (yes, made out of garlic) at pesky vampires. Control the angle and strength of your throws.
Remember to watch your garlic count!
Features: A variety of obstacles including challenging terrain, and objects such as boxes, pulleys and TNTs. Simple point and click throwing mechanic Interactive tutorial 30 challenging levels Fun halloween theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crossword Casual</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/crossword-casual/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/crossword-casual/</guid>
      <description>Solve everyday crossword puzzles involving various themes such as cities, objects, food, and buildings.
Features: Full screen mode Easy to use crossword puzzle. Regardless of device, play the same crossword puzzle as everybody else Easy selection of puzzle grid to insert answers Virtual keyboard for mobile and tablet users. Easily enter your answers to solve the puzzles Random puzzles generated from a pool of questions and answers Relaxing theme, suitable for everyone Note: if you&amp;rsquo;d like different themes, please contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flick Basketball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flick-basketball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flick-basketball/</guid>
      <description>Flick the ball. Score as many points are you can.
Features: Simple, 1 touch controls Easy to pick up and play. It becomes more challenging as you earn higher scores 3D-like view Collect stars for bonus points </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini Golf Adventure</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mini-golf-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mini-golf-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Put the ball into the hole. Use the shortest amount of putts to score maximum stars.
Collect gems to increase your score! Embark on this fun golfing adventure, as your discover new objects and power-ups to help you win.
Features: Discover new elements in this golf paradise, such as the magnet, teleportation stations, windmills, wind accelerators, and yes, a mole! Who&amp;rsquo;s the mole? Interactive tutorial to start putting away Over 24 levels and more to come Fun family oriented theme, suitable for all ages </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ski Hero</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ski-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ski-hero/</guid>
      <description>Ski down the mountain, while avoiding the obstacles. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash!
Features: Interactive tutorial. Anyone can play this game! Family friendly theme, suitable for all ages. Beautiful winter christmas landscape. Collect banners to earn extra points. Fans of winter skifree xmas will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Crush</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jewel-crush/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jewel-crush/</guid>
      <description>Match jewels to score points. Hit the targets to complete each level.
Watch out! You only have limited moves per level.
Earn 3 stars for completing the levels successfully. Discover cool powerups such as row clearing, column clearing, jewel bombs and snowflakes.
Features: Beautiful and shiny jewels to match Over 30 challenging levels Discover cool chain reactions as you complete each level If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a challenging Match-3 game with deep levels and powerups, this is the game for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rise Higher</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/rise-higher/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/rise-higher/</guid>
      <description>Protect your balloon with your shield.
Move your mouse or finger to block incoming threads from popping your balloon!
Features: Endless gameplay. Easy to learn, hard to master Peaceful and happy theme Very challenging obstacles as you go higher up Save your high score and beat it later </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Baseball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ultimate-baseball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ultimate-baseball/</guid>
      <description>Swing high, middle or low to hit the ball. Find your sweet spot and perfect timing. Hit correctly and score a baseball home run!
A simple arcade style baseball game for the fans.
Features: Simple controls to hit high, medium or low Baseball stadium theme, great for brand exposure The game gets more challenging as you score more home runs! Possibility of integrating a high score leaderboard to compete with other players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flip Jump</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flip-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flip-jump/</guid>
      <description>Tap, hold and release to jump.
Jump from one platform to the next.
How far can you jump?
Features: Extremely cute and positive jumper game theme, great for brands Simple, 1 touch gameplay Unlock more characters by reaching certain milestones Beautiful 3d artwork Fans of Tiao Yi Tiao and Bottle Flip will love this jumper game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Liner</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/one-liner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/one-liner/</guid>
      <description>Draw one single line, without ever lifting your finger or mouse.
How many levels can you complete?
Deceptively simple, yet profoundly deep game.
Features: Interactive tutorial Over 120 challenging levels to keep you occupied Upbeat, rhythmic theme How difficult can this be? Just Draw 1 Line! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trivia Quiz</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/trivia-quiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/trivia-quiz/</guid>
      <description>Test your general knowledge in this trivia quiz game.
How many questions can you answer correctly?
Features: Simple, clean and welcoming theme Easy to configure Trivia Quiz. Let us know what you need, and we&amp;rsquo;ll customize it for you. Question separated into different difficulty levels (easy questions first, followed by more challenging questions) 30 randomly rotated questions per round Over 100 different questions in the pool Fullscreen mode </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese New Year Mahjong</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cny-mahjong/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cny-mahjong/</guid>
      <description>Match chinese mahjong tiles to complete the levels.
Features: beautiful chinese inspired art interactive tutorial extremely simple and addictive gameplay easy to start, hard to master fun chinese / asian theme, coupled with mahjong matching elements power ups to reward the user, such as auto solve bonuses </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Hour</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/happy-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/happy-hour/</guid>
      <description>Fill up the martini glass. It&amp;rsquo;s Happy Hour!
Control the flow of drinks to fill up your glass! Everything you draw turns into real objects.
Come up with your own solution to each level.
Features: Funny Happy Hour quotes. Work on multiple drinks including cocktails, wine, spirits, beer and other alcohol related items. Beautiful bar scene and nightlife theme Chill vibe Addictive tracing gameplay. Draw anything. Over 30 challenging levels per city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spidey Swing</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/spidey-swing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/spidey-swing/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the adventures of Spidey. Shoot webs, grab on and swing like a spider pro. Avoid things such as sharp edges, rotating chainsaws, arrows, mace and other deadly objects.
Keep the majority of your body parts intact, and get to the finish line. Keep our beloved Spidey alive!
Features Interactive tutorial Touch, keyboard and mouse controls City skyscraper theme Update: Over 48 extremely challenging levels. Test your spider-man skills. Presence of blood and gore (can be turned off by request) Fans of spiderman and marvel superheroes will love the game </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agent Curiosa vs Rogue Robots</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/agent-curiosa-vs-rogue-robots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/agent-curiosa-vs-rogue-robots/</guid>
      <description>The robots have gone rogue! It&amp;rsquo;s up to teen hacker, Agent Curiosa to save the world.
Armed with your DIY electric zapper, zap these robots out of existence!
Features: Over 30 challenging levels. Fight robots of all kinds. Face big, bad drones in boss levels. Collect items such as extra bonus scores, invisibility, extra life and score boost. Interactive tutorial. Techy theme suitable for tweens and teens alike. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways to Die 3 World Tour</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-3-world-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-to-die-3-world-tour/</guid>
      <description>Play mini games featuring the characters from Dumb Ways to Die.
Dumb Ways to Die is a worldwide brand with over 300 million downloads on Apple App Store and Google Play combined.
Test your reflexes in this challenging series of mini games, where a milisecond can make the difference between winning and losing.
Score coins for each challenge, and use the to repair the once great town of Dumbville.
Features: Extremely challenging levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monster Truck Driving</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/monster-truck-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/monster-truck-driving/</guid>
      <description>Control your monster truck to reach the flag.
Boost, brake and tilt your truck left/right to navigate the path.
Earn stars by completing the level in record time.
Features: Interactive tutorial Use stars to unlock cool characters such as a cool flaming truck, Batman truck, Shark truck, Hyena truck and more. Panning function to plan your routes 20 challenging levels Play repeatedly to get the best high score Upbeat theme Monster Truck and Dirt Bike enthusiasts will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scratch and Match Animal</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/scratch-and-match-animal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/scratch-and-match-animal/</guid>
      <description>You have 3 minutes to scratch and match the animal cards. Beat the time and your high score!
Scratch and match beautifully done cards featuring giraffes, elephants, monkeys, tigers, rabbits, cheetahs, polar bears and elephants.
Features: Tutorial Intuitive scratching interface Fun and positive vibe for all ages </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backgammon</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/backgammon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/backgammon/</guid>
      <description>The objective is to move all your checkers into your home board. Then, bear them off.
Plan your strategy, roll the dice, and leave everything else to luck!
Features: Tutorial included Choose your color Three difficulty modes : easy, medium and hard Fun and casual theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cash Back</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cash-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cash-back/</guid>
      <description>Calculate and return the correct change to customers. Return a combination of dollar notes and coins to customers who purchase items from your store.
Score correctly and generate sales for your store!
Features: Interactive tutorial Hints system 3 difficulty modes Happy theme suitable for young kids </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper Planes</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/paper-planes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/paper-planes/</guid>
      <description>This is the game to train your focus and hand eye coordination.
Swipe in direction of the middle plane.
Score as many points within 60 seconds. Track your daily and weekly score.
Features: Unlock combos multipliers with a winning streak Interactive tutorial Relaxed theme suitable for focus </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Baseball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/extreme-baseball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/extreme-baseball/</guid>
      <description>Aim and release your baseball to knock out your opponents.
Bounce the ball off the walls to cleverly knock out multiple enemies in one attempt.
Collect baseball cards to increase your score.
Features: Tutorial to learn the ropes Interact with multiple elements such as glass, wood boxes, TNTs, buttons, moving platforms and more. Over 20 challenging levels Baseball card collectors will love this High tempo music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Faces</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/funny-faces/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/funny-faces/</guid>
      <description>Quick, you have 5 seconds to remember the face.
Then, drag and drop face parts into the correct positions.
How fast can you reconstruct each face?
Features: Fun and uplifting theme Increasingly complex faces to reconstruct. It gets challenging! Interactive tutorial Attention to detail. Players get to work on hair, eyes, eyebrows, nose, mouth, glasses, moustache and more. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unblocked</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/unblocked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/unblocked/</guid>
      <description>Clear a path for the red block. How many moves do you need, to win?
Features: Bright and positive theme 24 challenging levels Interactive hint system to help solve the puzzle </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valet Parking</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/valet-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/valet-parking/</guid>
      <description>A must have car parking simulator game. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to learn, and yet incredibly difficult to master.
Park your car in the perfect spot, with surgical precision. Be careful not to bump into other cars and objects.
Put on your safety belt, and let the game begin! Fans of parking frenzy games will love this.
Features: Interactive tutorial Beautiful parking spots 3 Star based system to reward precision Over 50+ parking challenges Keyboard controls for desktop, and touch controls for smartphones and tablets Drive a variety of cool cars </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Soccer</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-soccer/</guid>
      <description>Aim and shoot the ball into the goal. Collect the starfish to gain maximum score.
With golden sand, coconut trees, sand castles, crabs, and a gorgeous sunshine, what more do you need?
Features: Interactive tutorial Over 20 challenging levels. Put your thinking cap on. Fun beach theme and music Interact with challenging obstacles such as crabs, sandcastles, and more. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drone Pickup Service</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/drone-pickup-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/drone-pickup-service/</guid>
      <description>The drone revolution has arrived. You operate a Drone pick up service.
Your goal is to navigate the drones into difficult conditions, pick up the packages and return to base.
Fly around trees, hills, cars, airplanes and wind mills to pick up your package.
Complete your tasks in the fastest time to achieve 3 stars.
Features: easy left/right tapping mechanics to navigate extremely challenging levels with various obstacles Play with keyboard , mouse or touch Fun theme and music, suitable for a techy audience who grows up with Uber, Amazon, Instacart and on-demand delivery services </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitchie Clicker</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/twitchie-clicker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/twitchie-clicker/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Twitchie Clicker! If you&amp;rsquo;ve got twitchy fingers, this is the game for you.
Nicknamed H0lyThund3rDude with a cool beanie hat, you have your work cut out for you. Build your streaming empire from nothing. Earn one gamer view at the time, while generating cash.
Upgrade your fame factors to generate more views per second. Unlock cool videos that you can upload to your fans.
Grow your subscriber base to millions of passionate gamers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Running</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/banana-running/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/banana-running/</guid>
      <description>Play as Mr. Nanners, the funniest banana in town with a unique voice.
Unfortunately, Mrs. Nanners is missing, and it&amp;rsquo;s your job to find her in this endless runner.
Run along the city streets in your quest to find Mrs. Nanners. Slide left, right, and under obstacles while collecting Mrs Nanners dolls.
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to collect Banana Balls, and use them to upgrade your gear.
Features: Funny banana theme. Funny banana jokes with voiceover dialogues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gravity Kid</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/gravity-kid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/gravity-kid/</guid>
      <description>Hey you, Gravity Kid with a cool beanie hat. Quick, put on your anti-gravity shoes and start running!
Avoid obstacles, gaps, and oh, did we mention there&amp;rsquo;s a cop on your tail?
Features: Collect coins to upgrade your skills Collect powerups such as shields, coin magnets, and a slow motion potion Practise your reflex skills Pumping music and very street / urban theme Interactive tutorial </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Piggy Piggy Farm</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-farm/</guid>
      <description>Mango Piggy Piggy is HUNGRY. He comes across a mango farm. The mangoes look sweet and juicy, just like how he likes it.
Drag and aim to launch Mango Piggy Piggy towards the mangos. Eat them all to earn 3 stars!
Features: Fun, positive and ridiculously cute character. MPP bounces around and squeals almost like a soft toy. Innovative touch and drag mechanic Over 30 levels Unlock a hidden level Don&amp;rsquo;t eat the red mango!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tripoly</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tripoly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tripoly/</guid>
      <description>Rotate the triangle, to match the color of the line.
How high can you score?
Features: Fast and upbeat theme Interactive tutorial Easy to start, but it gets challenging very quickly </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Ball Dunkin</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/city-ball-dunkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/city-ball-dunkin/</guid>
      <description>Dunk the basketball into each hoop.
Time your dunks well. Make sure you don&amp;rsquo;t hit the ceiling, or fall to the group.
Collect points to unlock different cool balls from the store.
Beware, the challenges get more difficult over time!
Make your way past tricky hoops that move in weird ways.
How high can you score?
Features: A store to unlock different balls. Really cool ones. Fun theme Day and night transition Increasingly challenging gameplay </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways Jr Zanys Hospital</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-jr-zanys-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dumb-ways-jr-zanys-hospital/</guid>
      <description>From the creators of Dumb Ways to Die, the hit brand with over 300 million downloads total on Google Play and Apple App Store - we present to you an exciting spin-off brand called Dumb Ways JR Zany&amp;rsquo;s Hospital.
Visit Dumb Ways Hospital with Doctor Zany. Explore three main areas of play: a waiting room full of surprises to discover, a check-up room where children can play the role of doctor, and an ambulance that visits the hospital featuring fun guest appearances from the original Dumb Ways cast!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Horace vs Cheese</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/horace-vs-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/horace-vs-cheese/</guid>
      <description>Pull and launch Horace the Hamster into the cheese. Eat them all to earn 3 stars.
Then, land safely into the cheese house.
From the creators of Flossy and Jim, we bring you a new brand called Horace and co.
Features: Fun, positive and ridiculously cute character. Horace bounces around and squeals almost like a soft toy. Innovative touch and drag mechanic Over 30 levels Unlock a hidden level Don&amp;rsquo;t eat the blue cheese!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pocket Pac</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pocket-pac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pocket-pac/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t let the monsters catch you! Eat as many dots as you can in this retro arcade game.
Use arrow keys to move around the maze. Make sharp turns to avoid the monsters. Plan your route you never get trapped!
Collect super dots to fight back against the monsters.
How many points can you score?
Features: New and improved maze. Fun arcade theme. Keyboard controls for desktop. Touch controls for mobile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Build Me</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-build-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-build-me/</guid>
      <description>Remember the parts, then drag and drop the parts to form a complete character.
We&amp;rsquo;re proud to present Arty Mouse - Build Me, a branded game built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Interactive tutorial Fun theme for kids of all ages - helps to train cognitive abilities and memory Work with a variety of interesting characters from the Arty Mouse universe, including Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, and Spiro the snail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Sticker Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-sticker-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-sticker-book/</guid>
      <description>Now, your kids can express themselves through art.
Place your favourite Arty Mouse stickers onto the board, decorate them as you wish.
Drag and drop, resize and reposition them to your hearts content. Need to erase a sticker? No problem.
Create millions of sticker combinations using different Arty Mouse characters, objects and backgrounds. Work with Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, Spiro the snail, and more characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Chicken Memory Match</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-memory-match/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-memory-match/</guid>
      <description>From the hit animation series Chuck Chicken, we bring you this exciting memory match game.
Match your favorite Chuck Chicken cards, and do it in the shortest amount of time!
Discover cool cards featuring Chuck, Flick, Wing as well as nemesis cards including Dr Mingo, Dee, Don, Dex.
Features: Interactive tutorial Beautiful Chuck Chicken artwork Simple, crisp gameplay Fast paced action card theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-and-friends-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-and-friends-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Express your creativity via this coloring book.
We&amp;rsquo;re proud to present Arty Mouse &amp;amp; Friends Coloring Book, a digital coloring book built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Multiple templates to start with Choose different brush sizes and colours Eraser mode Save your works (useful if you&amp;rsquo;d like to print the pictures) Color interesting characters from the Arty Mouse universe, including Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, and Spiro the snail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Connect the Dots</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-connect-the-dots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/didi-and-friends-connect-the-dots/</guid>
      <description>Didi and Friends, popular kids animation with over 1 billion views on Youtube is here with a brand new game.
Connect the dots to reveal interesting objects, animals and characters.
Teach your kids and toddlers to connect the dots, and get rewarded with happy smiles from Didi the Chicken and his friends!
Features: Fun and vibrant theme, guaranteed to excite kids, preschoolers and toddlers. Simple gameplay suitable for kids Fullscreen mode Learn everyday objects, animals, environmental elements and above all, the brand new set of Didi and Friends characters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kuu Kuu Harajuku Diy Kawaii Stickers</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/kuu-kuu-harajuku-diy-kawaii-stickers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/kuu-kuu-harajuku-diy-kawaii-stickers/</guid>
      <description>Tick tock, time to rock! Kuu Kuu Harajuku is an animation brand created by Grammy winner Gwen Stefani. They&amp;rsquo;re back with a game for tween and teen girls!
Create your own sticker book with characters from the hit TV series. Drag and drop stickers that represent G, Love, Angel, Music and Baby into beautiful backgrounds of Harajuku City. Start with the Clubhouse, and move your way to decorate the studio, parks, and the Harajuku City skyline!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Piggy Piggy Hero</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mango-piggy-piggy-hero/</guid>
      <description>Mango Piggy Piggy is back with a brand new series and new episodes.
In his hero edition, control different superhero piggies, as you attempt to defend your town against the invasion of enemy robots.
Whats New:
Activate Panther Piggy to dash through obstacles. Activate Hulk Piggy to create a memorable, powerful smash attack. Activate Marvel Piggy to deal widespread damage to enemies. Activate Antman Piggy to suddenly become huge and inflict crazy damage Activate Spider Piggy to pull targets towards it Launch your hero piggy against the enemy, in Angry Birds fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boj Coloring Book</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Showcase your creativity via this coloring book, featuring Boj and friends. A fun, all-digital and reusable coloring book built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features: Multiple Boj themed templates to start with Choose different brush sizes and colours Did something wrong? Undo your colors via an eraser Save your works and print them. This feature is great for classrooms Color interesting characters from the Boj universe, including Boj the Bilby himself, Mimi, Pops, Denzil, Mr Cloppity, Mia Twitch, Julie Twitch and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boj Giggly Park Adventure</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-giggly-park-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/boj-giggly-park-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Explore Giggly Park with Boj and friends.
Boj is an award winning kids television series worldwide.
Do wonderful things such as ride a bike, climb the tree, fly a kite, dig underground for treasures, ride the swing, control a helicopter remotely and more.
Interact with various characters from the Boj universe, such as Mimi, Pops, Mr Cloppity, Denzil, Mia Twitch and more.
This is a new and innovative gameplay to encourage users to explore their curiosity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Chicken Magic Egg</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-magic-egg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/chuck-chicken-magic-egg/</guid>
      <description>Chuck Chicken is on a mission. Defeat his nemesis Dee, Don, Dex, Dr Mingo and more in this exciting and fast-paced puzzle platformer game.
Chuck Chicken is a worldwide kids and tweens animation brand with over 2 billion views.
In this game, throw your egg, and watch as it bounces from wall to wall, defeating your opponents.
Collect magic eggs to transform Chuck into his alter ego super hero. For example,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oddbods Ice Cream Fight</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-ice-cream-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-ice-cream-fight/</guid>
      <description>The mischievous Oddbods are at it again! Throw delicious ice cream at them, before they throw back!
This ice cream fight is getting wild! The Oddbods can duck, run left and right, and also appear out of nowhere to attack you.
Features: battle against different Oddbods such as Fuse, Bubbles, Pogo, Zee, Slick, Jeff and Newt. boss levels with Fuse. He&amp;rsquo;s a tough one to crack! fun theme song increasingly difficult challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oddbods Soccer Challenge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-soccer-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-soccer-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Fancy a soccer game with your favourite Oddbods? Kick the ball into the goal, but beware! The mischievous Oddbods are here to stop you.
Features: Compete against Oddbods such as Fuse, Bubbles, Pogo, Zee, Slick, Jeff and Newt. Fun Oddbods theme song Each Oddbod brings something interesting to the game Over 60 levels more more to be added soon Interactive tutorial Fans of soccer or football will love this game. If you&amp;rsquo;re into the World Cup, English Premier League or UEFA Champions League, this game will be interesting too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penalty Kick</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/penalty-kick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/penalty-kick/</guid>
      <description>The pitch is set. The stadium is packed full. The fans are chanting. The spotlight is on you.
Swipe the ball towards the goal. Avoid goalies and defenders.
How many goals can you score past the goalkeeper?
Features: fun, arcade style theme fast paced action goalie has varying degrees of intelligence unlock different balls based on high score </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stick Golf</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stick-golf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stick-golf/</guid>
      <description>Aim, adjust the club power and go! Playing golf has never been this easy.
From easy to challenging terrains, use your acute golf senses to land a hole in one.
Avoid bunkers and water hazards!
Features: interactive tutorial to help your audience relaxed theme and background. Playing golf has never been this relaxing. earn coins from successful holes use coins at the shop, to purchase fun skins such as top hat, pirate hat, bunny hats and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biker Lane</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/biker-lane/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/biker-lane/</guid>
      <description>Control your bike rider to reach the flag.
Boost, brake and tilt your bike left/right to navigate the tricky roads.
Earn stars by completing the level in record time.
Features: Interactive tutorial Use stars to unlock cool characters such as grandma biker, traffic police biker, punk biker, and pro biker. Panning function to plan your routes 20 challenging levels Play repeatedly to get the best high score Upbeat theme Motorcycle and moto x3m enthusiasts will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Castle Siege</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/castle-siege/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/castle-siege/</guid>
      <description>Use your cannon ball to destroy the foundations of the castle structure.
When the castle structure falls, the guards will be eliminated. Remember to avoid hurting the hostages!
Features: Innovative splitting mechanic. Aim your cannonball to split structures into multiple pieces Collect treasures to increase your score Place your shots correctly to earn more crowns Comedic sound effects Fun relaxed puzzle game </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soccer Pong</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soccer-pong/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soccer-pong/</guid>
      <description>How good are you at pong? Drag the paddle, and hit the ball into the opponent&amp;rsquo;s goal post.
Play in a soccer setting with the crowd cheering you all the way. A fun and engaging game for everybody.
Features: 3 different gameplay modes (Easy, Difficult and Expert). Easy mode is the standard classic pong Difficult mode increases the pressure with faster balls and smarter computer Expert mode ( the pong paddle is free to roam everywhere, the ball is fast and the computer is clever!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confident Driver</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/confident-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/confident-driver/</guid>
      <description>How fast are your reflexes? Control your car, pick the right lanes and avoid any crashes to win the level.
Features Drive alongside other vehicles such as mini coopers, new york taxi cabs, trucks, police cars and more Precise and accurate turning, allowing users to cut really sharp corners Beautiful graphics with vehicles closely resembling real vehicles A variety of obstacles such as oil spills, roadblocks, ice and more Challenging levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spider Solitaire</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/spider-solitaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/spider-solitaire/</guid>
      <description>Spider themed solitaire game. You&amp;rsquo;ll definitely get addicted
Features: stunning spider theme tutorial feeling stuck? Use our hints system hours of repetitive gameplay. Each deck is randomly generated. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Triangle Wars</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/triangle-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/triangle-wars/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re a lone spaceship lost in space. Attack other spaceships to survive in the vastness of space. Aim for the highest score.
Features: Interactive tutorial to ease learning curve Endless gameplay Space like physics, for fans of Space Invaders 90s retro games Pick up a variety of powerups such as bombs, splash bullets and extra lives Battle intelligent boss ships Energetic theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Survival</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/zombie-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/zombie-survival/</guid>
      <description>A strange virus outbreak turned your friends into zombies. Armed with a basic pistol, make your way through hordes of zombies.
How many days can you survive, before you become one of them?
Features: 3D like isometric graphics Collect coins with each zombie kill Multiple weapons to purchase. Try the machine gun, shotgun, rifle and laser gun Fun stats to review after each day 3 different gameplay modes: Survival, Hard Point and Nuke Tutorial to learn the ropes Yes, you can blow up barrels to burn the zombies </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Echo Simon</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/echo-simon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/echo-simon/</guid>
      <description>Simon says &amp;hellip; watch the sequence.
Memorize the sequence, then recreate it.
How high can you score?
Features: interactive tutorial endless gameplay easy to learn, difficult to master be prepared for surprises at later levels </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trixology</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/trixology/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/trixology/</guid>
      <description>Rotate the piece to fit the grid below. Fans of modern tetris, you&amp;rsquo;ll love this game.
Cover a full row without gaps, and earn yourself bonus points.
How high is your score?
Features: Clear instructions to learn the ropes Minimalist theme ensures focus for long gameplay and time spent Additional controls such as speed down, accelerate, and rotate clockwise / counterclockwise Increasingly difficult as the level progresses </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yatzy</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/yatzy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/yatzy/</guid>
      <description>Everyone loves dice games. Roll the dice, pick the combination and try to outscore your opponent.
If you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of Yacht or Yahtzee, you&amp;rsquo;ll fall in love with this game.
Features Interactive tutorial Fun theme suitable for all ages Includes a rolling cup and scorepad! Bonus animation if you get a &amp;lsquo;Yatzy&amp;rsquo; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Casual Chess</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/casual-chess/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/casual-chess/</guid>
      <description>Play classic chess against the computer. Plan your moves and execute your strategies to outwit your opponent.
Features 3 different themes Easy, moderate and hard computer AI Play as white or black in this two (2) player game Hints system to guide your moves Fun casual theme, suitable for all ages </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flip the Knife</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flip-the-knife/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flip-the-knife/</guid>
      <description>Swipe up to flip the knife. Make sure it lands correctly to get 3 stars.
Flip continuously to earn a higher score.
Flip it over chairs, tables, pots and pans, bottles, weighing machines, and other household items.
Did we mention this? There&amp;rsquo;s an annoying bird that tries to sabotage your knife trajectory.
Features: Easy to learn, hard to master Increasingly challenging Upgrade your knives collection. From machetes, to medieval knives, we&amp;rsquo;ve got em all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jumping Burger</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jumping-burger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jumping-burger/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re a sliding burger with jumping ability.
Avoid obstacles such as ketchup bottles, birds and tiny mice as you slide forward, while collecting ingredients to unlock the perfect burger.
Ingredients include lettuce, tomato, cheese, burger patties, mushroom and salmon fillets.
Grab Chillis to be come temporarily invincible.
How far can you go?
Features: Cute restaurant diner setting Easy to play, hard to master. This game is very challenging. A shop to unlock your burgers </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sky Castle</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sky-castle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sky-castle/</guid>
      <description>My liege, stack the castle parts above each other. Stack them high and strong. Be the ruler of the tallest castle in the world.
Features: Endless gameplay. Spend hours trying to perfect your placement. The castle becomes more challenging to build as they get higher Simple controls: tap to place castle blocks Use a variety of helpers such as Reverse, Repeat, Insurance, and Double Coins Beautiful graphics and ancient medieval theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Line</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/draw-one-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/draw-one-line/</guid>
      <description>Draw one single line, without ever lifting your finger or mouse.
How many levels can you complete?
Deceptively simple, yet profoundly deep game.
Features: Interactive tutorial Over 120 challenging levels to keep you occupied Upbeat, rhythmic theme How difficult can this be? Just Draw 1 Line! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skeleton Defense</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/skeleton-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/skeleton-defense/</guid>
      <description>Soldier! You&amp;rsquo;re the last hope for humanity. It&amp;rsquo;s up to you to stop the waves of undead skeletons.
Features: Interactive tutorial to learn the ropes Scary skeleton theme 7 different weapons. Use rifles, grenades, rockets, molotov cocktails and other impressive weapons to stop these skeletons 5 different skeleton types Unlimited gameplay A shop to upgrade and unlock new weapons </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowboard Hero</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/snowboard-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/snowboard-hero/</guid>
      <description>Snowboard your way down the mountain, while avoiding the obstacles. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash!
Features: Interactive tutorial. Anyone can play this game! Fast, pumping music suitable for X sports. Beautiful winter christmas landscape. Collect banners to earn extra points. Fans of winter skifree xmas or snowboarding will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bingo Solo</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bingo-solo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bingo-solo/</guid>
      <description>Play bingo by yourself. A single player bingo game.
Choose from 3 different speeds, based on what you need.
Features: Simple gameplay, great for solo play Real voices that call the numbers No computer opponents No AI opponents Can be installed in offline environments Win patterns included </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hardest Game on Earth</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/hardest-game-on-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/hardest-game-on-earth/</guid>
      <description>The title says it all! This is the world&amp;rsquo;s hardest game.
Navigate your way through the maze.
Collect coins, keys and avoid obstacles. Don&amp;rsquo;t break your glass!
Features: Tutorial included. Fun earth theme Extremely challenging levels. Be mentally and emotionally prepared! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oddbods Monster Truck Driving</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-monster-truck-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oddbods-monster-truck-driving/</guid>
      <description>Control your Oddbods monster truck to reach the flag.
Boost, brake and tilt your truck left/right to navigate the path.
Earn stars by completing the level in record time.
Features: Drive with all 7 Oddbods, including Fuse, Bubbles, Pogo, Zee, Slick, Jeff and Newt. Interactive tutorial Each Oddbod brings something special Use stars to unlock cool vehicles Panning function to plan your routes 20 challenging levels Play repeatedly to get the best high score Upbeat theme Monster Truck and Dirt Bike enthusiasts will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stack the Pancake</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stack-the-pancake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stack-the-pancake/</guid>
      <description>Drag and drop the pancake from the pan, onto the plate. It&amp;rsquo;s that simple!
How many pancakes can you pile up? Use your creativity to build stable and towering pan cakes!
Features: Interactive tutorial Fun casual theme, suitable for everyone Addictive stacking gameplay. Make your users compete to get the highest score Intuitive touch based controls </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooking Love</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cooking-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cooking-love/</guid>
      <description>You just arrived in New York, to pursue your dream of becoming a chef.
Your plan? Work for the famed and attractive chef extraordinaire, Giovanni van Damme to gain experience.
Work your way up the culinary ladder to become Manhattan&amp;rsquo;s hottest chef, in this episode driven interactive story novel.
Discover food, friendship and love. Stumble through life and live the ups and downs of what the Big Apple has to offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dominoes</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dominoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dominoes/</guid>
      <description>Draw dominoes: Every round, match tiles until your opponent is unable to move. If you have no possible moves, draw a domino until you can match a tile. If there are no dominoes left, pass your turn until you can. Reach 100 points to win.
Block dominoes: The same as Draw Dominoes. The main difference is, if you have no possible moves, pass your turn until you can match a tile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soda Can Knockdown</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soda-can-knockout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/soda-can-knockout/</guid>
      <description>Knock down soda cans with balls. Earn 3 stars for completing each level perfectly.
Features: Challenging levels. Encounter different sets with different soda cans Wide landscape (horizontal) design, with fullscreen mode Beautiful 3D carnival theme. Simple and addictive gameplay. Realistic physics This game is great for fans of various beverage brands such as Coca Cola, Pepsi, Red Bull, Monster and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typing Fighter</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/typing-fighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/typing-fighter/</guid>
      <description>Type fast, type accurate and fight hard in this innovative street fighter style typing game.
Charge up your typing and deliver killer power moves.
Get inspired by motivational phrases and quotes while you type.
Fight against a variety of opponents.
Features: Beautifully designed street fight urban setting Fluid character animations Over 200 motivational quotes and phrases to keep you going </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Volley</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-volley/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-volley/</guid>
      <description>Move your turtle to hit the ball.
Keep the ball from falling into your own court.
First to score 10 wins!
Features: Beautiful and minimalist beach theme Really cute sea turtles Challenging AI </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkour Climb</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-climb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-climb/</guid>
      <description>Tap to jump from wall to wall, parkour style.
How high can you climb up, in this parkur free running game?
Features: Modern futuristic theme Collect shields to stop your fall Collect jetpacks to boost your score Responsive design </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sort the Trash</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sort-the-trash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sort-the-trash/</guid>
      <description>Protect the environment by learning how to recycle correctly.
Collect items that can be recycled only. Avoid collecting contaminators such as organic waste, disposable coffee cups, plastic straws, ceramic dishware and lithium ion batteries.
Go green and save the Earth. Start becoming eco-friendly today!
Features: Simple elegant design Responsive design Positive them with recycling facts </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Invasion</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bubble-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bubble-invasion/</guid>
      <description>Defend your base against the invasion of bubbles.
Match 2 or more bubbles of the same color to eliminate them.
Don&amp;rsquo;t let any bubble cross the line!
How high can you score?
Features: Simple, minimalist bubble shooter theme Endless bubble shooter gameplay Responsive design Use a variety of power ups such as freeze, lightning, explosions and rainbow bubbles to gain a competitive edge </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commando Boat</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/commando-boat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/commando-boat/</guid>
      <description>Commando! Drive your speed boat behind enemy lines.
Avoid incoming obstacles such as river mines, tree logs, rocks and other boats.
Shoot and destroy obstacles with bullets.
This is a new and reimagined casual shoot em up game featuring a marine theme.
Features: Collect coins to purchase cool boat models such water raft, speed boat, hovercrafts, and more. Collect powerups including coin magnets, bullets and bubble shields Take ramp to get a cool boost forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flossy and Jim Whale Tickler</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flossy-and-jim-whale-tickler/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flossy-and-jim-whale-tickler/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a cute whale that you can tickle all day long.
Tickle and rub the whale until the bar fills up. Watch as you receive a special response from the whale.
With this game, spread the positivity and feel-good vibe with your audience.
Features: Random emotions and quotes each time Extremely cute design This whale has tusk! It&amp;rsquo;s a Narwhal! Unlimited gameplay and tickles Fun and chill music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knife Master</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/knife-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/knife-master/</guid>
      <description>Throw the knife at the target board.
Score double points for hitting the bullsye.
Sounds easy? As you progress further, you&amp;rsquo;ll need every single ounce of skill and finesse in knife throwing.
Not to mention, you&amp;rsquo;ll need impeccable timing too.
One miss of the knife, and you&amp;rsquo;re out!
Similar to darts, fans of knife throwing and all throwing sports will love this game.
Features: Fast paced knife throwing theme Minimalist look and feel Every challenge is designed exactly the same for each player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arty Mouse Learn Abc</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-learn-abc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/arty-mouse-learn-abc/</guid>
      <description>Arty Mouse is back with a new game! Teach your toddlers to trace alphabets from A to Z.
Help them recognize letter shapes and associate them with phonic sounds.
Suitable for toddlers, preschool and kindergarten kids.
Work with fun characters from the Arty Mouse universe, including Scribble the dog, Stripy the cat, Dot the bear, Rainbow Birds, Spiro the snail, and more characters.
Features: Interactive tutorial Upper and lower case alphabet tracing Fun, welcoming and inclusive game for kids </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create rows of jewels to win</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jewels-blocks-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jewels-blocks-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Drag and drop jewel blocks to fill the empty gap.
Complete a row of beautiful jewels to score points. Complete 2 rows or more to score bonus points.
How high can you score?
Features: Interactive tutorial Endless gameplay. Play until you run out of turns. Mesmerizing jewel theme to encourage focus and productivity. Fans of tetris and trixology will love this. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wheels on the Bus Sing Along</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/wheels-on-the-bus-sing-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/wheels-on-the-bus-sing-along/</guid>
      <description>The wheels on the bus go round and round in this kids activity game. Ride the bus with fellow animals such as Tiger the driver, Elephant, Rabbit, Monkey and Fox.
Listen to the sweet voice singing the song. Allow your kids to work on discovery activities such as tapping on the animals, activating the bus lights, making the bird sing, honking the bus and more.
Features: real vocals by voice actors cute animal characters touch-based activities for kids to keep busy This game is great for parents teaching kids sing-along songs with activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bricked</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bricked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bricked/</guid>
      <description>Tap and match bricks of the same color.
Plan your moves carefully, to ensure perfect elimination of the remaining bricks.
How high can you score?
Features: Ability to rewind. You have 3 wishes. Unlimited gameplay. Fun theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Crossword</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/holiday-crossword/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/holiday-crossword/</guid>
      <description>Solve holiday themed crossword puzzles involving various topics such as cities, food, celebrations and gift ideas.
Features: Full screen mode Easy to use cross word puzzle. Regardless of device, play the same crossword puzzle as everybody else Easy selection of puzzle grid to insert answers Virtual keyboard for mobile and tablet users. Easily enter your answers to solve the puzzles Random puzzles generated from a pool of questions and answers Relaxing theme, suitable for everyone Note: if you&amp;rsquo;d like different themes and questions, please contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkour Run</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-run/</guid>
      <description>Run along rooftops, jump through windows, hang from ledges, and slide under giant water tanks.
Perform various cool parkour inspired tricks using various vectors and angles, but be careful not to fall!
How far can you go in this endless runner platformer game?
Features: Exciting and fast paced music beats Simple minimalist graphics and urban style Addictive and repetitive gameplay, perfect for high score seekers Desktop and mobile friendly controls </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pipe Master</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pipe-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pipe-master/</guid>
      <description>Rearrange the pipes to make the water flow.
Build your pipe line and convey water from starting to end point. Don&amp;rsquo;t run out of moves!
Features: Beautiful pipe and water graphics Interactive tutorial Over 24 challenging levels. Level 1 is easy, but start wrecking your head with Level 2. Great music and sound effects Full screen version available This game is great for puzzle and cognitive game fans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Numbers Challenge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/numbers-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/numbers-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Which side is greater? Left, right or are they equal?
Numbers Challenge is a new and exciting cognitive math based game.
Answer 5 questions in a row correctly, to move up the level.
Miss one, and the game is over at the end of the level.
Features: Easy to start. The math gets complicated the further you go Peaceful theme, suitable for concentration Tough and tricky questions Accuracy stats for math geeks </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop the Virus</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pop-the-virus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pop-the-virus/</guid>
      <description>With the Coronavirus causing havoc around the world, we all need some time to destress, relax and chill out. Yes, that&amp;rsquo;s 3 different words to induce calm.
Pop as many COVID-19 virus cells before time runs out.
Tap quickly and tap often. Some corona viruses are harder to pop that others. It&amp;rsquo;s because they&amp;rsquo;re sneaky, and they&amp;rsquo;re wearing surgical masks too!
How many covid 19 viruses can you beat? Let&amp;rsquo;s defeat this killer plague together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Lane Racing</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/fast-lane-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/fast-lane-racing/</guid>
      <description>Race against other cars.
Tap to switch lanes. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash into other cars!
Keep on your toes and be prepared to switch lanes quickly in this fastlane game.
Features: Endless gameplay Urban hip hop racing theme Extremely simple controls Simple, linear high score system Fans of racing and driving games will love this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Colors</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/amazing-colors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/amazing-colors/</guid>
      <description>Swipe to paint in each direction.
Color the floors with the least amount of moves.
Can you beat your own high score?
Painting has never been this fun!
Features: Zen and minimalist theme. Over 60 challenging levels that will amaze you. Interactive tutorial Fully responsive design Colour the floor with a variety of different balls </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lock Master</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/lock-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/lock-master/</guid>
      <description>Tap to start the lock picking process.
Be patient, concentrate and wait until the key touches the orange dot.
When the moment is right, tap to unlock and score a point in this fast, hypercasual game.
How many locks can you unlock?
Features: Easy to play, hard to master Great spy and thief theme Overcome distractions and obstacles in each level </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teddy Bubble Rescue</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/teddy-bubble-rescue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/teddy-bubble-rescue/</guid>
      <description>Big Teddy needs your help! Pop the objects to rescue the mini teddy bears.
Place your shooter aim carefully to clear the maximum amount of objects in each level.
Features: Interactive tutorial 20 challenging levels Fun theme Solve sets using a variety of tactics. Use clever theory of angles, target higher objects and other tactics to solve each level </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climb the Rocks</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/climb-the-rocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/climb-the-rocks/</guid>
      <description>Wait for the right moment to grab the next rock.
Climb one rock at a time. Avoid unstable rocks, while keeping an eye at the prize.
Can you conquer Mount Narya?
Features: Feeling strong like Rocky? Try other more challenging mountains such as Mount Kibar, Alru, Chota, Ordh and Ucca. Endless gameplay Collect diamonds to unlock new mountain climbing characters. Challenging outdoor environment Great theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Soccer</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/smart-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/smart-soccer/</guid>
      <description>Soccer has never been this fun. Simply drag, aim and release to shoot the soccer ball.
The first to score 3 goals wins.
Features: Choose your side, from 32 nations. Smart and calculative AI. Be prepared to play hard! Tutorial to learn the ropes Exciting soccer stadium environment, perfect for soccer nuts </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Escape From Aztec</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/escape-from-aztec/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 12:42:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/escape-from-aztec/</guid>
      <description>You just stole King Aztec&amp;rsquo;s greatest treasure. Now you&amp;rsquo;re being hunted.
Run as fast as you can. Avoid tree trunks, boulders and ancient ruins. Switch lanes, jump and slide your way to freedom.
Collect treasures along the way to purchase powerups.
How far can you escape?
Features: 3D-like environment built with Aztec theme Use Aztec coins to purchase powerups in the store Use a variety of powerups such as invincibility, coin magnets, megaboost and extra lives </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
