<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hypercasual on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/hypercasual/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hypercasual on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/hypercasual/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alpha Space Invasion</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/alpha-space-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:00:58 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/alpha-space-invasion/</guid>
      <description>Alpha sector is under invasion. Young pilot, your task is simple. Warp into the sector, and destroy enemy spacecraft before they destroy you.
Avoid the asteroids and keep your shields high. Rake up as many hits as you can!
Features: Interactive tutorial Simple controls (keyboard on desktop, touch controls on mobile) Endless gameplay Fans of sci-fi movies such as Star Wars, Star Trek, Battlestar Galactica and Guardians of the Galaxy will - love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cam and Leon Donut Hop</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cam-and-leon-donut-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:55:10 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/cam-and-leon-donut-hop/</guid>
      <description>Brought to you by the creators of a 3D animation, Cam and Leon Donut Hop features 2 funny and cute characters, hopping their way around the park.
Hop in and out of donuts, but don&amp;rsquo;t hit the obstacles!
Features Interactive tutorial Easy to play, hard to master Increasingly challenging obstacles Unlock different characters as you progress. Gain access to Leon, Ladybird, Ice Cube and Pepper Shaker! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Hunt</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oil-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:48:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/oil-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Stretch out a pipe in order to strike oil.
Hit it big as you guide oil-hungry heroes and monsters in a mystical wasteland! Aim for the highest score, and unlock funny characters!
Explore different lands - from long stretching savannas, to green hills, sandy beaches and dark marshes - you’ll be surprised at all the places you’ll find where you can just stick a pipe and watch as tons of fantastic tasty dark stuff spill out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinosaur Run</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dinosaur-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:46:46 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dinosaur-run/</guid>
      <description>Play a cute and lovable T-Rex running across a desert.
Time your dino jumps to avoid the different obstacles.
How high can you score?
Features: Cool pixel artwork with T Rex dinosaur. Classic grayscale theme set in prehistoric era. Jump over a variety of plants and cactus. Easy to play, hard to master. The background accelerates and decelerates occasionally, to keep you on your toes. Responsive design with fullscreen capability Works great on Chrome and any modern HTML5 browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kill the Spy</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/kill-the-spy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:45:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/kill-the-spy/</guid>
      <description>Armed with your trusty pistol, it&amp;rsquo;s up to you, Agent 007 to eliminate the enemy spy agents.
Tap on the correct blocks to eliminate the spy agents. Use the least amount of moves to earn more stars.
Do not hard the hostages, or else the mission will fail.
Features: Innovative physics and game mechanics. Aim your spy pistol to split structures into multiple pieces Collect treasures to increase your score Place your shots correctly to earn more stars Spy theme and sound effects Fans of James Bond , Men in Black and spy themed novels will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stupid Zombies</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stupid-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:44:27 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stupid-zombies/</guid>
      <description>One man, one shotgun and a whole lot of zombies. You are humanity&amp;rsquo;s last hope, and it&amp;rsquo;s your job to keep them brainless.
Adjust your shots and angles, and you watch your bullets ricochet from wall to wall, elegantly picking off each zombie&amp;rsquo;s arms and limbs.
Features: 4 giant stages with over 360 challenging levels Exciting zombie theme Simple and innovative ricochet based gameplay. Defeat the stupid zombies with brains and ingenuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seashore Treasure</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/seashore-treasure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:42:41 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/seashore-treasure/</guid>
      <description>Tap an item to pick it up.
Next, pick up a new item that you haven&amp;rsquo;t picked up before.
Continue doing so, until you reach the limit.
Pick up cool items such as sun shades, sea shells, turtles, jellyfish, shorts, sun screen, fish, seahorses and more.
Features: Fun, relaxed beach and sunny theme Measure your cognitive ability and improve your memory 3 different beaches Beautiful sea shore graphics and animation </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Bottle Shooter</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/3d-bottle-shoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/3d-bottle-shoot/</guid>
      <description>Aim and shoot glass bottles. It&amp;rsquo;s so simple, yet so addictive.
Listen to the harmonic sounds of glass shattering amidst the peaceful countryside.
Aim for 3 stars in each level.
Features: Over 30 challenging levels Serene and peaceful countryside vibe Simple controls for the casual user Beautiful, low-poly gun, countryside, trees and mountains. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duck Carnival Shoot</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/duck-carnival-shoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/duck-carnival-shoot/</guid>
      <description>Take aim and shoot the ducks, before the time runs out!
Earn coins to upgrade your accuracy.
Complete mini missions to earn more coins.
Features: Cute ducks with funny outfits Fun and challenging gameplay. These ducks will surprise you. Interactive tutorial Play interesting mini missions. Gun down Mafia Duck Boss, Hunt the Police, and shoot all Ducks in Business Suits! Disclaimer: No real ducks are harmed in the production of this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rugby Extreme</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/rugby-extreme-flick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/rugby-extreme-flick/</guid>
      <description>Flick the ball into the goal post. How many goals can you score?
Features: Easy to play, difficult to master Get extra points for scoring in designated target areas Beware of the changing wind speeds at higher levels Flying capemen will try to block your shots Unlock different objects such as beer bottles, watermelon, easter eggs and rockets Fans of flick kick rugby, american football and rugby world cup will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Megacity Hop</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/megacity-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/megacity-hop/</guid>
      <description>Cross the roads with busy traffic. Hop your way across this endless mega city!
On desktop, use your arrow keys to move.
On smartphones and tablets, simply swipe to move.
Features: Easy and intuitive controls. Tap to move forward, swipe left or ride to move horizontally Collect coins to unlock various characters in the shop Play characters such as business man, cool DJ , office lady, policeman and sheriff Dynamic generation of terrain to provide endless gameplay If you&amp;rsquo;ve played crossy type games, this is a perfect fit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vampires and Garlic</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/vampires-and-garlic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/vampires-and-garlic/</guid>
      <description>Halloween and vampires are upon us! What do vampires dislike? Garlic!
Throw garlic bombs (yes, made out of garlic) at pesky vampires. Control the angle and strength of your throws.
Remember to watch your garlic count!
Features: A variety of obstacles including challenging terrain, and objects such as boxes, pulleys and TNTs. Simple point and click throwing mechanic Interactive tutorial 30 challenging levels Fun halloween theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flick Basketball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flick-basketball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/flick-basketball/</guid>
      <description>Flick the ball. Score as many points are you can.
Features: Simple, 1 touch controls Easy to pick up and play. It becomes more challenging as you earn higher scores 3D-like view Collect stars for bonus points </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini Golf Adventure</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mini-golf-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/mini-golf-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Put the ball into the hole. Use the shortest amount of putts to score maximum stars.
Collect gems to increase your score! Embark on this fun golfing adventure, as your discover new objects and power-ups to help you win.
Features: Discover new elements in this golf paradise, such as the magnet, teleportation stations, windmills, wind accelerators, and yes, a mole! Who&amp;rsquo;s the mole? Interactive tutorial to start putting away Over 24 levels and more to come Fun family oriented theme, suitable for all ages </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ski Hero</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ski-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ski-hero/</guid>
      <description>Ski down the mountain, while avoiding the obstacles. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash!
Features: Interactive tutorial. Anyone can play this game! Family friendly theme, suitable for all ages. Beautiful winter christmas landscape. Collect banners to earn extra points. Fans of winter skifree xmas will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jewel Crush</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jewel-crush/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jewel-crush/</guid>
      <description>Match jewels to score points. Hit the targets to complete each level.
Watch out! You only have limited moves per level.
Earn 3 stars for completing the levels successfully. Discover cool powerups such as row clearing, column clearing, jewel bombs and snowflakes.
Features: Beautiful and shiny jewels to match Over 30 challenging levels Discover cool chain reactions as you complete each level If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a challenging Match-3 game with deep levels and powerups, this is the game for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rise Higher</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/rise-higher/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/rise-higher/</guid>
      <description>Protect your balloon with your shield.
Move your mouse or finger to block incoming threads from popping your balloon!
Features: Endless gameplay. Easy to learn, hard to master Peaceful and happy theme Very challenging obstacles as you go higher up Save your high score and beat it later </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Baseball</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ultimate-baseball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/ultimate-baseball/</guid>
      <description>Swing high, middle or low to hit the ball. Find your sweet spot and perfect timing. Hit correctly and score a baseball home run!
A simple arcade style baseball game for the fans.
Features: Simple controls to hit high, medium or low Baseball stadium theme, great for brand exposure The game gets more challenging as you score more home runs! Possibility of integrating a high score leaderboard to compete with other players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Liner</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/one-liner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/one-liner/</guid>
      <description>Draw one single line, without ever lifting your finger or mouse.
How many levels can you complete?
Deceptively simple, yet profoundly deep game.
Features: Interactive tutorial Over 120 challenging levels to keep you occupied Upbeat, rhythmic theme How difficult can this be? Just Draw 1 Line! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Hour</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/happy-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/happy-hour/</guid>
      <description>Fill up the martini glass. It&amp;rsquo;s Happy Hour!
Control the flow of drinks to fill up your glass! Everything you draw turns into real objects.
Come up with your own solution to each level.
Features: Funny Happy Hour quotes. Work on multiple drinks including cocktails, wine, spirits, beer and other alcohol related items. Beautiful bar scene and nightlife theme Chill vibe Addictive tracing gameplay. Draw anything. Over 30 challenging levels per city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spidey Swing</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/spidey-swing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/spidey-swing/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the adventures of Spidey. Shoot webs, grab on and swing like a spider pro. Avoid things such as sharp edges, rotating chainsaws, arrows, mace and other deadly objects.
Keep the majority of your body parts intact, and get to the finish line. Keep our beloved Spidey alive!
Features Interactive tutorial Touch, keyboard and mouse controls City skyscraper theme Update: Over 48 extremely challenging levels. Test your spider-man skills. Presence of blood and gore (can be turned off by request) Fans of spiderman and marvel superheroes will love the game </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unblocked</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/unblocked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/unblocked/</guid>
      <description>Clear a path for the red block. How many moves do you need, to win?
Features: Bright and positive theme 24 challenging levels Interactive hint system to help solve the puzzle </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Soccer</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-soccer/</guid>
      <description>Aim and shoot the ball into the goal. Collect the starfish to gain maximum score.
With golden sand, coconut trees, sand castles, crabs, and a gorgeous sunshine, what more do you need?
Features: Interactive tutorial Over 20 challenging levels. Put your thinking cap on. Fun beach theme and music Interact with challenging obstacles such as crabs, sandcastles, and more. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Running</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/banana-running/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/banana-running/</guid>
      <description>Play as Mr. Nanners, the funniest banana in town with a unique voice.
Unfortunately, Mrs. Nanners is missing, and it&amp;rsquo;s your job to find her in this endless runner.
Run along the city streets in your quest to find Mrs. Nanners. Slide left, right, and under obstacles while collecting Mrs Nanners dolls.
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to collect Banana Balls, and use them to upgrade your gear.
Features: Funny banana theme. Funny banana jokes with voiceover dialogues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gravity Kid</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/gravity-kid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/gravity-kid/</guid>
      <description>Hey you, Gravity Kid with a cool beanie hat. Quick, put on your anti-gravity shoes and start running!
Avoid obstacles, gaps, and oh, did we mention there&amp;rsquo;s a cop on your tail?
Features: Collect coins to upgrade your skills Collect powerups such as shields, coin magnets, and a slow motion potion Practise your reflex skills Pumping music and very street / urban theme Interactive tutorial </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tripoly</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tripoly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tripoly/</guid>
      <description>Rotate the triangle, to match the color of the line.
How high can you score?
Features: Fast and upbeat theme Interactive tutorial Easy to start, but it gets challenging very quickly </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confident Driver</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/confident-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/confident-driver/</guid>
      <description>How fast are your reflexes? Control your car, pick the right lanes and avoid any crashes to win the level.
Features Drive alongside other vehicles such as mini coopers, new york taxi cabs, trucks, police cars and more Precise and accurate turning, allowing users to cut really sharp corners Beautiful graphics with vehicles closely resembling real vehicles A variety of obstacles such as oil spills, roadblocks, ice and more Challenging levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Triangle Wars</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/triangle-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/triangle-wars/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re a lone spaceship lost in space. Attack other spaceships to survive in the vastness of space. Aim for the highest score.
Features: Interactive tutorial to ease learning curve Endless gameplay Space like physics, for fans of Space Invaders 90s retro games Pick up a variety of powerups such as bombs, splash bullets and extra lives Battle intelligent boss ships Energetic theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Echo Simon</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/echo-simon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/echo-simon/</guid>
      <description>Simon says &amp;hellip; watch the sequence.
Memorize the sequence, then recreate it.
How high can you score?
Features: interactive tutorial endless gameplay easy to learn, difficult to master be prepared for surprises at later levels </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trixology</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/trixology/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/trixology/</guid>
      <description>Rotate the piece to fit the grid below. Fans of modern tetris, you&amp;rsquo;ll love this game.
Cover a full row without gaps, and earn yourself bonus points.
How high is your score?
Features: Clear instructions to learn the ropes Minimalist theme ensures focus for long gameplay and time spent Additional controls such as speed down, accelerate, and rotate clockwise / counterclockwise Increasingly difficult as the level progresses </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jumping Burger</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jumping-burger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/jumping-burger/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re a sliding burger with jumping ability.
Avoid obstacles such as ketchup bottles, birds and tiny mice as you slide forward, while collecting ingredients to unlock the perfect burger.
Ingredients include lettuce, tomato, cheese, burger patties, mushroom and salmon fillets.
Grab Chillis to be come temporarily invincible.
How far can you go?
Features: Cute restaurant diner setting Easy to play, hard to master. This game is very challenging. A shop to unlock your burgers </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sky Castle</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sky-castle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sky-castle/</guid>
      <description>My liege, stack the castle parts above each other. Stack them high and strong. Be the ruler of the tallest castle in the world.
Features: Endless gameplay. Spend hours trying to perfect your placement. The castle becomes more challenging to build as they get higher Simple controls: tap to place castle blocks Use a variety of helpers such as Reverse, Repeat, Insurance, and Double Coins Beautiful graphics and ancient medieval theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Line</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/draw-one-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/draw-one-line/</guid>
      <description>Draw one single line, without ever lifting your finger or mouse.
How many levels can you complete?
Deceptively simple, yet profoundly deep game.
Features: Interactive tutorial Over 120 challenging levels to keep you occupied Upbeat, rhythmic theme How difficult can this be? Just Draw 1 Line! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skeleton Defense</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/skeleton-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/skeleton-defense/</guid>
      <description>Soldier! You&amp;rsquo;re the last hope for humanity. It&amp;rsquo;s up to you to stop the waves of undead skeletons.
Features: Interactive tutorial to learn the ropes Scary skeleton theme 7 different weapons. Use rifles, grenades, rockets, molotov cocktails and other impressive weapons to stop these skeletons 5 different skeleton types Unlimited gameplay A shop to upgrade and unlock new weapons </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowboard Hero</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/snowboard-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/snowboard-hero/</guid>
      <description>Snowboard your way down the mountain, while avoiding the obstacles. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash!
Features: Interactive tutorial. Anyone can play this game! Fast, pumping music suitable for X sports. Beautiful winter christmas landscape. Collect banners to earn extra points. Fans of winter skifree xmas or snowboarding will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stack the Pancake</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stack-the-pancake/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/stack-the-pancake/</guid>
      <description>Drag and drop the pancake from the pan, onto the plate. It&amp;rsquo;s that simple!
How many pancakes can you pile up? Use your creativity to build stable and towering pan cakes!
Features: Interactive tutorial Fun casual theme, suitable for everyone Addictive stacking gameplay. Make your users compete to get the highest score Intuitive touch based controls </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dominoes</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dominoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/dominoes/</guid>
      <description>Draw dominoes: Every round, match tiles until your opponent is unable to move. If you have no possible moves, draw a domino until you can match a tile. If there are no dominoes left, pass your turn until you can. Reach 100 points to win.
Block dominoes: The same as Draw Dominoes. The main difference is, if you have no possible moves, pass your turn until you can match a tile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typing Fighter</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/typing-fighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/typing-fighter/</guid>
      <description>Type fast, type accurate and fight hard in this innovative street fighter style typing game.
Charge up your typing and deliver killer power moves.
Get inspired by motivational phrases and quotes while you type.
Fight against a variety of opponents.
Features: Beautifully designed street fight urban setting Fluid character animations Over 200 motivational quotes and phrases to keep you going </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beach Volley</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-volley/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/beach-volley/</guid>
      <description>Move your turtle to hit the ball.
Keep the ball from falling into your own court.
First to score 10 wins!
Features: Beautiful and minimalist beach theme Really cute sea turtles Challenging AI </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkour Climb</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-climb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-climb/</guid>
      <description>Tap to jump from wall to wall, parkour style.
How high can you climb up, in this parkur free running game?
Features: Modern futuristic theme Collect shields to stop your fall Collect jetpacks to boost your score Responsive design </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sort the Trash</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sort-the-trash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/sort-the-trash/</guid>
      <description>Protect the environment by learning how to recycle correctly.
Collect items that can be recycled only. Avoid collecting contaminators such as organic waste, disposable coffee cups, plastic straws, ceramic dishware and lithium ion batteries.
Go green and save the Earth. Start becoming eco-friendly today!
Features: Simple elegant design Responsive design Positive them with recycling facts </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubble Invasion</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bubble-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bubble-invasion/</guid>
      <description>Defend your base against the invasion of bubbles.
Match 2 or more bubbles of the same color to eliminate them.
Don&amp;rsquo;t let any bubble cross the line!
How high can you score?
Features: Simple, minimalist bubble shooter theme Endless bubble shooter gameplay Responsive design Use a variety of power ups such as freeze, lightning, explosions and rainbow bubbles to gain a competitive edge </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commando Boat</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/commando-boat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/commando-boat/</guid>
      <description>Commando! Drive your speed boat behind enemy lines.
Avoid incoming obstacles such as river mines, tree logs, rocks and other boats.
Shoot and destroy obstacles with bullets.
This is a new and reimagined casual shoot em up game featuring a marine theme.
Features: Collect coins to purchase cool boat models such water raft, speed boat, hovercrafts, and more. Collect powerups including coin magnets, bullets and bubble shields Take ramp to get a cool boost forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knife Master</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/knife-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/knife-master/</guid>
      <description>Throw the knife at the target board.
Score double points for hitting the bullsye.
Sounds easy? As you progress further, you&amp;rsquo;ll need every single ounce of skill and finesse in knife throwing.
Not to mention, you&amp;rsquo;ll need impeccable timing too.
One miss of the knife, and you&amp;rsquo;re out!
Similar to darts, fans of knife throwing and all throwing sports will love this game.
Features: Fast paced knife throwing theme Minimalist look and feel Every challenge is designed exactly the same for each player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bricked</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bricked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/bricked/</guid>
      <description>Tap and match bricks of the same color.
Plan your moves carefully, to ensure perfect elimination of the remaining bricks.
How high can you score?
Features: Ability to rewind. You have 3 wishes. Unlimited gameplay. Fun theme </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parkour Run</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/parkour-run/</guid>
      <description>Run along rooftops, jump through windows, hang from ledges, and slide under giant water tanks.
Perform various cool parkour inspired tricks using various vectors and angles, but be careful not to fall!
How far can you go in this endless runner platformer game?
Features: Exciting and fast paced music beats Simple minimalist graphics and urban style Addictive and repetitive gameplay, perfect for high score seekers Desktop and mobile friendly controls </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pipe Master</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pipe-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pipe-master/</guid>
      <description>Rearrange the pipes to make the water flow.
Build your pipe line and convey water from starting to end point. Don&amp;rsquo;t run out of moves!
Features: Beautiful pipe and water graphics Interactive tutorial Over 24 challenging levels. Level 1 is easy, but start wrecking your head with Level 2. Great music and sound effects Full screen version available This game is great for puzzle and cognitive game fans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Numbers Challenge</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/numbers-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/numbers-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Which side is greater? Left, right or are they equal?
Numbers Challenge is a new and exciting cognitive math based game.
Answer 5 questions in a row correctly, to move up the level.
Miss one, and the game is over at the end of the level.
Features: Easy to start. The math gets complicated the further you go Peaceful theme, suitable for concentration Tough and tricky questions Accuracy stats for math geeks </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop the Virus</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pop-the-virus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pop-the-virus/</guid>
      <description>With the Coronavirus causing havoc around the world, we all need some time to destress, relax and chill out. Yes, that&amp;rsquo;s 3 different words to induce calm.
Pop as many COVID-19 virus cells before time runs out.
Tap quickly and tap often. Some corona viruses are harder to pop that others. It&amp;rsquo;s because they&amp;rsquo;re sneaky, and they&amp;rsquo;re wearing surgical masks too!
How many covid 19 viruses can you beat? Let&amp;rsquo;s defeat this killer plague together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Lane Racing</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/fast-lane-racing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/fast-lane-racing/</guid>
      <description>Race against other cars.
Tap to switch lanes. Don&amp;rsquo;t crash into other cars!
Keep on your toes and be prepared to switch lanes quickly in this fastlane game.
Features: Endless gameplay Urban hip hop racing theme Extremely simple controls Simple, linear high score system Fans of racing and driving games will love this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lock Master</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/lock-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/lock-master/</guid>
      <description>Tap to start the lock picking process.
Be patient, concentrate and wait until the key touches the orange dot.
When the moment is right, tap to unlock and score a point in this fast, hypercasual game.
How many locks can you unlock?
Features: Easy to play, hard to master Great spy and thief theme Overcome distractions and obstacles in each level </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climb the Rocks</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/climb-the-rocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/climb-the-rocks/</guid>
      <description>Wait for the right moment to grab the next rock.
Climb one rock at a time. Avoid unstable rocks, while keeping an eye at the prize.
Can you conquer Mount Narya?
Features: Feeling strong like Rocky? Try other more challenging mountains such as Mount Kibar, Alru, Chota, Ordh and Ucca. Endless gameplay Collect diamonds to unlock new mountain climbing characters. Challenging outdoor environment Great theme and music </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
