<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fighting on ArcadeBoom</title>
    <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/fighting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fighting on ArcadeBoom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:03 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/tags/fighting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tank Battle</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tank-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/tank-battle/</guid>
      <description>Two tanks emerge on the battlefield. Only one will survive. Can you outsmart the other tank?
Collect ammo crates and powerups. Navigate your way to the enemy tank. Fire away!
This is the perfect game to play with friends and family.
Tip: For two player mode, play on the same device (one finger on each side). Enhance social interaction of your audience!
Features: Interactive tutorial to learn the ropes Collect different powerups such as additional health, bubble shields and speed boost Randomly generated battlefield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pro Wrestling Action</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pro-wrestling-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:37:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/pro-wrestling-action/</guid>
      <description>Get ready to rumble! Punch, kick, and wrestle your way through to be the last man standing.
Knock out your opponents, then throw them out of the ring!
Need to perform a spectacular feat? Climb the ropes, time your jumps and dive on the opponent.
Collect coins to upgrade your favourite wrestler in the shop.
Features: Simple controls to maximize fun. Start kicking and punching right away! Entertaining wrestling theme Clever and not so clever computer opponents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Survival</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/zombie-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:36:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/zombie-survival/</guid>
      <description>A strange virus outbreak turned your friends into zombies. Armed with a basic pistol, make your way through hordes of zombies.
How many days can you survive, before you become one of them?
Features: 3D like isometric graphics Collect coins with each zombie kill Multiple weapons to purchase. Try the machine gun, shotgun, rifle and laser gun Fun stats to review after each day 3 different gameplay modes: Survival, Hard Point and Nuke Tutorial to learn the ropes Yes, you can blow up barrels to burn the zombies </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typing Fighter</title>
      <link>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/typing-fighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:35:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/arcadeboom/games/typing-fighter/</guid>
      <description>Type fast, type accurate and fight hard in this innovative street fighter style typing game.
Charge up your typing and deliver killer power moves.
Get inspired by motivational phrases and quotes while you type.
Fight against a variety of opponents.
Features: Beautifully designed street fight urban setting Fluid character animations Over 200 motivational quotes and phrases to keep you going </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
